Previously on Alphas...
Agent Sullivan just called.
We have an Alpha missing--
Skylar Adams.
Skylar's smarter than
just about anyone.
She was always
inventing things.
Are you looking
for my mommy?
I was going to head out
to, uh--to the coffee shop.
Are you asking me out
on a date?
If we're gonna try this,
we're gonna need
to take it slow.
Slow is good.
Dr. Rosen...
Cornell Scipio.
- Is that a photic stimulator?
- There's 42 different models.
You remember the young woman
who built you your phone?
- Yeah, Skylar.
- Do you still have it with you?
She said I could call her
on this.
She might be the one
to figure out
how this thing works.
Identities of all volunteers
remain classified.
The purpose of the study
is to test reactions
to various frequencies
of light oscillation.
Project Bluebird,
Artichoke, Paper Clip--
you believe these names?
These Cold War programs were
the government's first attempts
to explore the limits of
the human neurological system.
And one of
the more promising experiments
was photic stimulation--
visual stimulus
to alter brain activity.
But as you can see,
some pretty
horrible results.
I still don't get
the connection to your toy here.
You said they use this
to treat people for epilepsy
and Parkinson's
and lazy eye syndrome.
Well, Bill, Stanton Parish
somehow managed to coerce
Senator Burton to fast-track
this particular device
through the FDA.
I seriously doubt
he was concerned
with lazy eye syndrome.
So you had Kat
take this thing apart.
She couldn't find anything.
Yeah, but why?
Why, Bill, was it used
so deliberately
on that Jason Miller kid
in the hospital?
It enhanced his Alpha ability,
which put you and the rest
of the team in danger.
Thousands of these are due
to be distributed right now.
I'm convinced that this--
this--well, whatever it is--
is a crucial part
of Parish's war plans.
And I hate to think
what will happen
if I can't figure out
what it does.
Well, whatever it is,
Nathan Cley needs this on his
desk tomorrow morning, okay?
That is evidence.
Yeah, well,
it's not going to be
on Nathan Cley's desk
tomorrow morning.
It's going to be
on Skylar Adams's.
If anyone can figure this out,
it's her.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
You know, I checked.
Health inspectors eat here.
I'm so sorry.
It's--
it's a force of habit.
Oh.
You know what?
I should get going.
You're really not gonna
tell me where you're going?
Dr. Rosen's being really
paranoid about security.
You know
I'm head of tactical, right?
Your boss is making it really
hard for me to do my job.
Do you want to come along
to protect me?
That's sweet.
Look, I just--
I'm sorry.
- No, no--
No, John, I'm sorry.
I--
I'm trying, okay?
And we'll get there, but...
I got to go.
Dr. Rosen,
why do I have to go?
I don't want to go.
I don't like going places.
Gary, you're part
of the team.
And I want everyone
doing security.
No, but Bill--
he does the security.
'Cause Bi--
Bill's the muscle,
and the muscle is
in the arm.
I'm the brain, and the brain
stays in the head.
The office is the head.
That's my metaphor.
Right, right.
That's a great metaphor, Gary,
you are the brains, okay?
Yeah, well,
then tell Dr. Rosen--
the brain stays in the head.
Gary, when Stanton Parish
finds out we have this device,
he's going to come
looking for it.
You are too important
to be left behind.
You monitor signals.
No one else can do that,
all right?
You're going.
Oh, okay. But then you ha-
you have to appease me.
Appease you?
Okay, all right, Gary,
how about you pick
where we stop for lunch?
Yeah, that's good.
How about we let him
drive us to lunch?
- No, no, I'm the shotgun.
- I'm gonna let you drive.
That's fool's gold, Bill.
You never let me drive.
Rachel?
- Where are you going?
- To see a guy about a thing.
You gonna miss me?
No.
Well, I bet I can change
your mind on that.
- Hi.
What, you don't like
office hours?
Sorry.
The subway was late.
Bentley's in the shop?
No. The Bentley
was repossessed.
She couldn't afford
to make the payments.
And she's not allowed to push
anyone anymore to keep the car.
So Nina's going, huh?
Yeah. Look, nothing's
gonna happen, okay?
Just trust me.
It's not you
I'm worried about.
Nina's promised to use
her ability for the, uh--
for the good of all.
Yeah, that's like
asking an alcoholic
to only drink in the office.
I need to do this myself,
so I can handle it.
Give her a chance, okay?
She's trying to change.
Yeah.
Cameron, we need to go.
Give my love to Dani.
Your dad says hi.
All right.
I'm the shotgun.
Nothing but trees--
where are we?
Well, I think
we're almost there, Bill.
I think, I think.
You think?
Doc, what exactly
did Skylar say?
Well, she wasn't
all that specific.
No, she hung up on him.
But I'd already
traced the call.
She's 3.2 miles
north of Route 11.
All right, well,
that's around here, then.
Yeah, it is, but it's all--
it's just trees.
There's trees everywhere...
At least on--on Mapquest
and Google maps.
When you're this far out,
you don't want to be found.
Don't--oh, wait, wait!
Stop, stop!
What, what?
- Gary, what are you doing?
- Gary!
Gary!
What are you doing?
It's all gone!
There's no wi-fi.
There's no 4g.
Everything's gone.
Gary, that's what happens
when you're out in the boonies.
Can you just get back
in the van, please?
This is no good.
We have to turn back now.
We're not turning back,
Gary.
Just don't--don't jump
out of the van again.
I don't like the boonies!
Oh, what's this?
Hey.
How you fellas doing?
Just fine.
But you're on private land.
You need to turn around.
Excuse me, we're looking
for a friend of ours
who lives
somewhere around here.
Her name is Skylar Adams.
Hey, D.C.I.S.
Hey! Hey!
You have to respect that badge.
Give me it back.
You're feds.
Get the hell out of here.
Give me.
- Go!
- All right.
Get out of here.
- Cameron, just--
- move it.
Just go ahead.
Look out!
Whoa!
He's an Alpha.
You're right, Gary.
- What do the other two do?
- We don't want to find out.
- Hey, hey.
- He opens doors.
- Hey, hey, hey, back off.
- Guess you're walking.
What do you think
you're doing?
- Let's go!
- Gower!
Back off!
Hello, Skylar.
Dr. Rosen.
- You're Rosen?
- Yes.
Yes--yes, I am.
And, uh--
and you are?
Skylar, are these folks
friends of yours?
No.
Neither are you.
Skylar?
Go home.
♪ Alphas 2x06 ♪
Alphaville
Original Air Date on August 27, 2012
♪
♪ Don't take no ♪
♪ for an answer ♪
♪ and there's no telling ♪
♪ where we've been ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
♪ 'cause people
don't understand ♪
♪ understand,
understand ♪
♪ people don't understand ♪
♪ people like me ♪
Skylar.
Skylar, listen to me.
I know I promised I'd never
make contact with you again,
but I need your help.
- We don't help outsiders.
- What do you mean, "we"?
I thought you weren't
with those people.
Just tell me what you want.
All right.
Thank you, Nina.
I need you to take a look
at this.
It appears to be
a photic stimulator,
but I think
it's much more than that.
You want to use me
for my abilities?
I'm shocked.
Take it to the genius bar.
Skylar.
Skylar...
This is important.
I took a tremendous risk
helping you elude the NSA.
I did not have to do that.
Really?
You're playing that card?
- Hey! Over here!
- Kids, come this way!
Wait up!
So this is where
you ended up--
a town full of Alphas.
It's just an old summer camp
they fixed up--
a place for refugees.
Refugees from what?
The neuro-typical world...
from you.
You don't look
too impressed.
No. With all these
Alphas here,
you never know
who's a Parish sympathizer.
So we got to keep
our eyes open.
Why don't you stay with Rosen
and the machine?
And I'll do a security check
with, uh, Rachel and Gary.
All right.
Xenon tube, flash header...
50-watt step-down
power supply.
Yeah, yeah,
I know what this is.
It's a photic stimulator.
Skylar, I-I know that.
But t-there's
got to be more to it.
Hey, look who's here.
Zoe, you remember Dr. Rosen.
Hi, Zoe.
- What's this?
- Whoa. Zoe, don't touch.
Don't touch.
I'll show you later.
She never stops.
This is how it always is.
Zoe
what's this?
Zoe, Zoe,
do you like bubbles?
Do you want to know how to blow
a giant bubble that never pops?
How do you do that?
I'll show you.
Come here.
Let's just sit
right here.
Now the first thing
you have to do,
is you have to
take a deep breath.
And then...
blow it out slow.
Here it comes. Here it comes.
Here it comes.
It's getting bigger
and bigger and bigger
and bigger and bigger...
There you go.
Wow. This is
an amazing-looking creature.
Think you could draw
a picture of it for me?
Okay.
Thank you.
How did you do that?
I've had a little experience
raising a equally spirited
one of my own.
She just--
she never stops.
She wakes me up
at 4:00 in the morning
to tell me she discovered
a new prime number.
Well, as they say, the apple
doesn't fall far from the tree.
Didn't you once take apart
your family's Volkswagen
and make an air cannon
or something?
It was a Nissan.
Careful, careful.
That, uh--
that could be dangerous.
More dangerous
than an air cannon?
Yeah, quite possibly.
Gary, do me a favor.
Try to keep your eyes
in the real world, please?
No. I don't like only being
able to see the real world.
It's boring.
I hate it here.
Yeah, well, you know,
this place reminds me
of when my parents used
to send me to summer camp.
I hated it as well.
I couldn't sleep
without the traffic noises,
but after a while, you learn
to appreciate a place like this.
Smell that.
You smell that country air?
Oh. Bees.
Oh, no.
- Gary, come on, back up.
- I don't like bees, Bill.
They have evil intent.
Gary, wait, wait, wait.
Come back.
- Calm down, son.
- Get off! Get off!
Don't let them sting you.
Oh...
You can speak bee.
Basically.
Huh.
You must be
Skylar's friends.
Um, Agent Harken?
Gary?
No. Agent Bell.
I'm an Agent, too.
Claude.
I'm the, uh, founder
of this colony
for people like us.
You're the guy I need to talk
to--I've got some questions
about security arrangements
around here.
We all get along pretty well.
We've never had any incidents.
I doubt we'll have any now.
You always want to prepare
for the worst
and hope for the best, right?
Oh, you're the founder,
so it's your fault
that there's no signals here.
Gary can read
electromagnetic communication,
so he gets a little cranky
in dead zones like this--
Bill!
I'm not cranky.
You're the cranky--
you're always cranky.
Yeah.
It's not exactly dead
around here.
Nature is crawling with signals,
if you're open to them.
Excuse me.
Okay.
This is amazing.
She's actually hand-drawing
algorithmic fractals.
Yeah, she's bored
with those.
She's moved on
to complex plane multibrots.
It's like having your own
little computer running around.
At least a computer
comes with a manual
and an "off" switch.
Well, it's not easy
raising an Alpha.
That's why we're here--
it takes a village
and all that crap.
Something is draining
the battery.
Could be a design flaw.
- Dinner, dinner!
- Hey--
Thanks, Claude.
Claude...
Skylar's mentioned you.
I'm Dr. Lee Rosen.
I know who you are.
What's that?
Good question.
I guess I'll be seeing you
at dinner.
- Uh, something I said?
- Actually, yes.
That stunt you pulled letting
the world know about Alphas
didn't make you
any friends here.
Dinner!
Come on, mommy, let's go!
You can leave it.
It's safe here.
No, I-I prefer
to keep it with me.
Wow.
You should see a shrink
about those trust issues.
Gary, where are you going?
What are you doing?
I'm going back
to the office!
Bill, I don't have
my things.
I don't have my pajamas or my
mouth guard for the bruxism.
- Gary, listen to me.
- I can't sleep
without my signals.
Gary, this is part of the job.
We have to be on the lookout
for any outside communication,
anybody trying--
Oh, Bill, I told you-
there are no signals.
It's not--
What?
What, someone out there?
No.
Oh.
What-what do you see?
It's a star.
Gary, we're not here
to look for damn stars.
No, it's good.
Some stars, they--
they send out radio waves.
I know that.
- Gary.
- It's a pulsar.
Gary, you're killing me
right now,
you know this, right?
It's pingy.
Whoo-hoo.
Gary.
Gary!
Gary, listen to me.
It's time to eat, okay?
You're late, okay?
You're late to eat, Gary.
Let's--can we--
can we look at stars
another time?
No, Bill, it's not stars.
It's something else.
It's all--
it's all--
it's yellow
and purple and--and red.
And it's--
it's like curtains,
but they're exploding.
Yeah, that sounds like
the Aurora Borealis, Gary.
I've seen that
in Alaska before.
Huh.
It's the whole sky.
Pretty amazing.
You hungry, Gary?
Hey, let's sit right here--
come on--with Hicks.
I could've killed them both.
Don't sneak up on me
like that.
It's what I do.
You're so quiet, we should tie
a frickin' bell on you.
Parish sent us here
to observe.
No one's around--let's just go
and grab the machine.
If we go for it now,
they'll know it's valuable.
We only move if they figure out
what it does.
What the hell is this?
See, uh,
it's a green algae.
Apparently they grow
their own food.
Really?
Yep. Eat up.
Gary, what's the deal?
I thought we had
radio silence out here.
Oh, yeah. No.
I-I was wrong.
There are signals everywhere.
I just--I wasn't focusing
hard enough,
'cause even the trees
have signals,
and the rocks have signals.
It's all--it's wavelengths,
but it's smaller.
It's like--
even this food.
This food has a signal.
It's go--
it sounds like,
Aw-wa, ba-wawawawa, ba-wawawa--
Yeah, that means
"don't eat me."
That's what this means.
- What else is there?
- 'Cause of the color.
No dessert until you
clear your plate, Digit.
Didge.
Look at you,
all domestic.
You even lasered off
all your tattoos.
Or was that just to make it
harder for the FBI to spot you?
Come on, let's go.
Rebel...
Mom.
I thought this was a place
where Alphas could be free
to be themselves.
Not me.
I'm here for Zoe.
So what, you can't be
yourself and her mom
all at the same time?
Well, right now
I'm kind of sucking at both.
Trouble in the Justice League?
They're not exactly thrilled
to have me around.
Maybe I should just
stay here with you.
That's a load of crap.
I saw you.
You were happy.
Made me want to throw up.
Yeah, but I ruined it.
And now when I'm with them,
I just feel alone.
This is delicious.
Honey wine.
You made this?
- The bees do all the work.
- Mmm.
It's human nature
to exploit
the special abilities
of other creatures.
Perhaps.
But it could also be perceived
as two groups working together
for their mutual benefit.
And when one disengages
from that bond,
both suffer.
Have you ever had a brick
thrown through your window?
Have you ever been persecuted
for being who you are?
Claude, I'm sorry,
but Dr. Rosen
has spent his entire career
fighting against exactly
that kind of intolerance--
- Rachel--
- His career?
This is our lives
I'm talking about.
And we did not elect you
to be our spokesman.
You're not one of us.
You never will be.
You're just an outsider
looking in.
Yes, I'll admit it--
I am an outsider.
But let me
ask you this, Claude.
If you knew that your bee
colonies were going to collapse
no matter where
you hide them,
what would you do?
Wouldn't you
try to stop it?
Why'd you come here, huh?
No!
Please, no!
I can kill more than cars.
Hey!
Doc!
Doc, you all right?
Yes, I think so.
Easy, easy, easy.
I got him.
What do you know
about this?
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Put those away!
We don't solve things
with violence around here.
Oh, really?
Perhaps you should tell
your man about that.
I didn't start this, Claude.
The hell you didn't!
You started
the whole damn thing.
My life fell apart
because of you.
My wife left me,
and she took my kids,
all because of you
and your big mouth.
Do you have a name?
- Gower.
- Mr. Gower...
I opened my big mouth
because it was
absolutely necessary.
If you'll just
let me explain--
Gower!
Go home.
Claude--
You can
spend the night here,
but I want you gone
by morning.
Come on.
Let's get back
to our homes.
There gonna be some way
to repair this?
Well, maybe
if you stop touching it.
Ugh.
Gower smashed this one up.
I mean, we replaced
the circuit boards.
Hey, do you see that?
Sneaky-ass,
clever bastards.
What?
W-what have you found?
Control circuits.
Nano-processors embedded
in the wires themselves.
Idiots installed it
all backwards.
Yeah, this photostim has
definitely been tampered with.
Is there any way
to determine
what exactly
has been done to it?
- It's gonna take some time.
- We don't have time, Skylar.
Claude wanted us out of here
first thing this morning.
Lucky you.
Hey, you know, you and Zoe
can come with us.
Actually,
that's a great idea.
No. I brought Zoe here
to be around kids like her.
Every morning I wake up
and wish I could leave.
It was so much easier
when I was alone.
Hey, Zoe.
Zoe.
God!
Mother of the frickin' year.
Digit!
Digit?
Skylar.
Oh!
Ugh!
- Rachel, turn that thing off.
- Yeah, okay.
It's got its own
internal power source.
Maybe if I reconnect it--
Rachel!
Bill!
- Oh, my God, what happened?
- She's having a seizure, Bill.
Rachel, stay with me.
Stay with me.
Dr. Rosen...
Where are you?
I can't see you.
I'm right here.
Zoe?
Digit.
Skylar.
Gary, have you seen my kid?
No, but, Skylar, I'm looking
for something too.
I want to get a cabin,
but I want one with carpet.
Everything here's made of wood,
and I like carpet,
'cause it's all--
it's squishy beneath my toes.
I don't have time for this.
Zoe?
- Aah!
- How did that machine do that?
It's as if that--
that instrument, whatever it is,
has amplified
her Alpha ability.
So...it's like
what happened
to that coma kid
in the hospital, right?
Yes, but whatever adjustment
Skylar made to that thing
has increased its potency.
Rachel, Rachel,
what you're experiencing
is an intensification
of your own ability,
which means
you can probably control it.
Just focus,
go through your protocols.
You can control this.
Zoe?
Zoe!
Didge?
I didn't mean it.
Come back.
Zoe!
Oh, didn't mean to scare you.
So don't sneak up on people
in the middle of the woods.
Who are you?
We want that machine
you fixed.
It's not mine to give.
Yeah, well,
it's not the Doc's either.
See, he stole it.
We want it back.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
- You sure?
- Yeah, fine.
- Here, Rache.
- I'm okay.
Just get this off of me.
I can't breathe, okay?
Just get it off of me.
- Shh, shh.
- Okay, just--I can't breathe.
Oh.
Rachel, what's wrong?
Oh, you look like
one of the faces
from my expressions chart--
j-joyless.
Rachel's sick, okay?
We're gonna take her home,
as soon as Dr. Rosen gets back
with that photostim.
Oh, okay, drive safe...
and really fast.
I'm gonna go and air out
my cabin.
- What?
- Gary, you--
your cabin?
Yeah.
Yeah, number 33.
Claude said
that I could live here.
And, Nina, you can take
your office back,
'cause I-I don't need
my man cave anymore.
Gary, you're not staying.
Let's go. Get in the van.
- No, I am staying.
- Shh! Stop talking so loud!
I make up my own mind.
I make my decisions.
Gary, there's no
Thai food here,
no Chinese, no take-out,
nothing.
Come on.
No, you're--
you're trying to trick me.
I told you,
I-I'm not leaving!
Oh, God.
Gary!
Gary, have you seen
Skylar anywhere?
- Oh. Yeah, yeah.
- Where?
She went into the trees.
She was looking for Zoe.
I was listening to the sun.
Yeah, well, if you see her,
tell her I'm looking for her.
Yeah, in the--okay.
Where is she?
That's not how this
is gonna work.
90,000 volts--
that's how it's gonna work.
Where is she?
Hey, Doc.
Long time no see.
You're looking good.
Skylar, please don't give
Mr. Scipio that instrument.
He can't be trusted.
He works for Stanton Parish.
They don't care who they hurt!
Come on, Doc, that any way
to talk about an old friend?
We used to have something.
- He has Zoe.
- What?
Lee, you are the reason
why he's here.
We were safe--
Aah!
Doc, come on,
I'm taking that bag.
Why did you do that?
How are we gonna find her now?
We'll find her, I promise.
We have to get out of here!
Go! Go!
We have to get to the van!
Rachel, let us know
when you hear something.
Stop, stop!
Stop the car!
Just let me--
just let me hear, okay?
- What, Rachel?
- Let me just listen!
I hear a child,
breathing hard.
She's scared.
There's somebody with her.
They're indoors.
All right, how far?
Where?
1/4 mile, that way.
Skylar, wait, wait.
It's too dangerous.
- No.
- She'll be fine.
- It's my daughter.
- Skylar!
Skylar! Skylar!
Aah!
Want to do your thing?
Want to let them know
we're coming?
I don't think so.
Hey, want to come
do your thing?
Over on this side.
That open window
right up there.
It's all you, baby.
Yeah.
Do you smell that?
- What?
- Smell what?
It's a fire.
The forest is burning.
It's heading east,
towards the camp.
- That's over a mile away.
- Get in.
Move.
- Look out!
- Run, Zoe!
Aah!
Hey! Hey!
Let me go!
Stand still!
Come here!
Stop!
Look, all we want is the kid.
So let me out
and give me the machine.
Fair trade.
Can't do it, sweetheart.
You're Hicks, right?
My sister told me
about you.
She said she kicked your ass
at Highland Mills.
That's not quite
how I remember it.
Oh, yeah?
Well, you'll remember this.
- You okay?
- Do I look okay?
Get me up.
Where is she?
Where's Zoe?
- Uh, she--
- Where is she?
She's that--
she went that way.
Come on, go, go, go, go.
Zoe!
Mommy's here.
Mommy!
Easy, easy.
Good. You found her.
Come on!
Let's go! Come on!
Okay.
We got to get out of here,
now, now!
All right.
You should've played nice.
No, no, no.
Get back.
Back, back!
Go, go, go!
It's okay.
- Easy, easy, easy.
- Don't worry, honey.
Don't worry.
There's no way we're gonna
make it out of here!
Zoe, you stay
with Hicks, okay?
I got her.
I can fix this.
Everybody, come on!
Hurry up!
Let's go! Move!
Let's keep moving here!
What are you still doing here?
I'm trying to help.
Dr. Rosen!
- Gary!
- Dr. Rosen.
My eyes are all red.
I can't see.
- Go, get in the car.
- Come on, come on.
I'm the shotgun.
Just get in the car, okay?
Gower, go, I've got her.
I've got her.
Here you go.
Claude, what can I do?
Haven't you done enough?
I need that canister.
Here you go.
Okay, give me the hose.
All right.
Hurry.
Let me help.
Okay.
Here, right there.
You lost
213ccs of blood.
That's 7.223868 fluid ounces.
I rounded.
Yeah, I'm gonna take
your word for it, kid.
Take the washers.
- I got 'em, here.
- Okay.
What else?
Make sure
that connection's tight.
Will it work?
Do you know my mommy?
Zoe, come here.
Come on, get out of here.
- What about you?
- I'll be fine. Just go.
- Thank you!
- Go!
Hicks. Hicks!
Come on.
Skylar!
Where's Skylar?
They got out.
Let's get out of here.
Oh, he's hurt.
He's hurt.
Are you okay?
Yeah, yeah.
I stopped bleeding. I'm fine.
Ah, Doc, he's bleeding.
We stopped it.
What happened?
We have to get him
to a hospital.
I'll drive.
A wildfire that broke out
earlier today
near White Mountain National
Forest is reportedly contained,
although a code orange
air-quality alert
remains in effect.
- What are you drawing there?
- A picture of us.
You're a pretty cool kid,
you know that?
I know.
Where's the red one?
This part needs to be red.
Maybe it fell.
Thank you.
They roll everywhere.
She is very talented.
Hitting on a single mom
via her kid--
it's kind of creepy.
I'm not hitting on you,
Ms. Adams.
You're far too young for me.
I'm bringing you an offer.
A child like Zoe--she needs
an environment
that she can thrive in,
as do you.
Who are you?
I'm Stanton Parish.
I believe you met some
of my colleagues recently.
I apologize
for their behavior.
They have
the unfortunate tendency
to get carried away.
What do you want?
To give you
an opportunity...
help make the world
a better place.
Isn't that what every mother
wants for her child?
- Hey.
Heard you had
a rough trip.
My whole world opened up.
I mean, my senses...
It's just--they got bigger
than ever before.
Dr. Rosen doesn't know
if I'll ever...
go back to the way I was.
I would've brought you
flowers, but...
I know the smell
would bother you, so...
What?
You just...
you get me.
You really do.
It's weird, right?
Like, everything's turned up
so high, but...
I'm still here.
Maybe...
Cam...
You could have been killed.
No.
But if it was a couple inches up
and to the right,
I really might've been
in trouble.
I'm so sorry.
Hey, it's not your fault.
Yeah.
No, I know.
It's just--
Besides, if I play
my cards right,
I just might get
medical leave.
You can nurse me
back to health.
Let me guess.
You told Cley that machine
got burnt up in the fire.
Yes. A tragedy.
He was disappointed.
One of these days, Doc,
crap is gonna come back
and bite you in the ass.
You know that, right?
What's on your mind, Bill?
Scipio knew that
we were gonna be there.
I know.
Someone close to us
is working with Parish.
Bill, I want you
to vet everyone.
Cley's office,
the D.O.D. staff,
families, friends, everyone,
even Kat.
All right, I'll bring Hicks
and Gary up to speed.
No.
They don't need to know.
This is just between you
and me.
Find this person, Bill.
And when we do?
Just find him.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org