Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
You know, we're gonna probably have
to sleep in my sister's empty room.
Probably don't even hold
my hand around around her.
It's gonna be good, right?
Hey, um, you told her I was coming, right?
I actually haven't gotten
a chance to talk to them yet.
Stop this.
Are you serious?
Just make a good impression.
They're very protective.
Oh. Oh, okay.
Oh, I see... I see the game we're playing.
I literally almost...
I was like, "Just leave me here.
I'm just gonna live in the subway forever."
- God.
- They're gonna love you.
Oh, yeah. I really hope so. Yeah. Yeah.
...exit in an orderly fashion.
All service at this station is suspended.
- That's weird, right?
- This is an emergency.
I don't know. Trains go out all the time.
At least we didn't get stuck in the tunnel.
All service at this station is suspended.
That's like a real-life thing that happens?
You just get stuck down there?
Yeah, one time we had a blackout,
and I had to use my phone for light.
- Are you serious?
- Mm-hmm.
That... You just described my worst
nightmare to me, just right back at me.
Gives me anxiety just to think
about being stuck there.
Why are you acting like such a baby?
I'm not a baby. You're a baby.
Your face is a baby.
But it's a normal human-being thing not to
want to get stuck underground, you know.
Why do you say I'm weird? Tell me.
Because you're not being very manly.
Aren't you supposed to be all,
you know, protective and tough?
Oh. Okay, cool.
I'm supposed to be protective of you.
I would, if I had, like, an incentive.
- Like what?
- Um, I can't think of...
Yeah, it feels a little better.
- Mm-hmm.
- I... Yeah.
Manlier, macho, I'd say.
Shut up.
Okay, this is a little weird.
Nobody here, huh?
- Where'd everybody go?
- I don't know.
They're just ahead of us, right?
It's probably just a drill.
- After you.
- Thank you.
Yeah.
Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. What the fuck?
Holy shit!
- Holy shit.
- We got to...
- No, no, no. Don't.
- What? We just leave him there?
All right.
- Um, let's just...
- Let's just...
No, no, no. Let's just go.
We got to get out of here.
- All right. What...
- Is there police around?
Where the fuck is everybody?
Let's get up to the street.
Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Back up. Back up.
- This is not normal.
- What the hell's going on?
Something seriously must be wrong.
Holy shit.
Emergency alert.
I don't know. I've never
seen anything like that.
This is an active combat zone.
Deadly force will be employed against...
All right.
No, no, no. Where are you going?
You stay here where it's safe.
I'm just gonna go check it out.
Honey, I'll be right back, okay?
- Don't. No!
- Stop.
Jose?
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Oh, my God!
Emergency alert.
Oh, my God.
Holy shit. Holy shit.
Okay. Um, I'm... I'm gonna go get help.
I'm gonna go get help.
Oh, my God. I'm gonna go
get help at the hospital.
Help! Somebody help me, please!
Somebody help me!
Get the fuck down!
My boyfriend! He's...
They're coming around!
What the...
Hey!
Stop!
Who the fuck are you?
Stay the fuck down!
Ow! I can't breathe.
Ow! That fucking hurts.
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Shit.
Okay.
- Man, fuck this.
- All right. All right.
- Hey!
- Fuck was that?
Motherfucker went over there.
- You good?
- Yeah.
Go ahead. Go ahead.
Go ahead. I got you.
Where the fuck you go?
Nothing.
Empty in here, too.
Oh, ho, ho. Look at this. What do you think?
You think someone lives
in this fucking shithole?
I fucking hope not.
All right. Well, grab what you can.
Yo, it fucking stinks in here.
Old-ass shit everywhere.
All right. All right.
- You ready?
- Yeah.
One, two, three.
Oh, hey! Whoa! Whoa! Hey!
Damn! Fuck, bro! She fuckin' maced me, bro!
Oh, yeah. And it's a bitch. Get up.
- Fuck her up!
- Up.
Ah, ah, ah. Drop it.
Drop it.
Hands on your head. Hands on your head.
Thank you.
It fucking burns, man.
Look at that. That's all you got?
This cheap piece of shit?
Come on, give me your fucking purse, now!
Fucking chump change, man.
Hey. Hey. You ain't got nothing, do you?
Get on the bed.
- No.
- N...
Oh. No?
No?
White bitch got something to say, huh?
Hey, you think you're better than us?
- Huh?
- No, I don't.
Bushwick is our neighborhood.
When you white bitches gonna learn that?
I'm from here, and I'm just
trying to go home.
- Oh, you're from here? Oh.
- Look at that.
- Oh she's got tears.
- She's from here.
Get the fuck out of here, you're from here.
I will give you a reason to cry.
How about that?
Yeah. One big-ass reason.
Damn. Let's see what you got under here.
Looks good.
- Oh!
- Oh! What the fuck?
Who do you think...
Oh, my God!
Oh! You fucking bitch.
Are you okay?
Are they dead?
- What are you doing in my house?
- I'm... I'm sorry.
You can't just come into
someone's house like that.
- They followed me in here.
- You need to leave.
- They were gonna attack me.
- You need to get out of here.
Do you know what's going on?
There's, like, a whole fucking army
out there that's just killing people.
And I was on the L train,
and there was a man...
Why are you out here?
- What?
- Why are you in Bushwick?
I live here.
And I'm just... I was trying to...
I'm just... I'm home from school, and I'm
trying to just get to my grandma's house,
and she just lives a couple blocks away.
And I...
Fuck. I was supposed to call her
when I got off the...
The cells are overloaded or blocked.
I don't have any cell service.
You're not gonna get through.
She's probably freaking out because I was
supposed to be there already by now.
Oh, God.
Hey. Hey.
Can you tell me your name?
What's your name?
Hey.
Lucy.
Hey, just do me a fav...
Don't fucking touch me.
Here. Have some water.
They declared martial law,
and my radio went dead.
Not just here, everywhere...
Boston, Chicago, D.C., Manhattan.
Is, um... Is this 9/11 again?
Terrorists?
No, it's different.
It's more tactical.
Tactical? What do you... What do you mean?
I mean it's more tactical.
This isn't an attack.
This is an invasion.
How do you know this?
I mean, this is... this is Bush... Bushwick.
Who fucking invades Bushwick?
I'm not sure who they are,
so we got to get out of here.
I...
This is just really fucking crazy shit.
I'm... I'm just really confused, and I just
want to know what the fuck is going on.
Strategic plan.
It's overwhelm...
overwhelming our defense system.
Are you a cop or something?
Janitor.
How do you know this?
I really want to just go home.
Good luck.
Wait, where are you going?
Hoboken.
Why?
My wife and my son are there.
Well, I just need to get to Cypress Avenue.
It's just a couple blocks that way.
Sorry. I can't help you.
No, no. Please. Don't leave me here.
Please don't leave me here.
Please.
The main assault's probably over.
They're gonna be canvassing block by block.
Just keep your head down.
You'll be all right.
Wait.
Sniper.
I got it.
Wait. What the fuck are you doing?
Stay down.
You're gonna get us both killed.
This is fucked up. We need to find cover.
Shit.
The school.
Oh, my God.
Come on.
You know where you're going?
I used to go to school here.
What's upstairs?
There's a science lab
and a library and a study hall and, um...
Can we get up to the roof?
Yeah. Teachers used to go up there and smoke.
Okay. Let's get up there
and take a look around
and see if we can see out on the street.
Then we get the hell out of here.
Okay.
Shit.
Do you have a compact?
What?
A compact, the mirror.
Oh, God.
Go.
Go, go, go ahead.
Go ahead.
Don't shoot, please!
Shit.
Hold it. Hold it.
Ah! Grenade!
Oh, fuck.
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
Do you want them to figure out we're up here?
Holy shit. You're bleeding.
Yeah, I know.
I got to take care of it.
We can go over here. Let's go over here.
Oh, my God.
What are you gonna do?
Take this glass out of my leg.
Then cauterize this wound.
I'm gonna need you to help me.
What?
I can't do this.
I don't know how to cauterize a leg.
You... You need a doctor.
Oh!
Hold that there.
Hold it there, just like that.
All right.
Oh, God.
When I take this glass out, I'm gonna
need you to count to five for me, okay?
- Uh, uh, okay.
- Okay?
Take it out, count to five.
Okay. Yeah.
Oh, God.
All right, ready? Count.
One.
Two.
Three, four, five.
Five.
Now what?
I need you to do the other side for me.
- No.
- Just like I did.
- Oh, fuck.
- I need you to do it.
I'm bleeding too much. Okay?
Okay. Uh...
Just like I did. Heat the blade.
At least five seconds, okay?
No less, or it's not gonna work.
Ready?
- All right, do it.
- Okay.
Do it.
Okay. Okay. Oh, God.
One.
Two.
Three, four, five.
Five.
Take the alcohol and pour...
Pour alcohol over it really good, okay?
Really good, all over it.
Oh, God. Fuck. It fucking stinks.
Okay.
Wrap it with that gauze.
Wrap it up good.
Nice and tight, right over the wound.
- All right.
- Okay.
Take that tape and wrap it
around there nice and tight
so that gauze won't come off... come off.
- Okay.
- Is this okay?
Really gonna do it like this?
Okay.
I did it.
Holy shit.
How'd you learn how to do that?
I watched a lot of "ER."
I was in the military.
I was a Marine.
Please, take that. Take it.
What's your name?
Stupe.
- Stupe?
- Call me Stupe. Yeah.
Well, I don't know how to use a gun, Stupe.
Keep your finger off the trigger.
- Don't point it at me.
- I'm sorry.
You look down the barrel.
You line up the front sight
and the back sight.
When you're ready to shoot,
and not until you're ready to shoot,
you put your finger on the trigger,
and you shoot to kill.
Now, we got to get out of here.
Are you ready?
Wait, are you sure you can?
Yeah. I'm good.
You worry about you.
There's a fire escape. Come on.
All right.
Holy fuck.
We're not gonna make it, are we?
We'll make it one block at a time.
Who are they?
I don't know.
What if it's not just Brooklyn?
What if they're in Hoboken, too,
where your family's at?
My family's safe.
Come on.
We can go to Mr. Argo's It's right there.
Right there.
Yo, it's all free now. Stock up.
Is there any new info?
Who cares? Just take whatever you want.
Don't ask questions.
Hey, yo. Let's go.
Are they saying who's doing this?
You have a gun. You figure it out. Peace.
The militants are American.
We don't know that, Fran.
We don't know anything more than
the unreliable eyewitness accounts,
and we just don't have
an official word as of yet.
Why are we being kept in
the dark about all this?
Why is it so important to keep
the public unaware of our situation?
Oh, you've got to be joking.
What you're insinuating
is paranoid and delusional.
I'm saying that, over the last few
years, certain politicians have lied
and swindled and cheated
their way into office,
and this... this kind of domestic terrorism
is not such an illogical conclusion.
We expect to hear from the president shortly.
The government has issued
some initial guidelines.
Stay inside.
Do not answer the door.
The U.S. military will be
setting up extraction points.
This information is coming in
very sporadically.
We'll keep broadcasting as we get more info.
The fucking government.
Bridges and tunnels are closed.
- Useless as usual.
- JFK and LaGuardia are closed.
They got to realize how fucked up this is.
Logan Airport is closed.
My grandmother is not gonna understand.
If soldiers come to her house,
she's not gonna leave.
We have to get there before they do.
Is she close?
She's about a block and a half
on Willoughby Street.
Did you hear that?
Mr. Argo?
Oh, my God. Oh, God. Mr. Argo, what happened?
Candy, they stole candy, fucking candy.
I didn't try to stop them,
but he still stabbed me.
Those guys? They...
Yes.
Ohh. It's all a game to them.
Mr. Argo?
Shit. Mr. Argo?
Lucy. Lucy, we got to get
the fuck out of here.
Okay.
My grandmother's house is that way.
Let's go.
Oh, God. Shit.
Dude, get the fucking bags.
We got to get out of here.
We fucked that guy up, some old dude.
Yo, man, got the keys.
- Got the keys.
- We got to go.
Dragging your ass, man.
Come on, come on, come on.
Yo, come on, man. Let's go.
What the fuck?
Fuck!
Drive, drive, drive.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Oh, God. We need to stop the bleeding.
Oh, shit. Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
What the hell were you thinking?
Are you hit anywhere else?
No.
God damn it. What were you thinking?
Fuck.
My finger. There's so much blood.
Oh, my God.
We'll fix it when we get to your
grandmother's house, all right?
Come on. We got to keep moving.
Damn it.
That's the guy that stabbed Mr. Argo.
He fucking killed Mr. Argo for no reason.
He was gonna shoot this guy, too.
What are you doing?
Giving these to help with the pain.
We can't just leave him here.
- We can't just leave him.
- We can't help him.
We got to keep moving!
Let's go. Let's go!
Okay. Okay.
We're coming in. Open the door.
We will use force.
This is an order.
Grandma, where are you?
Grandma? She must be upstairs.
Grandma? Hello?
Lucy?
Her heart wasn't very strong.
I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry I wasn't here.
Oh, God.
We should... We should get her off the floor.
Fuck! God!
Gonna check the front,
see how much time we have.
Here, take these.
They'll help you and your hand.
I'll be right back.
The neighborhood is fighting back.
We got a few minutes.
Get that hand fixed up,
get the fuck out of here.
Is it bad?
Looks like we stopped a lot of bleeding.
Ow, ow. Shit.
Fuck.
Oh, God. You're such an asshole.
That's what my wife says.
Your wife is a very smart lady.
Bet you can't wait to see her and your kid.
What did you do in the military?
- I was a hospital coroner.
- Ow! Oh, my God!
Oh, my God.
A medic.
So you were a medic. Now you're a janitor.
That's good.
Tired of watching people die.
Oh, God.
I feel weird. I feel really weird.
Like...
I feel like my...
my insides are, like, floating.
It feels good. It feels...
I'm not complaining, but it just...
I don't know what's going on.
I just...
Oh, my God.
What am I gonna do when I get married?
Jose.
I guess it doesn't
really matter anymore, huh?
Why God gave you two hands, right?
Got nine fingers left.
Do you believe in God?
I do.
I believe in God.
Thank you for helping me.
Who said I was helping you?
Open the door.
Is there another way out?
The basement.
Lucy!
Oh, I feel really sick.
My sister's house is that way.
We're gonna go that way.
No. The soldiers went that way.
No. We're gonna go that way.
We're gonna get my sister.
Come on. Let's go.
Well, I'm going.
Lucy!
Fuck!
Goddamn it.
Fuck are you doing?
My sister lives here.
Okay?
- Hey.
- Hi.
- Who the fuck is that guy?
- No, no, no.
- Shut her up.
- Get the fuck out of my house.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey. Hey.
- Lucy!
- Will you shut her up?
- No, no, no. Stop.
Calm down. Relax. Listen to me.
- Get out!
- No, no, no. Listen to me.
Jose is dead, and this guy
saved me from these...
- He's a friend.
- What?
Are you on drugs? Did he fucking drug you?
- No.
- Motherfucker!
Hey, do you have any idea
what's going on right now?
What? No. I've been asleep.
The fucking neighbors have been
blasting "Call of Duty" all day,
and it just woke me up.
You haven't heard any of these helicopters
or anything that's been going on?
Lucy, there's always helicopters.
This is Brooklyn. You've been
gone too long, college girl.
Listen, listen. Sit down. Sit.
Okay. I want you to pay attention to me.
Why are you being so serious?
I was thrown on the ground
and zip-tied by this soldier,
and then there was these two guys
that followed me into this basement.
And then this guy, he helped me.
He saved my life.
What? This is...
This is... This is too much.
My... My brain is gonna melt.
This is... Lucy, this is too much.
I mean, Lucy, I think you're
just a little too high, man.
- But...
- No. I'm not on any...
I mean, I... Well, I am on drugs.
I'm on drugs that he gave me
for my finger, but that's it.
All right. I'm gonna...
I'm gonna go get my shit together,
and then when I get back,
you and me and him,
we're getting out of here.
We're gonna get somewhere safe, okay?
What about Grandma?
She's gone.
No. What?
What?
- What?
- I didn't know what to do.
- No.
- I'm sorry.
Okay.
- I'll be right back.
- Lucy.
Hey, keep an eye on her for me.
That was Oswaldo.
I left the little latch thing open,
and he got out.
Yeah. They'll do that.
What are you...
Are you trying to fuck my sister?
You're sisters?
Yeah. My grandma...
My grandma raised us, so we're sisters.
So don't you try and fuck with
my sister or fuck my sister.
- I'm not trying to fuck her.
- Oh, yeah?
I'm just trying to get through the day.
What are you taking pills for?
What's wrong with you?
I shot a guy. I crushed a guy.
I got glass in my leg, hurts. Needs help.
You, like, a soldier?
I'm a janitor.
A janitor? Right.
I like soldiers.
Hey, what do you think?
It's a cat.
It's a happy pussy.
Meow.
- What the fuck?
- Don't even fucking think about it.
Why are you coming in here?
Are you alone?
Don't come in my house!
Lucy, make sure no one
comes up through that window.
You speak English?
Hey.
Where are you from?
Kentucky, sir.
You're an American?
What the fuck is going on?
Texas is seceding from the United States.
Bullshit.
By the order of the fathers
of the New American Coalition.
We are a united force
with the goal of establishing
an independent nation,
free from government tyranny
and the right to live our lives
the true American way.
Yeah. That makes perfect fucking sense.
- Sir?
- Who's "we"?
Texas, Louisiana, Florida, North Carolina,
South Carolina, West Virginia,
and Georgia are with us.
Parts of Maryland and
Pennsylvania are on the brink.
It's like a... like a new Civil War?
I served with... with good men
from those states.
Yeah. We're a private army.
Mercenaries?
What's the plan?
We'll force Congress to ratify the secession.
Well, how are you gonna do that?
This... This is how we're
gonna do that, insurgency.
What's the plan here in New York?
We were just supposed to lock
down Bushwick, round people up.
No one gets hurt.
Establish a green zone for further operations
and wait for the president to fold.
We, uh... We didn't anticipate
so much resistance from...
resistance from a designated soft spot.
And why the hell is that?
Ethno-diversity, sir.
Racist motherfucker.
I ain't racist. It's fact.
This racist pig fucker thinks
that because there's so many minorities
here in Brooklyn that we won't fight back?
Well, how's that working out for you?
How? How is that working out?
- Our intel told us...
- Fuck your intel.
There weren't supposed to be so many guns.
They're illegal here.
Welcome to New York, stupid motherfucker.
Once we got blowback, they gave us orders
to shoot on sight if our lives were in danger.
Killing innocent Americans.
I'm just following orders. I'm a soldier.
- What'd you say?
- I'm a soldier, sir.
You don't get to call yourself
a fucking soldier.
You're not a soldier!
Sir, I'm sorry, sir. Sir, please.
Please, I was just... just following orders.
Who's in charge?
Who's the fucking asshole who sent you
and all your dumbass buddies
out here to get yourselves
killed for nothing?
No. Nothing.
It doesn't matter. You're a mindless fuck.
Why would you question your orders?
You were in the military, right?
You understand.
- I can't be second-guessing...
- Shut up.
Where's the DMZ?
- Where's the goddamn DMZ?
- Fuck you. I ain't telling you.
I know where the DMV is.
The DMZ.
What's the DMZ?
It's a demilitarized zone.
It's where our troops are embedded,
where they're getting people out.
And you're gonna fucking tell me.
I'm tired of playing games with you.
You have three fucking seconds, or
I'm gonna blow your goddamn head off.
- Please, sir.
- One, two...
Grover Cleveland Park in Queens.
The U.S. Navy and Coast Guard
are evacuating noncombatants
from there, the ones that make it.
The ones you don't kill first.
No one was supposed to fight back, okay?
We had too many casualties.
They gave us orders.
They told us Bushwick was a
shoot-to-kill zone, us or them.
And we were just supposed to fucking take it?
Those were our orders.
It's not my fault.
Fuck your orders.
- Sir...
- Fuck you.
Sir, please...
Cleveland Park.
Three or five blocks at the most.
We don't have much daylight.
What do you want to do?
It's up to me now?
My leg's fucked.
What do you want to do?
Okay. We're getting out of here.
Is it safe to go out there?
Probably not, but it's not safe in here.
Can I get a gun?
No.
What are we gonna do about him?
Ah!
- Let's go!
- Okay.
Just in case he comes back.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. This is real.
I didn't know it was this bad.
I didn't know those guys could fight.
Come on. Let's go. Move.
# If I died in my apartment
like a rat in a cage #
# Would the neighbors smell the corpse #
# Before the cat ate my face? #
Dead yet, pussy?
# I'm trying to jettison the ballast
With the hazardous waste #
Sit your ass down.
# Steep in a self-imposed
Stockholm and Lima in flux #
# Maybe an occupation popular
with demons and ducks #
# Made any mingling akin
to being seasoned and stuffed #
Fuck! These streets
are crawling with soldiers.
Let's make a run for it.
Yo, we got to go upstairs.
Inside, go.
Who the fuck are you?!
- Put your fucking guns down.
- Don't shoot.
Put the fucking guns down.
Don't shoot. We're just...
We're just...
We're just trying to stay alive. Okay?
Put your fucking guns down.
Okay. Everybody relax.
Okay? Just relax.
Okay?
Chill.
Okay. All right.
What the fuck are you doing in our building?
You don't know what's going on out there?
Look... if we can all just get
to Cleveland Park,
the U.S. Army is evacuating
people out of here.
- We can get out of here.
- That what you heard?
What does he mean?
What does that mean? Whoa!
What the fuck is wrong with you, James?
Shut up, Ma.
Get your dumb asses up here and sit down.
I said now!
Go! Hurry up.
Whoa.
The United States Army is set up
at a park over in Ridgewood,
helicopters, tanks, whatever else.
Some people know better than to stick around
in a war zone, James.
You don't remember the '70s.
Eventually, they gonna
get us all out of here.
But we... Right now, we can't get to them.
Coalition fuckers in the way.
- Ain't shit, Ma.
- Shut up, now, James.
My boys are tough,
but they ain't tough enough
to get through that blockade by themselves.
Ma'am, we're not gonna
be enough to fight them.
I'm not talking about you.
Two blocks over, Church of God,
we heard they got 30, 40 people
all riled up and ready to go.
So what's the problem?
James, you want to tell these nice folks
why we can't go and ask Father John for help?
We got issues.
They need our help.
They got some people,
but they ain't got enough guns.
Well, it just so happens that right here,
- down in this basement...
- Ma.
...my boy and his little club...
- It's a gang.
- ...they got all kinds
of weapons... knives, guns, bullets...
for their little dick-swinging gang bullshit.
Ma, they can't have our guns.
Oh, yes, they can.
This is what we gonna do.
James heads over there
and tells them we got they back,
he gets shot.
Me? I wouldn't make it
halfway down the block.
But...
...this sweet little white girl,
she gonna go for us.
No.
You two are gonna stay here for insurance.
- No.
- No. I'm...
You can't send her out there alone.
I'm not doing that.
I go with her or no deal.
I don't recall offering you a deal.
- I'm not going.
- Look. Look, ma'am.
You send her out there alone,
she's just gonna get herself killed.
That's not gonna do
anybody any good, so just...
You let me go with her.
We'll figure it out, all right?
I'm not leaving my sister.
- Please?
- Lucy.
Please?
Your sister will be fine.
You and your bodyguard go tell Father
John we'll meet him at the Laundromat.
Tell him we're going there right now.
You'll see your sister in no time.
- No. No. No.
- No.
James, show these people the front door.
- No. No. No!
- Let's go. Come on.
- Come on.
- No!
- Hurry up.
- Come on. God damn it.
- Lucy!
- Shut the fuck up.
- Shit!
- Get off me.
Why are you doing this?
Don't fuck around. Do what I tell you to do.
- Don't you fucking touch her.
- Oh, this isn't right, man.
We're all from the same neighborhood.
We got to stick together.
We're not from the same neighborhood.
At least give us our guns, man.
Don't send us out there without our guns.
Take your fucking guns.
You better meet me at the Laundromat.
Holy shit.
It's getting worse.
How are we gonna get Belinda back?
Are you okay? Do you need help?
Can you walk?
Thank you for helping. Deborah.
- Whose street?
- Our street.
Whose street?
Lucy.
Bushwick!
Go, go, go.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Go inside.
Come on. Let's go, let's go,
let's go, let's go, let's go.
Jesus.
Do you see him?
No.
He's got to be here somewhere.
Well, let's find him.
Have you seen Father John?
Take these over there
to that woman, all right?
I'll be right back.
Why don't you see if you can find him?
I'm going to help out around here.
Um, excuse me. Where is Father John?
Um, we've seen a few priests,
don't know their names.
Excuse me. Are you Father John?
Who are you?
There's a group,
and they have a lot of weapons.
- And they sent me here...
- I'm not Father John.
He's praying downstairs.
Right through those doors.
Thank you.
Father John?
Hello?
Multitudes in the valley of decision.
For the day of the Lord is near
in the valley of decision.
The sun and the moon grow dark.
Excuse me. Hi.
I'm looking for Father John.
I am Father John.
Oh, okay.
Are you hurt? Are you okay?
We need to go to the Laundromat,
and there's a woman on
Starr Street with her son and...
Is anyone among you sick?
Sick?
No. Wait.
Let him call for the elders of the church.
- I...
- And they will pray over him,
anointing him with oil
in the name of the Father
and of the Son and of the Holy Ghost.
I don't know what you're talking about.
We need your help. We have to go.
You don't understand.
The prayer of faith
will save the one who is sick,
and the Lord will raise him up.
If he is guilty of sin, he will be forgiven.
Oh, shit!
Fuck!
Oh, my God.
You stupid...
Oh, my God. Shit.
- Did you find Father John?
- He's, um... He's gone.
What do you mean, he's gone?
We have to go. We have to go now.
Father John wouldn't leave this congregation.
- He's gone. We have to go.
- You didn't answer me.
Is Father John okay?
He did it to himself.
Okay. Listen. Listen up.
Um, it's not going to be safe
here for very much longer.
So we need to... we need to go.
Anybody who is able, please
help somebody who's injured.
We are going to all meet at the
Laundromat on Cypress Avenue,
where we will meet a group of people that
have a lot of weapons, and from there,
we are going to get to the evacuation
helicopters inside Cleveland Park.
We need to stick together,
but we need to go now.
Stupe, come on. Let's go.
- What happened to Father John?
- We have to go now.
- No. He's gone.
- I can't just leave him...
We have to go. We have to go now.
- Just let me finish this.
- No.
Stupe, come on.
His shoulder is fucked.
Jesus. Go. Go. Go. Stupe.
Just give me two minutes. God damn it.
I will meet you by the front door. Come on.
Lucy! Shit.
Come on. Let's go.
Open this fucking door!
Open the door!
Oh, shit.
Stand down.
Shit.
Holy shit. Are you okay?
Yeah. I'm okay.
Yes, yes. I can get up. I'm okay.
Let's go.
Ouch.
Let's go. Let's get the fuck out of here.
Come on. Go. Go. Move.
I just killed a guy with an ax.
Where is everybody?
I don't know.
Are we supposed to meet them inside?
Are we supposed to meet them outside?
We were just with everybody,
and where did they go?
How long do you think it's gonna
take for Belinda to get here?
I don't fucking know!
Can you be patient for one fucking second?
I don't want to be here any more than you do.
So what year of college are you?
Second-year grad student.
What are you studying?
Civil engineering.
That's great. That's great.
You'll be able to help make a difference.
That's great.
How old's your kid? You never told me.
When my wife and I used to argue,
she'd get pretty worked up at me.
And I'm so stubborn.
She'd get so frustrated, and she'd...
she'd lose her temper with me.
And she'd say, "Stupe,
you're such a fucking asshole."
I can be.
But almost immediately, she'd come over.
And she'd put her hands on my face.
And she'd say, "But you're my asshole."
We were so in love.
And my son...
My son was so beautiful, so smart.
I wish you could have seen him.
They're dead.
They were killed in
the World Trade Center attacks.
And I was so angry.
I was so full of hate.
I just wanted someone to pay.
So I enlisted in the Marine Corps.
About a year and a half later,
they shipped me over to Iraq,
and I got my chance to fight.
I thought it would make me feel better,
but it just made me feel worse.
I did a lot of things I'm not real proud of.
So, uh...
I became a hospital corpsman.
'Cause I thought
if I saved lives, that would...
that would make me feel better, but I just...
I lost more men than I saved.
And one day...
...after months of nightmares
and not being able to keep
my goddamn hands from shaking,
I just stopped.
I just...
I couldn't bear to watch
one more fucking person die.
So they sent me home on a medical discharge,
and I just turned myself off.
For years, I just wanted to be invisible.
And here I am again,
right in the middle of it,
right in the middle of all this
fucking death and killing.
It's like it's being shoved
down my fucking throat,
and it just goes on and on.
It just never stops,
and it's fucking for what?
For what?
When my family died, I died with them.
But we're gonna get out of here.
We're gonna get Belinda.
We're gonna get the fuck out of here.
Thank you for telling me.
I'm sorry I lied to you.
I've just never really
been able to talk about it.
Why'd you tell me you had to go to Hoboken?
I thought if I told you
I was going to Hoboken,
no fucking way you'd try to follow me.
Who the fuck wants to go to Hoboken?
You.
I got to take a piss.
Stupe!
- What the fuck did you do?
- I'm so sorry.
He came at me, and I...
Get the fuck out! Get the fuck out!
Oh, my God.
Stupe.
Stupe. Stupe.
Wake up. Wake up.
Oh, my God. No, no, no, no, no.
Fuck.
I don't know... I don't know what to do.
Just tell me what to do, and I'll do it.
I'll just... Let me help you.
Let me... I don't...
Damn it.
I'm so sorry.
What am I gonna do?
Fuck.
Sorry.
Lucy!
Lucy. Oh, yes!
Ohh. I thought I lost you, too.
Are you okay? What happened?
Did they do... Hey, hey.
Get the fuck away from my sister.
We did exactly what you asked.
Now get the fuck away from...
Hey, hey. Calm the fuck down.
The fight's outside.
You did your thing with the church group,
and we got your sister here.
- You okay?
- Lucy, I'm really okay.
It's really bad outside.
We all just want to get out of here.
Where's the big guy?
Look. You guys can stand
around talking about nothing,
but we're getting the fuck out of here.
- Just give me a minute.
- Wait.
You're wasting time. We're leaving.
Come on!
Lucy, what are you doing?
Fuck me.
Really? He's dead?
That's some shit.
We got to get out of here.
Whoa.
We're going.
- Come on.
- Okay, okay, okay.
Stay close to me.
I'm so scared.
I told you it was fucked up out here.
Stay close to me.
Okay, okay, okay. I'm here.
There's so many people.
You can't even see anything.
Let's get behind this.
We're stuck.
We're not going to be able to get through.
- No, no, no.
- Lucy, let's go.
They have a plan. We just have
to get to those helicopters.
Where are they?
They're right over there.
- Stay near me.
- Okay.
Whoa!
Okay. Let's go.
Don't lose me.
Oh, shit.
- Belinda, wait.
- Got you, bitch.
Get the fuck off me.
Come on. Come on. Get up. We got to move.
Belinda?
This way.
Okay.
You're good. You're good. You're good.
This way. This way. This way.
- The gun's out.
- Drop it, drop it.
Take his gun. Take his gun.
Come on.
Help me. Help me. Help me.
Run and keep shooting!
Yeah? Okay.
Gonna get behind those barrels.
Ready? Okay. Run.
Run!
You okay?
We have to make it through there.
What?
No. Fuck. We're not gonna make it.
Okay. We're gonna pull these. Are you ready?
We're gonna pull these. One, two, three.
- Throw it.
- Throw.
Grenade! Grenade! Grenade!
- Oh, look!
- We found it.
We're almost in. The helicopters
are right over there.
We got to get the fuck out of here.
Oh, shit.
I see the helicopter.
Come on. We're so close.
Everybody keep moving towards the chopper.
Aah!
Stay low.
Belinda!
Okay. I'm coming for you.
Hold on. Hold on. Hold on.
Aah! Aah!
Aah!
Oh. Fuck.
Fuck. Okay. Can you walk?
I can't.
Okay, okay. I'm gonna pull you.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Okay. One.
We're so close. We're so close.
Lucy!
Lucy, get up.
Lucy.
Come on.
No!
Come on, come on.
- Get up.
- I won't leave her.
We got to keep moving.
No!
Lucy!
# Die already, none defy
the one-man walled city #
# Stone made flesh,
veins etched in his hands #
# 88 stance draped in invasive plants #
# And rain dance unsafely,
brace for the supercell #
# Mutiny or footage for your
blooper reel, who can tell? #
# Pours hot tar from the top of the barn #
# Necktie on his head, condor on his arm #
# Dog Star in a jar,
bordering unsustainable #
# Mea culpa, mea culpa,
maybe I should pray occult #
# Systematic Catholic or sigil
of the Baphomet unraveling #
# Either way his ID show a snake and skull #
# Always been a private dude
who couldn't keep a tally #
# Of which lies he told who #
# Flea comb, exorcism, and deworming #
# Fitted for a curse
and a crown of birds circling #
# Search party falling forward unthwarted #
# Meet him at the crossroads,
drawn and quartered #
# For a master of puppets,
how sad are his cupboards #
# Non-dairy creamers, can of last supper #
# And a runneth-over cup
full of black tap water #
# It's a marvel of privacy over pack hunter #
# Raspberry jelly on his Jesus toast #
# And turn heather gray sweats
into Easter clothes #
# With no immediately measurable
crime-wave ice age #
# Christ children still skin a cat sideways #
# I don't pick teams or administer bans #
# I'm in the creek with a pick
and pan, it go #
# Forcibly ejected
or a voluntary death scene #
# Tell 'em what the out-of-order
blinking EMF mean #
# Ghost #
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org