Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
People always ask me
if I know Tyler Durden.
Three minutes.
This is it. Ground zero.
Do you have a speech for the occasion?
With a gun barrel between your teeth,
you speak only in vowels.
I can't think of anything.
For a second, I forget about
Tyler's controlled demolition thing
and I wonder how clean that gun is.
It's getting exciting now.
That old thing,
how you always hurt the one you love.
Well, it works both ways.
We have front-rowseats
for this theatre of mass destruction.
The Demolitions Committee
of Project Mayhem
wrapped the foundations
of 12 buildings with explosives.
ln two minutes,
primary charges will blowbase charges
and a fewblocks willbe reduced
to smouldering rubble.
I know this because Tyler knows this.
Two and a haIf.
Think of everything we've accomplished.
Suddenly I realise that all of this,
the gun, the bombs, the revolution,
has got something to do
with a girl named Marla Singer.
Bob. Bob hadbitch tits.
This was a support group
for men with testicular cancer.
The big moosie slobbering all over me,
that was Bob.
We're still men.
Yes, we're men.
Men is what we are.
Bob had his testicles removed.
Then hormone therapy.
He developed bitch tits because
his testosterone was too high
and his body upped the oestrogen.
- That was where I fit...
- They'll have to drain my pecs again.
..between those huge sweating tits
that hung enormous,
the wayyou'd think of God's as big.
OK, you cry now.
No, wait. Back up. Let me start earlier.
For six months, I couldn't sleep.
I couldn't sleep.
With insomnia, nothing's real.
Everything's far away.
Everything's a copy of a copy
of a copy.
When deep space exploration ramps up,
it'll be the corporations that name everything.
The IBM Stellar Sphere.
The Microsoft Galaxy.
The Planet Starbucks.
I need you out of town this week
to cover some red flags.
It must have been Tuesday.
He had on his corn flower blue tie.
You want me to deprioritise my reports
until you advise of a status upgrade?
Prioritise these. Here's your flight coupons.
Call me if there's any snags.
He was full of pep.
Must have hadhis grande latte enema.
Like so many others, I had become
a slave to the Ikea nesting instinct.
Yes. I'd like to order
the Erika Pekkari dust ruffles.
- Please hold.
- Anything clever,
like a coffee table in the shape ofa yin-yang,
I had to have it.
The Klipsk personal office unit.
The Hovetrekke home exerbike.
Or the Ohamshab sofa
with the Strinne green stripe pattern.
Even the Ryslampa wire lamps of
environmentally-friendly unbleached paper.
I'd flip through catalogues and wonder
''What kind of dining set
defiines me as a person?''
I had it all. Even the glass dishes
with tiny bubbles and imperfections,
proof that they were craftedby the honest,
hard-working, indigenous peoples of...
- Please hold.
- ..wherever.
We used to read pornography.
Now it was the Horchow collection.
- No. You can't die of insomnia.
- What about narcolepsy?
I nod off, I wake up in strange places.
I have no idea how I got there.
- You need to lighten up.
- Can you please just give me something?
Red andblue Tuinals, lipstick-red Seconals...
No. You need healthy, natural sleep.
Chew some valerian root
and get more exercise.
Hey, come on.
- I'm in pain.
- You wanna see pain?
Swing by First Methodist, Tuesday nights.
See the guys with testicular cancer.
That's pain.
I always wanted three kids...
two boys and a girl.
Mindy wanted two girls and a boy.
We never could agree on anything.
well, I... She...
She had her first child last week.
A girl.
With... With her... With her new husband.
Fuck!
Thank God, you know...
I'm glad for her.
She deserves...
Everyone, let's thank Thomas
for sharing himself with us.
Thank you, Thomas.
I look around this room,
and I see a lot of courage.
And that gives me strength.
We give each other strength.
It's time for the one-on-ones.
So let's all of us follow Thomas's example
and really open ourselves up.
Could you find a partner?
And this is how I met the big moosie.
His eyes already shrink-wrapped in tears.
Knees together. Those awkward little steps.
- My name is Bob.
- Bob?
Bob had been a champion bodybuilder.
You know that chest expansion programme
on late-night TV?
That was his idea.
I was ajuicer.
You know, using steroids?
Diabonal and
Wisterol.
Oh, they use that on racehorses,
for Christ sakes.
And now I'm bankrupt.
I'm divorced.
My two grown kids
won't even return my phone calls.
Strangers with this kind of honesty
make me go a big, rubbery one.
Go ahead,... Cornelius.
You can cry.
And then... something happened.
I let go.
That's really good.
Lost in oblivion.
Dark and silent and complete.
I foundfreedom.
Losing all hope was freedom.
It's OK.
Babies don't sleep this well.
I became addicted.
If I didn't say anything
people always assumed the worst.
They cried harder... then I cried harder.
Now we're going to open the green door,
the heart chakra...
I wasn't really dying.
I wasn't host to cancer or parasites.
I was the warm little centre
that the life of this world crowded around.
Imagine your pain
as a white ball of healing light.
It moves over your body, healing you.
Now keep this going. Remember to breathe
and step forward
through the back door of the room.
Where does it lead?
To your cave.
Step forward
into your cave.
That's right.
You're going deeper into your cave.
And you're going to find
your power animal.
Slide.
Every evening I died.
And every evening I was born again.
Resurrected.
Bob loved me because he thought
my testicles were removed too.
Being there, pressed against his tits,
ready to cry.
This was my vacation.
And she
ruined everything.
This is cancer, right?
This chick, Marla Singer,
did not have testicular cancer.
She was a liar.
She had no diseases at all.
I had seen her at Free And Clear,
my blood parasites group, Thursdays.
Then at Hope,
my bimonthly sickle-cell circle.
And again, at Seize The Day,
my tuberculosis, Friday night.
Marla,
the big tourist.
Her lie reflected my lie.
And suddenly, I felt nothing.
I couldn't cry. So once again,
I couldn't sleep.
Next group, after guided meditation,
after we open our heart chakras,
when it's time to hug,
I'm gonna grab that bitch,
Marla Singer, and scream.
Marla, you liar!
You big tourist, I need this! Now, get out!
I hadn't slept in four days.
We'll just let that dry...
When you have insomnia,
you're never really a sleep.
And you're never really awake.
To begin tonight's communion,
Chloe would like to say a few words.
Oh, yeah. Chloe.
Chloe looked the way Meryl Streep's skeleton
would look if you made it walk around
being extra nice to everybody.
well, I'm still here.
But I don't know for how long.
That's as much certainty
as anyone can give me.
But I've got some good news.
I no longer have any fear of death.
But... I am in a pretty lonely place.
No-one will have sex with me.
I'm so close to the end,
and all I want is to get laid for the last time.
I have pornographic movies
in my apartment,
- and lubricants and amyl nitrite.
- Thank you, Chloe.
Everyone, let's thank Chloe.
Thank you, Chloe.
Now, let's ready our selves
for guided meditation.
You're standing at the entrance of your cave.
You step inside your cave and you walk...
If I did have a tumour, I'd name it Marla.
Marla.
The scratch on the roof of your mouth
that would healif you could stop tonguing it.
But you can't.
..deeper into your cave as you walk.
You feel a healing energy all around you.
Now find your power animal.
Slide.
OK. Let's partner up.
Pick someone special to you tonight.
Hey.
- We need to talk.
- Sure.
- I'm onto you.
- What?
Yeah. You're a faker. You're not dying.
Sorry?
In the Tibetan-philosophy, Sylvia-Plath
sense of the word, I know we're all dying.
- But you're not dying the way Chloe is.
- So?
So you're a tourist.
I've seen you. I saw you at melanoma,
I saw you at tuberculosis.
I saw you at testicular cancer!
I saw you practising this.
- Practising what?
- Telling me off.
Is it going as well as you hoped,... Rupert?
I'll expose you.
Go ahead. I'll expose you.
Come together. Let yourselves cry.
Oh, God. Why are you doing this?
It's cheaper than a movie
and there's free coffee.
Look, this is important.
These are my groups.
I've been coming for over a year.
- Why do you do it?
- I don't know.
When people think you're dying,
they listen to you instead of...
Instead of waiting for their turn to speak.
Yeah. Yeah.
Share yourself... completely.
Look, you don't want to get into this.
- It becomes an addiction.
- Really?
I'm not kidding. I can't cry
if another faker is present, and I need this.
You gotta find somewhere else to go.
Candy stripe a cancer ward.
It's not my problem.
No, wait a second. Hold on.
We'll split up the week, OK?
You take lymphoma and tuberculosis.
You take tuberculosis.
My smoking doesn't go over at all.
OK. Good. Fine.
Testicular cancer should be no contest.
Technically, I have more right to be there.
You still have your balls.
- You're kidding.
- I dunno. Am I?
No. No.
- What do you want?
- I'll take the parasites.
You can't have both.
Take the blood parasites.
- I want brain parasites.
- I'll take the blood but I want brain dementia.
- I want that.
- You can't have the whole brain.
So far, you have four. I only have two.
OK. Take both the parasites. They're yours.
Now we both have three...
Hey! You left half your clothes.
- What, are you selling those?
- Yes!
I'm selling some clothes!
So! We each have three. That's six.
What about the seventh day?
I want bowel cancer.
The girl had done her homework.
No. No. I want bowel cancer.
That's your favourite too?
- Tried to slip it by me, eh?
- Look, we'll split it.
Take the first and third Sunday.
Deal.
Looks like this is good bye.
Let's not make a big thing out of it.
How's this for not making a big thing?
Hey, MarIa!
MarIa!
Maybe we should exchange numbers.
Should we?
- We might wanna switch nights.
- OK.
This is how I met Marla Singer.
Marla's philosophy of life
was that she might die at any moment.
The tragedy, she said, was that she didn't.
It doesn't have your name!
Who are you? Cornelius? Rupert?
Travis? Any of the stupid names
you give each night?
You wake up at Sea Tac.
SFO. LAX.
You wake up at O'Hare.
Dallas Fort Worth.
BWI.
Pacifiic. Mountain. Central.
Lose an hour. Gain an hour.
The check-in for that flight
isn't for another two hours, sir.
This is your life,
and it's ending one minute at a time.
You wake up at Air Harbor International.
If you wake up at a different time,
in a different place,
could you wake up as a different person?
Everywhere I travel,
tiny life.
Single-serving sugar and cream.
Single pat of butter.
The microwave cordon bleu hobby kit.
Shampoo-conditioner combos.
Sample-package mouthwash.
Tiny bars of soap.
The people I meet on each flight,
they're single-serving friends.
Between take off and landing,
we have our time together.
That's all we get.
Welcome!
On a long enough time line,
the survivalrate for everyone drops to zero.
I was a recall coordinator.
My job was to apply the formula.
The infant went through the wind shield.
A new carbuilt by my company
leaves somewhere travelling at 60mph.
The rear differential locks up.
The teenager's braces
are stuck to the ash tray.
Might make a good anti-smoking ad.
The car crashes and burns
with everyone trapped inside.
Now, should we initiate a recall?
The father must have been huge.
See where the fat burned to the seat?
The polyester shirt?
Very modern art.
Take the number of vehicles in the field, A.
Multiply it by the probable rate of failure, B.
Multiply the result by
the average out-of-courtsettlement, C.
A xB x C
equaIs X.
If X is less than the cost of a recall,
we don't do one.
Are there a lot of these kinds of accidents?
You wouldn't believe.
Which car company do you work for?
A major one.
Every time the plane banked too sharply
on take off or landing,
I prayed for a crash or a midair collision.
Anything.
Life insurance pays offtriple
if you die on a business trip.
''If you are seated in an emergency exit row
and would be unable or unwilling
to perform the duties
listed on the safety card, please
ask a flight attendant to reseat you.''
It's a lot of responsibility.
Wanna switch seats?
No. I'm not sure
I'm the man for that particularjob.
An exit-door procedure at 30,000ft.
The illusion of safety.
Yeah. I guess so.
You know why
they put oxygen masks on planes?
- So you can breathe.
- Oxygen gets you high.
In a catastrophic emergency,
you take giant panic breaths.
Suddenly you become euphoric, docile.
You accept your fate.
It's all right here.
Emergency water landing, 600mph.
Blank faces. Calm as Hindu cows.
That's...
That's an interesting theory.
- What do you do?
- What do you mean?
What do you do for a living?
Why? So you can pretend you're interested?
OK.
You have
a kind of sick desperation in your laugh.
We have the exact same briefcase.
Soap.
- Sorry?
- I make and I sell soap.
The yard stick of civilisation.
And this is how I met...
Tyler Durden.
Did you know if you mix gasoline and
frozen orange juice, you can make napalm?
- No, I did not. Is that true?
- That's right.
One can make all kinds of explosives
with simple household items.
- Really?
- If one was so inclined.
Tyler, you are by far the most interesting
single-serving friend I have ever met.
- Everything on a plane is single-serving...
- Oh, I get it. Very clever.
Thank you.
How's it working out for you?
- What?
- Being cIever?
Great.
Keep it up, then. Right up.
A question of etiquette.
As I pass, do I give you the ass or the crotch?
How I came to live with Tyler is...
Airlines have this policy
about vibrating luggage.
- Was it ticking?
- Throwers know modern bombs don't tick.
- Sorry, throwers?
- Baggage handlers.
But when a suitcase vibrates,
the throwers have got to call the police.
- My suitcase was vibrating?
- Nine times out often
it's an electric razor.
But... every once in a while
it's a dildo.
It's company policy never to imply
ownership in the event of a dildo.
We have to use the indefinite article,
a dildo, never
your dildo.
I don't own...
I had everything in that suitcase.
My CK shirts.
My DKNY shoes. My AX ties.
Never mind.
Hey! That's my car!
Home was a condo on the 15th floor
of a filing cabinet
for widows and professionals.
The walls were solid concrete.
A foot of concrete is important
when your next-door neighbour
has to watch game shows at full volume.
Or when a blast of debris
that used to be your personal effects
blows out of your windows
and sails flaming into the night.
I suppose these things happen.
There's... nothing up there.
You can't go into the unit. Police orders.
Do you have somebody you can call?
How embarrassing.
A houseful of condiments and no food.
The police later told me
the pilot light might have gone out
letting out just a little bit of gas.
That gas could have filled the condo.
1700 square feet with high ceilings
for days and days.
Then the refrigerator's compressor
could have clicked on.
Yeah?
I can hearyou breathing...
If you ask me now,
I couldn't tell you why I called him.
- Hello?
- Who's this?
- Tyler?
- Who is this?
We met... We met on the airplane.
We had the same suitcase?
The clever guy?
Oh, yeah. Right.
I called a second ago. There was no answer.
- I'm at a payphone.
- Yeah, I *69'dyou. I never pick up my phone.
So what's up?
well.
You're not gonna believe this.
You know, it could be worse.
A woman could cut off your penis
while you sleep and toss it out of a car.
There's always that. I don't know.
When you buy furniture,
you tell yourseIf, that's it.
That's the last sofa I'll need.
Whatever happens,
that sofa problem is handled.
I had it all.
I had a stereo that was very decent.
A wardrobe that was getting very respectable.
I was close to being complete.
- Shit, man. Now it's all gone.
- all gone.
all gone.
Do you know what a duvet is?
- A comforter.
- It's a blanket.
Just a blanket. Why do guys
like you and I know what a duvet is?
Is this essential to our survival
in the hunter-gatherer sense?
No.
What are we, then?
I dunno. Consumers.
Right. We're consumers.
We are by-products of a lifestyle obsession.
Murder, crime, poverty.
These things don't concern me.
What concerns me are celebrity magazines,
television with 500 channels,
some guy's name on my underwear. Rogaine.
Viagra. Olestra.
- Martha Stewart.
- Fuck Martha Stewart.
She's polishing the brass on the Titanic.
It's all going down.
So fuck off with your sofa units
and Strinne green stripe patterns.
I say never be complete.
I say stop being perfect.
I say let's evolve.
Let the chips fall where they may.
But that's me, and I couId be wrong.
Maybe it's a terrible tragedy.
It's just stuff. Not a tragedy...
You did lose a lot of versatile solutions
for modern living.
Fuck, you're right. I don't smoke.
My insurance is probably gonna cover it, so...
What?
The things you own end up owning you.
Do what you like, man.
Oh, it's late.
- Hey, thanks for the beer.
- Yeah, man.
I shouId find a hotel.
What?
- A hotel?
- Yeah.
- Just ask, man.
- What are you talking about?
Oh, God. Three pitchers of beer
and you still can't ask.
What?
You called me
because you needed a place to stay.
- Oh, hey. No, no, no.
- Yes, you did. So just ask.
Cut the foreplay and just ask, man.
would... would that be a problem?
Is it a problem for you to ask?
- Can I stay at your place?
- Yeah.
Thanks.
- I want you to do me a favour.
- Yeah, sure.
I want you to hit me as hard as you can.
What?
Let me tell you a little bit about Tyler Durden.
Tyler was a nightperson.
While the rest of us slept, he worked.
He had one part-time job as a projectionist.
A movie doesn't come all on one big reel.
It comes on a few.
Someone has to switch the projectors
at the exact moment
that one reel ends and the next one begins.
You can see little dots come into
the upper right corner ofthe screen.
In the industry, we call them cigarette burns.
That's the cue for a changeover.
He fIips the projectors, movie keeps
going and the audience has no idea.
Why would anyone want this shit job?
Because it affords him
interesting opportunities.
Like splicing a frame of pornography
into family films.
So when the snooty cat and the courageous
dog with the ceIebrity voices first meet,
that's when you'll catch a flash
of Tyler's contribution to the film.
Nobody knows that they saw it but they did.
Nice, big cock.
Even a humming bird
couldn't catch Tyler at work.
Tyler also works sometimes as a banquet
waiter at the luxurious Pressman hotel.
He was the guerrilla terrorist
of the food service industry.
Do not watch. I cannot go when you watch.
Apart from seasoning the lobster bisque,
he farted on meringues,
and as for the cream of mushroom soup...
Go ahead, tell'em.
You get the idea.
- You just want me to hit you?
- Come on. Do me this one favour.
- Why?
- I don't know. Never been in a fight. You?
- No. But that's a good thing.
- You can't know yourseIf if you haven't!
I don't wanna die without any scars.
- Come on. Hit me, before I lose my nerve.
- Oh, God. This is crazy.
So go crazy! Let it rip.
- I don't know about this.
- I don't either.
Who gives a shit? No-one's watching.
What do you care?
This is crazy. You want me to hit you?!
That's right.
- Where? Like, in the face?
- Surprise me.
This is so fucking stupid.
Motherfucker!
He hit me in the ear!
- well, Jesus, I'm sorry.
- Ow, Christ!
- Why the ear, man?
- I fucked it up.
No, that was perfect.
No, it's all right.
It really hurts.
Right.
Hit me again.
No, you hit me. Come on!
We should do this again sometime.
- Where's your car?
- What car?
I don't know how Tyler found that house
but he said he'd been there for a year.
It looked like it was waiting to be torn down.
Most of the windows were boarded up.
There was no lock on the front door from
when the police, or who ever, kicked it in.
The stairs were ready to collapse.
I didn't know if he owned it or was squatting.
Neither would have surprised me.
Yep. That's you.
That's me. That's the toilet. Good?
Yeah, thanks.
What a shit hole.
Nothing worked.
Turning on one lightmeant
another lightin the house went out.
There were no neighbours.
Just warehouses and a papermill.
That fartsmell of steam.
The hamster-cage smell ofwood chips.
What have we here?
- Hey, guys.
- Hey.
Every time it rained, we had to kill the power.
By the end of the first month,
I didn't miss TV.
I didn't even mind the warm, stale refrigerator.
Can I be next?
all right, man.
Lose the tie.
At night, Tyler and I were alone
for halfa mile in every direction.
Rain trickled down through
the plasterand the lightfiixtures.
Everything wooden swelledandshrank.
Everywhere were rustednails
to snagyour elbow on.
The previous occupant hadbeen a shut-in.
Hey, man. What are you reading?
Listen to this. It's an article written
by an organ in the first person.
''I am Jack's medulla oblongata.
Without me,
Jack could not regulate
his heart rate or breathing.''
There's a whoIe series of these.
''I Am Jill's NippIes.''
- ''I Am Jack's Colon.''
- ''I Get Cancer. I Kill Jack.''
After fiighting, everything else
in life got the volume turned down.
What?
- You could deal with anything.
- Have you finished those reports?
If you could choose,
who would you fight?
I'd fight my boss, probably.
Really?
- Yeah, why? Who would you fight?
- I'd fight my dad.
I don't know my dad.
I mean, I know him, but...
He left when I was like, six years oId.
Married this other woman
and had some other kids.
He did this every six years.
- He changes city and starts a new family.
- Fucker's setting up franchises!
My dad never went to college.
- So it was real important that I go.
- That sounds familiar.
So I graduate. Call him up long-distance
and say, ''Dad, now what?''
- He says, ''Get ajob.''
- Same here.
Now I'm 25. Make my yearly call again.
''Dad, now what?''
He says, ''I dunno. Get married.''
You can't get married.
I'm a 30-year-old boy.
We're a generation of men raised by women.
I'm wondering if another woman
is really the answer we need.
Most ofthe week, we were Ozzie and Harriet.
But every Saturday night,
we were finding something out.
We were finding out more and more
that we were not alone.
It used to be that when I came home angry
or depressed, I'd just clean my condo.
Polish my Scandinavian furniture.
I should have been looking for a new condo
or haggling with my insurance company.
I should have been upset
about my nice flaming little shit.
But I wasn't.
The premise of cybernetting an office
is make things more efficient.
Monday mornings,
I just thought about next week.
Can I get the icon in corn flower blue?
Absolutely.
Efficiency is priority No.1, people.
Because waste is a thief.
I showed this to my man here.
You liked it, didn't you?
You can swallowa pint of blood
before you getsick.
It was rightin everyone's face.
Tyler and I just made it visible.
It was on the tip of everyone's tongue.
Tyler and I just gave it a name.
Come on, you've gotta go home!
Turn off the jukebox. Lock the back.
Every week,
Tyler gave the rules that he and I decided.
Gentlemen!
Welcome to Fight Club.
The first rule of Fight Club is
you do not talk about Fight Club.
The second rule of Fight Club is
you do not talk about Fight Club!
Third rule of Fight Club.
Someone yells stop, goes limp, taps out,
the fight is over. Fourth rule.
OnIy two guys to a fight.
Fifth rule.
One fight at a time, fell as.
Sixth rule. No shirts. No shoes.
Seventh rule.
Fights wiII go on as long as they have to.
And the eighth and final rule.
If this is your first night at Fight Club
you have to fight.
This kid from work, Ricky,
couldn't remember whether
you orderedpens with blue ink or black.
But Ricky was a god for ten minutes
when he trounced
the maitre d' of a local food court.
Sometimes, all you could hear were
the flat, hard, packing sounds over the yelling.
Or the wet choke
when someone gas pedand sprayed...
Stop!
You weren't alive anywhere
like you were there.
But Fight Club only exists in the hours
between when Fight Club starts and ends.
Even if I could tell someone
they had a good fight,
I wouldn't be talking to the same man.
Who you were in Fight Club
is not who you were outside of it.
A guy came to Fight Club for the first time.
His ass was a wad of cookie dough.
After a few weeks, he was carved out of wood.
If you could fight any celebrity,
who would you fight?
- allve or dead?
- Doesn't matter. Who'd be tough?
Hemingway. You?
Shatner. I'd fight William Shatner.
We all started seeing things differently.
Everywhere we went,
we were sizing things up.
I felt sorry for guys packed into gyms,
trying to look like how Calvin Klein
or Tommy Hilfiiger said they should.
Is that what a man looks like?
Oh, self-improvement is masturbation.
Now, self-destruction...
Excuse me.
Fight Club wasn'tabout winning or losing.
It wasn't about words.
The hysterical shouting was in tongues
like at a Pentecostal Church.
- Is that it?
- Stop!
When the fight was over, nothing was solved.
But nothing mattered.
Cool.
After wards, we all felt saved.
Hey, man. How about next week?
How about next month?!
Everybody here in the middle.
New guy, you too.
Sometimes, Tyler spoke for me.
He fell down some stairs.
I fell down some stairs.
Fight Club became the reason to cut
your hairshort or trim your fingernails.
OK. Any historical figure.
I'd fight Gandhi.
Good answer.
- How about you?
- Lincoln.
Lincoln?
Big guy, big reach.
Skinny guys fight till they're burger.
Fuck!
Hey, even the Mona Lisa's falling apart.
Hello?
Where have you been the last eight weeks?
Marla?
- How did you find me?
- You left a forwarding number.
I haven't seen you at any support groups.
We split'em up.
That was the idea. Remember?
Yeah, but you haven't been going to yours.
- How do you know?
- I cheated.
I found a new one.
- Really?
- It's for men only.
Like the testicle thing?
Look, this is a bad time.
I've been going to Debtors Anonymous.
- They're really fucked-up people...
- I'm on my way out.
Me too. I've got a stomach full of Xanax.
I took what was left of a bottle.
It might have been too much.
Picture Marla Singer throw herself
around her crummy apartment.
This isn't a for-real suicide thing.
This is probably a cry-for-help thing.
So you're staying in tonight, then?
Do you wanna wait
and hear me describe death?
Do you wanna listen
and see if my spirit can use a phone?
Have you ever hearda death rattle before?
Tyler's door was closed. l'd been here for
two months and his door was never closed.
You won't believe this dream
I had last night.
I can hardly believe anything about last night.
What are you doing here?
What?
This is my house.
What are you doing here?
Fuck you!
Oh, you've got some fucked-up friends!
Limber, though.
Silly cooze.
I come in last night. Phone's off the hook.
Guess who's on the other end?
I knew the story before he told me.
Have you everheard a death rattle before?
Do you think it'll live up to its name?
Or will it just be a death hairball?
Prepare to evacuate soul.
Ten,
nine,... eight...
How could Tyler, of all people,
think it was a bad thing
that Marla Singer was about to die?
Five,
four...
Hang on.
You got here fast.
Did I call you?
The mattress is all sealed in slippery plastic.
Oh, don't worry. It's not a threat to you.
Oh, fuck!
Somebody called the cops.
- Hey, where's 513?
- End of the hall.
The girl who lives there
used to be a charming, lovely girl.
She has lost faith in herself.
- Miss Singer, let us heIp you!
- She's a monster!
- You have every reason to live.
- She's infectious human waste!
- Miss Singer!
- Good luck trying to save her!
If I fall a sleep,
I'm done for.
You're gonna have to keep me up
all night.
Un-fucking-believable.
He was obviously able to handle it.
- You know what I mean, you fucked her.
- No, I didn't.
- Never?
- No.
You're not into her, are you?
No! God, not at all.
I am Jack's raging bile duct.
Are you sure? You can tell me.
Believe me, I'm sure.
- Puta gun to my head and spray my brains.
- That's good.
She's a predator posing as a house pet.
Stay away.
The shit that came out of
this woman's mouth, I had never heard!
My God.
I haven't been fucked like that
since grade school.
How could Tyler not go for that?
The other night,
he was splicing sex organs into Cinderella.
Marla doesn't need a lover,
just a caseworker.
Or a wash.
This isn't love, it's sport fucking.
She invaded my support groups
and now my home.
Hey, hey. Sit down.
Now, listen.
I can't have you talking to her about me.
Why would I...
Say anything about me or what goes on
in this house to her or anybody,... we're done.
- Now promise me. You promise?
- OK.
- Yeah, I promise.
- Promise?
- I just said, I promise! What...
- That's three times you promised.
If only I had wasted a few minutes
and gone to watch Marla Singer die,
none of this would have happened.
Harder, yes! Oh, harder, harder!
I could have moved to another room.
On the third floor
where I might not have heard them.
But I didn't.
- What are you doing?
- Just going to bed.
Wanna finish her off?
- No. No, thank you.
- I've found a cigarette.
- Who were you talking to?
- Shut up.
I became the calm little centre of the world.
I was the Zen master.
I wrote little haiku poems.
I e-mailed them to everyone.
Is that your blood?
Some of it, yeah.
You can't smoke in here.
Take the rest of the day off.
Come back Monday with some clean clothes.
Get yourself together.
I gotrightin everyone's hostile face.
''Yes, these are bruises from fighting.''
''Yes, I'm comfortable with that.''
''I am enlightened.''
You give up the condo life, give up
all your flaming world lypossessions,
move to a dilapidated house
in a toxic waste area,
and you have to come home to this.
- Hello.
- This is Detective Stern with the Arson Unit.
We have some new information about
the incident at your former condo.
Yes.
I don't know if you're aware, but someone
sprayed Freon into your front-door lock.
They useda chisel to shatter the cylinder.
No, I wasn't aware ofthat.
I am Jack's coldsweat.
Does this sound strange to you?
Yes, sir, strange. Very strange.
- The dynamite
- Dynamite?
left a residue
of ammonium oxalate potassium perchloride.
- Do you know what this means?
- No, what does it mean?
It means it was home-made.
I'm sorry. This is just coming
as quite a shock to me, sir.
Whoever set this dynamite could have blown
out your pilot light days before the explosion.
- The gas was justa detonator.
- Who would go and do that?
- I'll ask the questions.
- Tell him.
Tell him the liberator who destroyed
my property reallgned my perceptions.
Excuse me. Are you there?
I am listening.
It's hard to know what to make of this.
Have you recently made enemies who might
have access to home-made dynamite?
- Enemies?
- Reject civilisation,
especially material possessions.
- Son, this is serious.
- Yes, I know it's serious.
- I mean that.
- Yes, it's very serious.
Look, nobody takes this
more seriously than me.
That condo was my life. OK?
I Ioved every stick offurniture in that place.
That was not just a bunch of stuff
that got destroyed.
- It was me!
- l'd like to thank the Academy.
- Is this not a good time for you?
- Just tell him you fucking did it!
Tell him you blew it all up!
That's what he wants to hear.
- Are you still there?
- Wait. Are you saying that I'm a suspect?
No. I may need to taIk to you, so you
let me know if you're gonna leave town.
- OK?
- OK.
Except for their humping,
Tyler and Marla were never in the same room.
My parents pulled this exactsame act
for years.
The condom is the glass slipper
of our generation.
You slip one on when you meet a stranger.
You... dance all night.
Then you throw it away.
The condom, I mean. Not the stranger.
What?
I got this dress at a thrift store for $1.
It was worth every penny.
It's a bridesmaid's dress.
Someone loved it intensely
for one day.
Then tossed it.
Like a Christmas tree.
So special.
Then
bam!
It's on the side ofthe road.
Tinsel still clinging to it.
Like a sex crime victim.
Underwear inside out.
- Bound with electrical tape.
- well then, it suits you.
You can borrow it sometime.
Get rid of her.
- What? You get rid of her!
- Don't mention me.
I am six years old again,
passing messages between parents.
- I really think it's time you left.
- Don't worry, I'm leaving.
- Not that we don't love your visits.
- You are such a nutcase. I can't keep up.
Gotta get off
Thanks. Bye.
Gotta get off of this merry-go-round
Gonna get, need to get...
Gotta get...
You kids!
Why do you still waste time with her?
I'll say this about Marla.
At least she's trying to hit bottom.
And I'm not?
Feathers up your butt
do not make you a chicken.
What are we doing tonight?
Tonight... we make soap.
Really?
To make soap, first we render fat.
The salt balance has to be just right
so the best fat for soap comes from humans.
- Wait, what is this place?
- A liposuction clinic.
Pay dirt!
Richest, creamiest fat in the world.
Fat of the land!
No! Don't pull it, don't pull it!
- Oh, God!
- Give me another one.
As the fat renders,
the tallows float to the surface.
Like in Boy Scouts.
- It's hard to imagine you as a Boy Scout.
- Keep stirring.
Once the tallow hardens,
you skim off a layer of glycerin.
Add nitric acid, you've got nitroglycerin.
Then add sodium nitrate and sawdust,
you've got dynamite.
Yeah, with enough soap,
one couId bIow up just about anything.
Tyler was full of use fulinformation.
People found clothes got cleaner
when washed at a certain point in the river.
- You know why?
- No.
Human sacrifices were once made
on the hills above this river.
Bodies burnt.
Water permeated the ashes to create lye.
This is lye. The crucial ingredient.
Once it mixed with the meIted body fat,
a white soapy discharge crept into the river.
May I see your hand, please?
What is this?
This is a chemical burn.
It wiII hurt more than any burn
and it will leave a scar.
Meditation worked for cancer,
it could work now.
- Don't shut the pain out.
- Oh, God!
The first soap was made from heroes' ashes,
like the first monkey shot into space.
Without pain or sacrifice,
we would have nothing.
I triednot to think
of the wordsearing offlesh.
Stop it!
This is your pain, this is your burning hand.
I'm going to my cave
to find my power animal.
No! Don't deal with this
the way those dead people do! Come on!
- I get the point!
- No! You're feeling premature enlightenment.
It's the greatest moment of your life,
and you're off somewhere else!
I am not!
Shut up!
Our fathers were our mode Is for God.
If our fathers balled,
what does that tell you about God?
Listen to me. You have to consider
the possibility that God does not like you.
He never wanted you.
In all probability, He hates you.
This is not the worst thing that can happen.
We don't need Him!
- I agree!
- Fuck damnation, fuck redemption.
We are God's unwanted children? So be it!
- I'm getting water!
- You can use water and make it worse or...
- Or use vinegar to neutrallse the burn.
- Please let me up!
First, you have to give up.
First, you have to know, not fear,
know that some day, you're gonna die.
You don't know how this feels!
It's only after we've lost everything
that we're free to do anything.
OK.
Congratulations.
You're one step closer to hitting the bottom.
Tyler sold his soap
to department stores at $20 a bar.
God knows what they charged.
- This is the best soap.
- Why, thank you, Susan.
It was beautiful.
We were selling rich women
their own fatasses back to them.
He was wearing his yellow tie.
I didn't weara tie to work anymore.
''The first rule of Fight Club
is don't talk about Fight Club.''
I'm haIf-a sleep again.
I must have left it in the copymachine.
''The second rule...'' Is this yours?
Pretend you're me.
Make a managerial decision.
You find this. What would you do?
well, I gotta tell you,
I'd be very, very careful
who you talk to about that.
Because the person who wrote that
is dangerous.
And this button-down, Oxford-cloth psycho
might just snap
and then stalk from office to office
with an Armallte AR10 carbine gas-powered
semiautomatic weapon,
pumping round after round
into colleagues and co-workers.
This might be someone
you've known for years.
Someone very, very close to you.
Tyler's words coming out of my mouth.
And I used to be such a nice guy.
Or maybe you shouldn't bring me
every piece of trash you pick up.
- Compliance and Liability.
- My tit's gonna rot off.
WiII you excuse me? I need to take this.
- What do you mean?
- I need you to check for a lump in my breast.
- Go to a hospital.
- I can't afford to waste money on a doctor.
I don't know about this, Marla.
PIease.
She didn't call Tyler. I'm neutral in herbook.
That's nice.
Taking food to Mrs Haniver and Mrs Raines.
Where are they, exactly?
Tragically, they're dead.
I'm alive and I'm in poverty. Want any?
- No, no.
- I got one for you.
Thanks for the thought.
What happened to your hand?
Oh, nothing.
Right there?
- Feel anything?
- No.
well, make sure.
OK, I'm pretty sure.
You feel nothing?
No, nothing.
well, that's a relief. Thank you.
- No problem.
- I wish I could return the favour.
Breast cancer doesn't run in my family.
- I couId check your prostate.
- I think I'm OK.
well, thanks, anyway.
- Are we done?
- Yeah, we're done.
See you... around.
Cornelius?
Cornelius!
It's me! Bob!
Hey, Bob.
- We all thought you were dead.
- No, no. Still here.
- How are you, Bob?
- Better than I've ever been in my whole life.
- Really? Still remaining men together?
- No, no.
- I got something so much better now.
- Really, what is it?
well...
The first rule is,
I'm not supposed to talk about it.
And the second rule is
- And the third rule is...
- Bob, Bob. I'm a member.
Look at my face, Bob.
That's fucking... fucking great.
- I've never seen you there.
- I go Tuesdays and Thursdays.
- I go Saturday.
- Congratulations.
Yeah, hey, to both of us, right?
Have you heard about the guy
that invented it?
- Yeah, actually...
- I hear all kinds ofthings.
Supposedly,
he was born in a mental institution
and he sleeps only one hour a night.
He's a great man.
Do you know about Tyler Durden?
I didn't hurt you, did I?
Actually, you did.
Thank you for this.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Fight Club.
This was mine and Tyler's gift.
Our gift to the world.
I Iook around, I Iook around,
I see a Iot of new faces.
Shut up!
Which means a lot of people have been
breaking the first two rules of Fight Club.
I see in Fight Club the strongest
and smartest men who've ever lived.
I see all this potential.
And I see it squandered.
Goddamn it,
an entire generation pumping gas.
Waiting tables.
Slaves with white collars.
Advertising has us chasing cars and clothes.
Working jobs we hate
so we can buy shit we don't need.
We're the middIe children of history.
No purpose or place.
We have no Great War.
No Great Depression.
Our great war is a spiritual war.
Our great depression is our lives.
We've all been raised
on television to believe
that one day we'd be millionaires
and movie gods and rock stars.
But we won't.
We're slowly learning that fact.
And we're very, very pissed off.
Yeah!
- First rule of Fight Club is, do not talk...
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org