Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Ten minutes late.
You see anything?
There's a guy walking around inside.
It's one of his body guards.
Do you think
Kozlenko changed his mind?
No way.
With the amount of money
being waved in front of him,
trust me, he's comin' with us.
Get rid
of them.
He just gave the signal.
Copy that?
Didn't you hear me?
He gave the signal.
Yeah, yeah.
Thanks for the warning Jared.
Go get him.
Jesus.
Get outta there.
C'mon.
Let's go.
Marta.
There we go.
I got her, man. Go, go, go.
Get in. Drive. Go.
Jared, c'mon, get in.
Son of a bitch.
Who tipped them off? Let's go.
Let's go.
Go, go, go. Drive.
There he is.
Yale.
Sorry, I'm late.
They closed Ku'damn Strasse
to traffic.
Can you believe this?
How'd they find out he was defecting?
I don't know.
How is she?
How do you think?
Hm.
Is it confirmed that Kozlenko is dead?
And his body guard.
So what now?
Do you hear that noise out there?
That is the sound of a chapter
of history closing.
I do believe
we have just won the Cold War.
There's an entire city out
there tearing the wall down.
Gorbachev and the Ruskies
are now our new best friends.
Washington does
not want the boat rocked.
So what are you saying?
We're no longer relevant?
No, no, no.
There'll always be an enemy.
NIA thinks it's going to be the,
the Middle East. Oil.
Middle East?
Whoa. Wait, wait.
When you recruited me
you promised Paris, right?
Berlin, London. So now,
now what are you saying, Rihad?
You better drink up
while you still can, partner.
Saudi Arabia is a dry country.
Yeah,
maybe it's time for a career change.
Mr. Gorbachev, tear down this wall.
We're not walking away
until our mission is done,
until the invader is out of Kuwait.
I, William Jefferson Clinton,
do solemnly swear
that I will faithfully execute
the office of President
of the United States.
And will to the best of my ability,
preserve, protect and defend
the constitution of the United States.
So help me God.
The President of the United States.
Our war on terror begins with
Al Qaeda, but it does not end there.
The coalition authority is intent on
moving forward as quickly as we can.
I love it.
Ah, good guys, keep it up.
Nice.
Two couples, uh,
let's get the feet uh,
right, yes, no, that's perfect.
Perfect.
Oh, very sexy guys.
Beautiful.
Let's switch it up,
switch it back up.
Good.
That's perfect.
Alright guys, together. Yes.
Great, great.
Beautiful. Beautiful.
Alright, really sexy now.
Let's feel the love.
Nice.
Why can't I meet a man like that?
Very hot, guys.
Yes.
Nice.
(speaks foreign language)
Yeah, goin' for a look.
Ciao.
Oh.
Oh, oh.
There's that little girl
that I love so much.
Hello, hello, hello.
Got everything you need?
- Right here.
- Alright,
let's drop by the apartment
and then we'll go wherever you want.
The pet shop?
Uh, well...
A puppy, please.
Uh, no, no, no.
Your mother would kill me.
You said anywhere.
Oh, how 'bout a movie.
I getta choose it?
Yes, whatever you want,
I'm yours for the weekend.
Yeah.
Do you want some gelato?
Mama never lets me
have any before dinner.
Well, I don't see her around here,
do you?
She'll get mad.
Only if she finds out.
Alright, now, here take this,
go over there, buy some gelato.
I'm not gonna tell your mom. Go.
Oh that's a lot more than we thought,
huh?
Yeah.
Alright eggo, put your uh,
backpack up in the room,
- we'll head off to the theater.
- Okay.
(speaks in Italian)
Papa, why do you take pictures
of people in their underpants?
- Jacob.
- What's that, sweetie?
Why don't you take pictures
like these anymore?
Oh well, you know uh,
Daddy, I guess uh, got a little
tired tryin' to save the world
and decided to
make some money instead.
(speaks in Italian)
Jacob, it's Marta,
l- I know its been a long time,
but I have to see you.
I'm coming to Milan by train from
Zurich, arriving at five-oh-nine.
Regardless
of what happened in the past,
you have to meet me.
I'll explain then.
Please be there.
Who was that?
There's someone at the door.
I will get rid of whoever it is.
Hey.
Hi, mama.
What are you doing here?
Are you okay, baby?
Oh no, she's fine, she's fine.
I just need you to watch her
for a couple hours.
I can't believe this.
Your timing is terrible.
I tried to call but your cell was off.
You said you weren't goin' anywhere.
I have plans.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Uh, something came up.
What?
I wouldn't do this if I had a choice.
And it won't take long.
Promise?
I swear.
And we'll still make the movie.
Okay.
You owe me.
Big time.
Come on, baby.
How was school today?
She's on the way out.
Marta, Marta.
Okay, you can
explain what's going on later.
Let's get outta here.
Let go.
What kind of trouble are you in?
Do I know you?
Is this a joke?
Yes, you know me.
Y- you told me to meet you here.
Hey.
Why?
Look, just get in.
Prove you know me.
How the hell am I supposed to do that,
huh?
Uh, you got a fuckin' star tattoo
on your left hip.
(speaks in Italian)
Are you satisfied?
C'mon. C'mon, hurry.
(speaks in Italian)
So, what fuckin' happened man?
Just don't lose them.
Who the hell are you?
I'm Jacob.
Wait,
you- you don't remember calling me?
No.
You left me a message telling me
you were in trouble.
I don't even know why I'm here.
Hey, well that guy sure seemed
to know you were coming.
What do you think he wanted with me?
Oh my Jesus,
how the hell am I supposed to know?
I haven't seen you in years.
(speaks in Italian)
Why can't I remember?
I really wish I knew.
What's my name?
It's Marta.
Did you get hit in the head?
Have an accident or something?
I don't know.
Well you must have ID on you
or something with your name on it.
Look you were on a train,
got your passport?
All I have is this.
A key.
To what?
I don't know.
'Kay, let's uh, let's get inside.
How do we know each other?
We were operatives for the NIA.
NATO intelligence.
You went to Georgetown in Washington
DC where you were recruited.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
You were born in Russia,
small town north of Moscow.
Left with your mother
when you were still a child.
Why would I call you?
Sounds like you
got yourself into some trouble.
I'm gonna try and track down Yale
Erickson, who was our section chief.
Maybe he knows what's going on
and can help you.
Do you still work for them?
No, not for a long time.
Do I?
I have no idea.
I need to uh, where's...
Yeah, it's uh, upstairs.
The one on the left.
I haven't heard that ring before.
It's a call coming in
on an old analog line.
Can you access it?
I think so.
Caller, please identify yourself.
This is Nighthawk.
Five-four-six-L-W-A.
Route me through to T-Rex.
Please hold.
Nighthawk's calling us.
Can you get me a location
and can you contact the director?
Nighthawk,
T-Rex is listed as an inactive file,
can you please state
your identifier again.
Yeah, Nighthawk.
Five-four-six-L-W-A.
You're also listed as inactive.
Please stand by.
Shit.
(unintelligible)
What?
Here.
C'mon, c'mon.
C'mon.
Nighthawk.
Hello?
Did you get a location on him?
Come in.
If that damned idiot didn't
fail in the first place,
we gotta clean house for another week.
Now we got those bastards firing
missiles, back & forth at each other,
like a pack of 9 year olds
in a summer camp.
Marcus,
I'm gonna have to call you back.
I'm going to see you on the 15th,
so you give my love to Catherine.
What the hell is this?
Communications received a call,
on an old analogue number
routed out of Milan.
546LWA
We haven't used indicative numbers
like that, since the 90's.
It's an inactive file, the caller
identified himself as Nighthawk.
We crosschecked the name, but it's
under a restricted access code.
I know who it is.
Jacob Keene, he's before your time.
Who's the point person in this?
His name is Henry, Aginon Henry.
He's an agent
in the Communications Department.
You transferred him
from the South American Office.
Right, right, right,
we recruited him out of Ml5.
That ambitious guy.
This is agent Henry.
Put me through to Nighthawk.
I'm afraid that's impossible, sir.
Why?
He hung up.
Call him back.
We've been trying,
but there's no answer.
What's his location?
He's still in Milan,
you want him apprehended, Sir?
Agent Henry, you're in communications,
not operations, is that correct?
Yes, sir, I know, I'm just...
I'm sending agent Davis down there.
She answers only to me, understood?
Yes, sir, understood.
What's the story on Keene.
It's complicated.
He was one of our best.
Was?
He's retired.
So why is a retired agent
calling in on a telephone line?
That's what I'd like to know.
I want you to go down there,
and I want you to track him.
I want to know where he goes,
what he does, who he sees.
But I don't want him stopped,
understood?
Completely.
And Davis...
This is on a need to know basis.
I don't want
the NIA turned upside down,
Just because of some ex-agent
on a cell phone, understood?
Hello, Jacob.
About time you showed up.
Okay, why are they after me?
What's the last thing you remember?
Whatta you mean?
Do you remember getting on the train?
No, just getting off.
How did they find us?
What?
If it's the agency,
they could've traced my phone.
So turn it off.
Nope. Got a better idea.
That guy seems to know you.
Smile at him.
I don't think I'm his type.
Wait here.
You know the Metro Club?
Yes.
One hour.
Marta, Marta.
Hey, where you going?
I'm going to the police.
No. No, no.
I didn't do anything.
You don't know that.
I gotta get you to Yale.
We can be tracked if we use credit
cards or ATM's so we need cash.
C'mon.
There's not much here.
Okay, in here.
Jesus.
What are you doing here?
I promised the proofs
to the client by Monday.
Remember?
You shot film.
I have to develop the negatives.
It's okay, Marta.
Who is she?
Old friend.
And where is Julia?
I need to borrow your car.
Where is yours?
Uh, left it at the train station.
I'll explain later.
How much cash do you have?
A little over two hundred euros.
Great, great, great.
Keys?
Let's go.
I can't believe this is happening.
It's been twenty years
since I've had to watch my back.
Where are we going now?
I'm taking you to Yale's chalet.
I'm betting that's where he is.
I'm gonna get you to him
and then I'm outta this.
Pronto.
Who is this?
Raphael.
Where is Jacob?
Let me talk to him.
This is not my phone.
I do not know who Jacob is.
Put him on.
Hello.
Where are they?
This is not my phone.
Of course it isn't.
Who is this?
You uh, you want to have some fun?
Sure.
I'm sure Daddy just got busy.
Decoy.
They could be a hundred kilometers
from here by now.
What're we gonna tell him?
Nothing.
Gone?
What do you mean gone?
We are not sure sir, we tracked
his cell phone as per Davis's orders.
He moved around Milan for several
hours and then the signal vanished.
He turned off his phone.
With all due respect, agent Davis,
even in shut down mode,
cell phone antenna continue
to transfer a microwave signal.
Maybe he realized
you were tracking him,
and he destroyed the goddamned thing.
Why did Keene retire?
He didn't.
He was retired.
Under what circumstances?
Jacob Keene caused this agency
a lot of embarrassment a long time ago.
And the agency
won't let it happen again.
So for all this time,
he makes a phone call,
wants to talk to you,
but then hangs up and does everything
he can to make sure we can't find him?
Why?
Something changed, and it scared him.
Or someone?
Bring me in it.
I already advised
all the border crossings,
all major railways out o f Milan.
Don't tell me the plans, Davis.
Execute it.
Find him, stop him.
I want Jacob Keene.
Oh, um, grazie.
(speaks in Italian)
Where are we?
Uh, we crossed the Swiss border
almost an hour ago.
How well do we know each other?
Did we just work together?
No, we were close.
How close?
What are you asking?
Were we lovers?
Marta...
I keep remembering things,
these moments of you and me.
It's complicated.
No, it's not.
Either we had sex or we didn't.
We did.
It was a long time ago, Marta.
What happened?
Things changed, we moved on.
I wish I knew
if anything you say is true.
(speaks in Italian)
Where's your boss?
Who are you?
Where did he and the woman go?
I don't know.
It's the weekend.
He could be anywhere.
I don't know where he is.
Why don't I believe you?
There's such a thing
as misplaced loyalty, my friend.
I've gotten information out of men
who were trained to ignore pain.
Where are they?
I don't know.
Car key's missing.
Did he take your car?
Kiss my ass.
Alright.
Jesus man,
tell him what he wants to know.
I know how to find him.
Car's got anti-theft tracking device.
It's under control.
Sure, bye.
Pretty boy,
you should be in the movies.
Got anything to say
to your boss before I kill ya?
Jacob.
Hi Jillian, how are you?
How am I?
Surprised, for one thing.
I thought you were
the delivery boy with my pills.
Oh my god.
I can't believe this.
Marta?
Oh, it's been so long.
Let me look at you.
You haven't changed a bit,
except your hair.
When did you change the color?
I don't know.
I need to see your husband.
Work had gotten to Yale.
Nothing was the same
after the wall came down.
The agency put him on medical leave.
This place was always his dream.
We thought being here would help
but um, nightmares continued.
Wake up in a cold sweat.
He was always secretive, but
I had a pretty good idea what he did.
You two and Jared were
the only people he ever brought home
and that was just toward the end.
One morning I woke up and he was gone.
I didn't know where he was for weeks.
And then I got a call
to meet him at St. Albans.
It's a small village
a couple of hours from here.
But he was different, withdrawn.
Said he wasn't coming home.
Told me to have a good life.
He is still alive.
As far as I know.
You never saw him again.
Life's strange, isn't it?
Whoever thought you two would be
together after what happened.
Why St. Albans?
There's a monastery nearby.
Yale went there.
He was cutting himself off
from everything, including me.
We never really talked about it,
but every time he went off
to god knows where,
we both knew he might never come back.
And when he did, he was
always looking over his shoulder.
He became detached, emotionless.
Maybe that's
why they called it the cold war.
In the house, both of you.
Who are you?
Jacob, let him go.
Hans,
from the chemist with my medication.
You're in trouble.
I thought you two were out.
I thought so too.
You were telling me the truth.
We were spies.
Were is the operative word.
I have a new life, one that I love.
Why was Jillian surprised
that we were together?
I don't know.
Your German was better than mine.
The brothers of St. Albans.
No admittance.
Please respect our privacy.
Alright, stay here.
I'm gonna check the place out.
For what?
It's a monastery for god's sake.
We were in the suspicion business.
Could be NIA safe house.
You're paranoid.
Remember don't trust anything.
Or anyone.
What are you doing here?
Yale, it's Jacob.
I know who it is.
Why are you here?
Marta's in some kind of trouble.
Gotta be NIA.
I haven't worked
for the NIA for years.
Who told you I was here?
Jillian. She misses you.
She said to tell you
the roses came up early this year.
The good brothers allow me
to stay here.
In return I do their gardening
and maintenance.
I think I may know
how you came to lose your memory.
Now think back.
Milan,
do you recall anything before Milan?
No.
Nothing at all?
I have flashes.
As if I'm in a dark room and somebody
turns on a light for a second.
Now don't be alarmed,
I just want to look for something.
Good.
What is it? I felt it before.
It's a small red mark.
It was made by an injection gun.
It's the reason
you've lost your memory.
She must have had some information
that they wanted.
If she had information they wanted,
why would they take her memory?
Back in the eighties
the lab boys at Langley came up
with the ultimate truth serum,
Trisodium nitrol,
code name Delphi.
Once injected,
the interrogates
could only tell the truth
about anything for thirty minutes.
But Delphi had a side effect.
The interrogates would start
to lose their memories.
In twenty-four hours they couldn't
even remember their own names.
Permanent irreversible amnesia.
No, I still have memories.
No, that's temporary.
That's just the last
few brain cells expiring.
Soon you will remember nothing.
I'm so sorry.
Delphi?
I've never heard of it.
Well, you didn't need to know.
It all goes back
to that Kozlenko matter.
If you had succeeded in bringing
him out in eighty-nine,
I was going to interrogate him.
What are you saying?
We were gonna drain his memory
and not give a damn
about what happened to him?
Believe me, I did much worse
when I worked for NIA.
Why do you think
I live here in a monastery?
What about the ten million dollars?
Well that was real enough.
The agency covered it's ass
just in case he checked.
Who's Kozlenko?
He was our last assignment.
You, me, a third agent named
Jared Clayton,
were gonna bring in a KGB operative,
Yuri Kozlenko.
First we were instructed to
go to a bank in Zurich,
where the agency had deposited
ten million US dollars
into a numbered account.
Pass code had twelve digits,
each of us was to enter four digits
and not tell the others
what they were.
I was told
that after Kozlenko was debriefed,
we'd give him the pass code
and he'd use the money
to start a new life in the west.
But it was a lie.
What about the money?
Well I suppose it was forgotten about.
When I left the agency it was uh,
still in the bank account in Zurich.
That's great, that's great.
Someone's after the money
and needs all the pin numbers.
Which means Jared
and I are in danger too.
Unless they got to him first.
C'mon, let's go.
C'mon.
Hurry.
They killed him.
They could've shot us both.
No, they need you alive to
get your part of the pass codes.
Look out.
You okay?
Yeah.
He's dead.
What're you gonna do?
Find out who he is?
I call the police.
Where's the other one?
Klaus Proppe.
Vigo DiPalma.
James Hollings.
How many names has he got?
It's probably none of the above.
He got Yale right between the eyes.
I bet he's an assassin for hire.
Hey, what are you doing?
Where are you going?
You drive.
Most of the calls are to one number.
Country code is forty-one, Switzerland.
City code's forty-four, Zurich.
What are you doing?
Oh, seeing what else is in here.
The truck driver was calling the
police. They'll be able to find us.
Got anything you wanna say
to your boss before I kill ya?
Fuck you.
Jacob.
Stop.
- We need to keep driving...
- Stop the damn car.
They killed Paolo.
They found his body
in the South Gardens of the monastery.
Yale.
You knew him?
He was NIA, and a friend.
It was a single bullet,
precision shot, a probe.
Who've seen this?
You, but just on the safe side,
I left a few things out.
Keene wasn't alone, the monks
reported seeing him with a woman.
They were able to give us
a very detailed description of her.
Apparently, it's been
a while since they've seen one.
So they paid close attention.
Martha.
Another agent?
A recruit.
She was brought in
for specific mission.
There was something else.
The location
of Keene's last cell phone signal
was an address in central Milan.
They found a body there last night.
20 year-old, his throat has been cut.
It doesn't necessarily mean
that Keene had anything to do with it.
He's ex-NIA.
His files are under
a restricted access code.
He was retired
for an embarrassing situation
and dead bodies are piling up
in his wake.
With all due respect, Sir.
I don't think you can
write this off as a coincidence.
With all due respect.
If you have something to say,
Davis, say it.
I thought I was sir.
Is there something
else I need to know about Keene?
Like?
Like how many people
did he kill for this agency?
One, and that was collateral damage.
Keene was part of a team,
whose first mission was aborted due
to circumstances beyond their control.
The target in question is killed.
Is that what these bodies are, sir?
More collateral damage?
I don't know what they are.
But is it is some kind of vendetta that
Keene has in mind it stops here now.
Find him.
Wherever the hell he is, find him.
Whack up new traces.
What do you want us to do to him,
when we find him?
You leave that to me.
They found his body
at the scene of a car crash
just outside
St. Albans carrying NIA documents.
He was discharged from the NIA six
months ago for psychiatric reasons.
So where'd he get the NIA papers?
Pronto.
You all right?
Yes.
Is Julia with you?
Thank god.
Okay, where are you?
At home. Where the hell are you?
Better you don't know.
The police came here looking for you.
They found Paolo's body
at your studio.
Kyra, you know I thought
I could leave the past behind.
I know you did.
But why did you run?
It's complicated.
Look I need your help.
I have a Swiss phone number.
I need you to go on the computer,
use reverse directory,
see if you can get a, uh,
name and an address.
Kyra, it'll take you ten seconds.
Give me the number.
Got it.
Christian Lenk,
Twenty-one Zermatt Strasse,
Zurich, Zero-Five-W.
Great, okay, now you and Julia
need to go away for a couple days.
Go to the inn where she likes to
feed the ducks, you know where I mean.
You are creeping me out.
Promise you'll do it.
Not until you tell me
what's going on.
Okay look,
just get out of your apartment.
Turn off your cell phone. I'll
call you at the inn as soon as I can.
Go now.
Okay.
Tell Julia I love her.
Mama?
Right.
Who's Julia?
She's my daughter.
You were married.
Kyra's a friend of mine.
We both wanted a child.
I want you to tell me the truth.
About what?
You, me, what happened in Berlin.
I told you, we worked together.
Don't.
The memories are fading,
I can feel them disappearing.
I wanna know the truth
while it still matters. Please.
You were studying in Washington.
I was assigned to recruit you.
You seduced me.
It was part of the job.
Why me?
We knew you could help flip Kozlenko.
Who am I?
What is my name?
Kozlenko.
You're Marta Kozlenko.
He was my father?
I lured my father to his death?
It wasn't your fault.
He wanted it to look like a
kidnapping, not a defection.
Somehow the KGB got onto us.
We'll go to Zurich,
first thing in the morning.
I'm sorry.
You're sorry? For what?
For all of this.
Maybe if I hadn't called you
or taken you out of your life, maybe...
It would've happened anyway.
Whoever's
after us needs my numbers too
and you weren't just part of the job.
I've always cared about you,
I always will.
Marta.
Alright we have to get outta here.
What's wrong?
Police are downstairs.
We made the paper.
(speaking German)
You speak English?
We need you to drive us to Zurich.
We're not gonna hurt you.
But my deliveries. I have customers.
Today we're you're only customers.
Don't even think about it.
Thank you, Jann. I hope we didn't
cause you too much trouble.
Appreciate it if you can, uh,
wait a couple hours
before callin' the police.
And you were right.
The strudel was excellent.
Damn, we should have grabbed
a couple of those crescents to go.
Oh well.
Jacob, what happened to me
after my father died?
Honestly, I don't know.
You hated me.
You left Berlin
and I left the business.
And we never spoke again?
Oh, I'd phone,
you wouldn't take my calls.
I have no idea
where you went or what you did.
Started a new life,
thought I could leave the past behind.
So much for that, huh?
We don't just ring the doorbell,
right?
Look, why don't you, uh, stay here.
I'm gonna go look around.
(speaking German)
Marta.
Don't move.
Hi.
How did you?
Dog seems to know you.
Maybe.
Do I live here?
It doesn't look familiar.
Huh, no labels.
Well, someone's got expensive taste.
Men's clothing, no women's.
I must not live here.
Gotta be something
to identify whoever does.
You definitely know
whoever lives here.
Okay, what's going on Marta?
Know what I think?
I think you set me up.
I think this amnesia is bullshit.
No, no.
Oh, fuck me.
What? You're gonna tell me,
you don't know who this is?
Who is it?
It's Jared, damn you.
Paolo and Yale are dead, Marta. Why?
I don't know.
Alright, I don't remember anything,
I swear.
Is Jared a victim too
or is he in on this?
Yeah, um, I'm getting out of here.
What're you gonna do?
It's Kyra.
I told you
to turn off your cell phone.
What have you gotten us into?
Why are you calling here?
Because I told her to.
You know she was packing
to leave when we got here.
Oh, I haven't spoken
to you since Berlin, partner.
What do you want, Jared?
Oh, come on. You're a smart guy.
You've spoken to Marta,
you found my place.
You must have figured it out by now.
Numbers to the Swiss bank account.
There ya go.
This can't be agency sanctioned.
Yeah well,
let's call it my retirement plan.
You killed Yale.
And Paolo.
You dragged them into this.
Now give me the fucking numbers.
You're outta luck asshole.
I forgot 'em years ago.
Really?
Oh you did?
I don't think so.
- Papa, please help us.
- Please...
Mama?
You know it's gonna take me
a little while to get to Zurich
so make yourselves at home.
There's a bottle
of Chateau Le Fit in the cellar.
You kids knock yourselves out.
I'll see you at the bank at four.
You remember where that is.
'Kay, we're not staying here.
And I am not letting you out
of my sight.
Get her ready to go.
Hurray.
No, no.
Please.
- Please.
- Listen. Listen to me. Listen.
You say nothing about this, and
your daughter will be home tonight.
Talk to anyone and she's dead.
You understand what I'm saying.
Look, l- I don't blame you
for not trusting me.
Look, if it makes you feel any better,
the Marta I knew wouldn't be
involved in anything like this.
People don't change that much.
Jacob, where are we going now?
I'm gonna do whatever it
takes to get her back.
If I'm gonna save her,
I'll need your help.
Can I trust you?
C'mon.
That's it.
Shit, c'mon.
Jared.
How'd you recognize me?
From pictures.
Of us together.
Where's Jacob?
Take me to Julia, and when
I know she's okay, I'll call him.
What would you say if I told you,
uh she was still in Italy?
Then you don't get your money.
Good old Jacob, huh?
I shoulda known
he'd keep the game interesting.
Where is he?
Is he looking at us now?
Is the girl in Italy?
No, she's here in Zurich.
I have a taxi waiting.
How long was I with you?
Not long.
You were setting me up.
To get the money.
(speaking German)
How did we get together?
Does it really matter?
Yes.
I tracked you down.
I bumped into you in front
of your apartment in Paris.
Pretended it was just,
uh, by chance.
We had a really good time
in St. Tropez.
You stole my life.
Look, if it's any consolation,
it really wasn't much of a life.
You didn't seem very happy.
Oh. Blame yourself.
I mean, I tried to cut you in, but
you wouldn't give me your pass code,
so I mean, I had to use the drug.
How did I get away from you?
I guess I'm getting old.
Sloppy.
I forgot how physical you could be.
You ran off to tell Jacob.
(speaking German)
Please.
Oh yeah, I'd be afraid too.
Why are you helping him?
Call it instinct.
You couldn't take that away from me.
Uh, do you wanna see the girl or not?
This way.
Stay.
What happened?
It's under control, thank you.
Julia, I'm Marta.
I'm a friend of your father's.
Where is he?
He's waiting for you.
Where?
Yes, okay. Thank you.
You've seen the girl,
now let's make this thing happen.
Jacob wants me to stay with her.
He doesn't care about the money,
he wants his daughter.
And he wants to remember who she is.
Where's the injection gun?
Oh yes, this is vintage Jacob.
Always loves a chess game.
And always three moves ahead.
I have it.
It stays here.
It's the only way
he'll give you his numbers.
You'll meet him
at Fraumunster Church.
And what stops me
from killing you right now?
Because you're a smart man.
You're gonna meet Jacob,
he'll call, you'll
have us released and after that,
you'll have the numbers and Jacob.
You may have lost your memory Marta,
but, uh, you still have balls.
If you haven't heard
from me in an hour,
kill them both.
She really needs to
go to the bathroom.
Do I look like I fucking care?
Just tell me where it is.
Fuck.
The end of the corridor.
(speaking German)
Oh, shit.
I'll walk.
Here.
(speaking German)
Hey.
Get the fuck off.
You alright?
Yeah.
Okay.
Where is she?
This way.
Hey baby. Hi. Hey. Hey. You okay?
Yeah? You're okay. Okay.
Everything's gonna be alright.
Oh god, what would I do without you?
C'mon, daddy's got you.
Let's get outta Zurich.
Not yet.
We got one more thing to do.
Damn it.
Jacob?
Jared.
What's goin' on, buddy?
Where are you?
Turn around.
This isn't working out
the way you wanted, is it?
Let's go in the church.
You need to repent.
Keep going.
You probably don't go to church much,
do you?
What the fuck is this all about?
How about Paolo?
Huh?
How 'bout Yale?
Collateral damage.
Acceptable losses
when you consider that with
interest there's over twenty million
in Kozlenko's account right now.
Aw, c'mon partner, just think
what we could do with that money.
You been planning this
for a long time, huh?
Nah.
You know, you got out when you should.
I stayed too long.
I got bounced around, passed over.
You know, the last time
I really enjoyed the game was Berlin.
Right before the wall came down.
So, you started thinking about
the money.
Yeah, checked some records.
It was forgotten about.
I mean, c'mon,
it's all sitting there, right there.
I think I'm gonna follow your
example, bro, and not share.
You are gonna tell me your code
numbers and Marta's code numbers.
Oh. Oh I know you way too well,
partner.
Yeah?
Yeah.
You're not gonna shoot me.
You couldn't pull the trigger.
You're right.
The only thing I'm gonna regret
is that you won't remember
what an asshole you've become.
I wonder what two shots would do?
So, how did it go?
Couldn't have been smoother.
They didn't ask any questions?
Transferred all the funds to
a new account in the Cayman Islands.
Oh baby.
He was found two weeks ago.
Patrolman saw him wandering
on Bahnhofstrasse.
Dazed, confused.
Ran his prints and uh,
found that he worked for your group,
NATO Intelligence.
Thought you could help us.
He was stationed in Zurich.
Shuffling papers.
Hm.
What'd the doctor's say?
No.
He's catatonic.
Appears to be awake
but he's uh, not responsive.
There's been no change
in the two weeks.
I think he's hopeless.
So whatever he once knew
will die with him.
Nothing?
No sir, we had a tracer
put on Keene's passport.
The woman as well.
But they vanished.
And Jared Clayton.
They are moving him
into a nursing home, outside of Staad.
On NIA pension of course.
Of course.
All right,
we tie up the usual loose ends.
Release statements
about terrorist cells to cover up.
And tomorrow morning,
we'll be back to business as usual.
Good night, agent Henry.
Sir, there's just one more thing.
It's very late.
It's about the Kozlenko affair.
What about it?
I did some research, and as you know
the NIA keeps excellent records.
Kozlenko's require
a Class A security clearance.
And in 1988 there were only two people,
other than the operatives themselves
with that kind of clearance
on that specific project.
One of them Yale, is dead.
Oh god, what the hell is this?
You are the one
that set up agent Kozlenko.
You told the Stazi
about the defection.
And you helped set the trap
that killed him.
You have no proof.
Actually sir, I do, the money.
The ten million dollars marked
for Kozlenko.
Once a year the bank needs
a signature to renew the account.
I checked it out.
It was your signature, sir.
The only thing
I can't figure out is whether
Jared Clayton was working for you.
Or you were working for him?
I knew you were ambitious, Henry.
I just didn't know how ambitious.
Security is on its way up to you, sir.
You might want to call your lawyer.
I'm not going to be calling anybody.
Sir, you were saying?
Sounds good.
I'll release the statement
in the morning.
You should get some sleep,
agent Davis.
You sound tired.
It's been a long week.
Yeah, yeah, I - I can hear him.
Uh, yapping in the background.
Is he house broken yet?
Mm, sorta.
Mama's not really happy.
When are you coming back?
Yeah, I'm- I'm not sure yet, angel.
As soon as I can.
Listen, I gotta go.
I will uh, I'll talk to you tomorrow.
Bye, I love you papa.
I love you too, Julia.
You two,
uh, takin' off for the airport?
Yeah.
You sure
you're doin' the right thing?
I mean, you know,
you just met the guy.
Could be he's only uh,
after your money.
Well, that's okay.
I'm only after his body.
So, how much longer
are you planning on staying?
I gotta think through some things.
Gonna take a while longer.
Don't forget about me.
Jacob Keane?
I'm Agent Henry.
I'm with the agency
you used to work for.
What agency?
We're very impressed
with what you did.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
The director would like to know
if you'd entertain
the notion of taking on a certain
freelance assignment.
And why would I wanna do that?
'Cause you're a rich man now.
I already was a rich man,
Agent Henry.
You gave the money to Marta.
After everything, don't you think
it's the least she deserves?
You on duty right now?
Not officially.
You like rum?
END
Subtitles by LeapinLar
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org