So, this "Naomi"
has been controlling you
since she got you
out of Purgatory?
Yes.
So you just want to
guide me out of Purgatory
out of the goodness
of your undead heart?
More or less.
What's in it for you?
I'm hopping a ride.
What?
It's a human portal,
jackass.
Only humans
can pass through.
He's a vampire.
He's also the reason I'm topside.
I know you had to do
what you had to down there.
But you're out now,
and Benny's still breathing.
Why?
Listen, Benny,
everything you've done for me
I will never forget.
End of the line?
End of the line.
God built a series of tests.
When you've done all three,
you can slam the Gates.
Sam,
I didn't pass a test.
But I did. And I'm doing
the rest of them.
You got to slow down.
No.
You said nuking hell --
that's how I get out.
That's how I go home.
I need this to be over.
Kevin.
I know what you're up to...
Working with them,
those Winchesters.
Dead end, Kevin.
Not here.
Not here, either.
Give up.
I'm in your head,
as well as everywhere else.
Last time you irked me,
you lost a finger.
Imagine what will happen
this time.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
♪ Supernatural 8x19 ♪
Taxi Driver
Original Air Date on April 3, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Kevin, open up!
Kevin!
Whoa! Whoa.
Geez. What's going on?
What's with the S.O.S.?
It's him.
It's who?
Crowley.
What about him?
He's in my head.
He's...in your head.
Do you know
what that means?
Yeah, it means we need
to up your anxiety meds.
Kevin, you're dreaming.
Look, if Crowley knew
where you were,
he'd do a hell of a lot more
than mess with your head.
All right, where's Garth?
On a case or -- or the dentist.
I don't know.
I haven't heard from him.
Okay, well, what did you want to tell us
that you
couldn't say on the phone?
Would you put the frying pan
down, please?
I translated the second trial
from the tablet.
You...crazy Prophet, you.
Nice work!
And if Crowley's in my head,
he knows.
Okay, he's definitely not in your head.
He's not in your head, Kevin.
It's okay. Just...
We know you're distressed.
Just stay with us, all right?
What's the second trial?
An innocent soul
has to be rescued from Hell
and delivered unto Heaven.
What?
"Unto." That's --
that's how God talks.
Rescue a soul from Hell?
Like actually...Go to Hell?
How -- how do you get a soul
unto Heaven?
I mean, how do you even
get a soul out of Hell?
We're gonna need
an expert.
Winchesters.
What happened
to the hot chicks?
I'm out of here.
Maybe not.
I ain't got nothing.
Oh?
Bite me.
Well, then how about
another owie?
Ohh!
You know, wouldn't it be
a lot easier
just to tell us how to enter
Hell, uh, uninvited?
It's...a secret.
We promise
we won't tell anyone.
No! Wait. I can't.
It's forbidden, man.
They're gonna kill me.
Please...
All right, look...
For a price, y'all can be
smuggled across Hell's border.
By who?
Rogue reapers.
They got secret ways,
in and out.
Not just Hell --
the Veil, Heaven.
Rogue reapers
smuggling people?
People, souls...
So, what?
They're like hell coyotes?
Now kill me.
Come on, man.
Better death than Crowley.
Hmm. Good point.
But first
you're gonna tell us...
everything.
Ajay.
Need to talk to you
for a sec.
You know my name.
And what you do.
We want to do business.
But you are mortal --
flesh and blood.
But if we wanted to cross
the border into Hell --
visitor's pass.
No one
wants to get into Hell.
But could a coyote like you
do it?
It's possible.
But I have special skills.
I have overhead.
It will be pricy.
How pricey?
You two are resourceful.
One day,
you will owe me a favor.
You say that
like you know us.
Of course.
You're the Winchesters.
Sorry. Have we met?
I am the reaper
who took Bobby Singer to Hell.
Bobby in Hell?
We burned his bones.
Once we did that, it was over.
End of story.
Hmm...
Not necessarily.
No, no, no, 'cause, see, Bobby
was on the good side of things,
and good guys
go to the penthouse.
Usually, mostly.
Depends on who you know,
what palms get greased.
If you're on the King of Hell's
no-fly list,
no way you cruise
the friendly skies.
Crowley.
Okay, let's do this.
How much for two tickets down
and three back?
Dean.
What?
Come here.
What the hell
are you thinking?
You heard the guy --
Bobby's in Hell.
We're gonna spring him.
We've gone over this, Dean.
I have to do the trials solo.
This is Bobby
we're talking about, Sam.
Now let's face it --
you have not exactly been
up to full speed lately, okay?
We got one shot at this.
We can't miss.
I'm not gonna miss.
I'll bring him back.
I'm in, just me.
Follow me.
Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait.
How does this...Work?
Not to fret.
He'll be back
in exactly 24 hours time.
Return for him then.
Take my hand.
And it gets creepier.
So, this is Hell?
Not at all.
This is Purgatory.
What do you mean
this is Purgatory?
This isn't what I paid for.
I booked the Hell tour.
Whoa, whoa, Winchester,
detach.
This is Hell-adjacent.
Been down this highway
many times before.
Follow the stream to where
three trees meet as one.
Where they meet,
there are rocks.
Between the rocks
is the portal.
A portal?
A back door to Hell.
Trust me -- it'll work.
Wait. So you're not
coming with me?
Don't be ridiculous.
Smuggling a mortal across
the border is risky enough.
But gate-crashing a Winchester
into Hell seriously blows.
No. I'll be back in 24 hours,
precisely.
Be here.
It's a good thing
you brought that.
It is not
an easy place.
Yo, Kev, it's me!
Kevin.
I believe the closet
would be safest.
Safe from what?
Crowley.
He's in my head, Dean.
And if he's in my head,
he knows where I am!
You know,
we -- we should move out.
We'll find another place.
Geez, Kev,
would you chill out, huh?
Have a burger.
Come on.
Don't lose it on me now, dude.
There you go.
That's it.
Just tell me
when this all ends,
'cause that's the only thing
I want to hear.
No, like I told you before,
this isn't going to end.
Look, man, other guys,
they got it easy, you know?
It's all backyard barbecues
and...bowling teams,
but you and me?
We got to carry
a little extra weight.
I can't take it.
Yes, you can.
Hey, look at me.
Now, this whole thing sucks.
I know.
But you suck it up
and you push through
because that's what we do.
And when you get on board
with that,
the ride is a lot smoother.
French fry?
I'm gonna --
I'm gonna be in my room.
Let me know
when there's a good day.
That's my pie.
Hello, Ajay.
It's been a while
since we chatted --
too long.
Pizza?
Extra anchovies.
Anything you want to
get off your chest?
An update?
Um...No.
No, not really.
As you may recall, patience
isn't one of my virtues.
Well, I don't have any virtues,
but if I did,
I'm certain that patience
wouldn't be one.
So, sure there's nothing
weighing on you?
Nothing, say, about making
a deal with the Winchesters?
Sir, I know better
than to attempt that.
My operative saw you leaving
with Sam Winchester.
Oh! Oh, Sam Winchester.
Oh, yes, that's, uh...
A possibility.
You're trying
my non-patience.
Sir, I was just doing
what I do.
As you are
more than aware,
I do occasionally --
moonlight as a freelancer.
You do not freelance
with them.
What did Sam want?
Well, uh, actually, it's, uh,
starting to come back.
He may have wanted
to get into Hell.
My Hell?
Why would he want to do that?
I don't know.
I swear. My job --
I don't ask questions.
And what time is Mr. Winchester
due back from Hell?
Uh,
I'm picking him up in...
Well, now 17 hours.
I see.
Anything else?
No.
I swear.
Hmm.
That's one fare
you won't be collecting.
It's a rabbit hole.
This is nuts.
I'm...innocent.
Help me.
Eddy? Eddy?
You came.
I knew you would.
I've been praying for it
forever.
I'm not...him.
I'm sorry.
You came.
I knew you would.
I've been praying for it.
Forever.
You came.
I knew you would.
I've been praying for it
forever.
Bobby?
Get the hell out of here,
you black-eyed son of a bitch.
What?
Bobby, it's Sam.
Yeah, and I'm Elvis.
Move your ass!
Bobby --
get!
It's me!
Okay, damn it.
If it's not Sam...
Then how do I know all about you
and Tori spelling?
What?
You're a fan. Yeah.
Or -- or, uh...
Okay. What about your free
pedicure at the Mall of America?
You made Dean swear to
never tell another living soul
how it changed your life.
Sam?
I'm sorry, Sam, but you're
the 200th Sam I've seen today.
That's
how they screw with me.
Just endless Sams and Deans
all wearing the Sam black eyes.
Wait a minute.
What the hell
are you doing here?
Please don't tell me
it's what I think it is.
No, no, no,
Bobby, I'm good. I...
I'm here to get you.
You don't belong here,
Bobby.
And we're getting you out.
Am I the only one who sees
the urgency of this situation?
Sir --
Something is going on.
My Hellhound
has been killed.
Winchester jumbo size is trying
to break into the mother ship.
And that Prophet of theirs
is madly translating away.
Add it up!
I will, sir.
Where did we get you, huh?
Temp agency?
I need Kevin Tran, and I need
his half of the tablet.
Apparently,
his half has the good stuff,
where mine has
the acknowledgements
and "about the author."
It will be done.
It had better be.
Find that kid.
Hey, Kevin!
Come in here
and grab some of these eggs.
Kev! Come on, man.
You can't hide in there forever.
Where the hell you been?
What happened
to being scared?
I am scared.
So I made
a preemptive move.
So...
Made a what now?
I can't sit here with the tablet
like a...sitting duck
and Crowley
breathing down my ass.
Getting rid of the tablet just
takes off some of the pressure.
Wait.
Getting rid of it?
Temporarily. I hid it.
What? Where?
If I tell you where,
it's not hidden, is it?
Kevin, tell me where the damn
tablet is, or I swear to you --
You'll what, Dean?
Kevin!
Kids. So cute
when they're little.
Then they turn into teenagers,
and the party's over.
We haven't been
formally introduced, Dean.
My name is Naomi.
Oh,
I know who you are.
And I know
what you did to Cass
after he got
out of Purgatory.
After I rescued him
from Purgatory, you mean,
at the cost
of many angels' lives.
You screwed with his head
and had him spy on us.
Well, it is true that I have
spoken with Castiel many times,
trying to reach out to him,
trying to help him.
Dean, you must have noticed
how Purgatory changed him.
I mean, he's been unstable
in the past,
but I was shocked
at how damaged he is now.
Stop, okay?
Don't -- don't try to spin this.
You think I don't know that you
told him to try and kill me?
Hmm.
Yeah, I suppose
that is how he would hear it.
When I learned
of the Angel tablet,
I did tell Castiel
to get it at any cost.
That's my job --
to protect heaven.
I'm a warrior,
just as you are.
What would you expect?
And now Castiel is
in the wind
with a hydrogen bomb
in his pocket,
and I -- I'm scared,
for all of us.
Save it.
See, I don't trust Angels,
which means I don't trust you.
And yet you haven't warded
this place against us.
I know.
You're hoping
Castiel will return to you.
I admire your loyalty.
I only wish
he felt the same way.
I know you don't want to
believe it, Dean,
but we're on the same side --
shutting the Gates of Hell,
bringing Castiel in
from the cold.
Take a moment.
Think about
what I've said.
Oh.
I know you've been
doing business with Ajay.
He did mention,
didn't he,
that his way into Hell
is through Purgatory?
I knew
you'd want to know.
You see, we can be of help
to each other.
You know
where the hell you're going?
Yeah,
we're almost there.
Get back.
Get back, get back.
Let's go!
We got to get out of here!
Bobby,
they're messing with you.
Don't listen to him.
He's not real.
Bobby, get away from him!
We got to go now -- aah!
You knew somehow,
right?
Took a chance.
50/50.
What do we do now?
Look, look.
Ajay? Hey.
What the hell is this?
All right,
don't get all pissed off.
Purgatory.
Balls!
Let's go.
Yeah. Hey, it's me.
I know.
I know, man.
It's been a long time.
I mean, I wanted to call. I did.
I just, uh...
I thought it might be better
if I didn't.
So good to hear your voice,
Dean.
I mean that.
How you been?
Oh, you know...
I get by.
I guess I let you down,
huh?
Look, I'm, uh...
I'm just happy as hell
to hear from you.
You might change your mind
about that.
Why? What you mean?
Benny,
I got to ask you a favor.
It's a big one.
So, how many more
of these trials after this?
Just one.
Don't know what it is,
though -- not yet.
Kevin's
still translating.
Well, you saw back there in
Hell, I ain't got a lot of rust.
Just feels so good
to be back in action again.
Might be handy
if you had me around to help.
Bobby, I'd --
I'd love that, believe me.
The thing is,
for this trial to be completed,
your soul
has to enter Heaven.
And besides,
if that weren't the case,
we burned your bones,
Bobby.
There's nothing to tie
your spirit to earth.
Yeah. Yeah, well...
You know, I always figured
that'd be the end of it...
You know,
just a Hunter's funeral.
Zip. Nothing.
And I was okay with that.
Imagine my surprise.
Well, I guess
if there has to be an eternity,
I'd pick Heaven over Hell.
Yeah. 'Cause there's nothing
screwy going on up there.
I wish I made the rules.
Well...
I'll, uh, do my part,
get to the end of this, but...
I ain't exactly
the retiring type,
so, you idjits figure out
a way to spring me...
Yeah. No, of course.
That's, uh -- yeah.
Oh, well,
let's get topside.
What's going on, Sam?
This is it. This is the place.
I'm sure of it.
Where your cabbie's
supposed to meet you?
Yeah. At exactly...now.
So,
he's running a little late.
No, see,
that's the thing.
He was very specific, Bobby,
like, to the minute.
And if he doesn't show...?
We got no way out.
If you want
nothing to do with this,
I completely understand.
Wow.
When Dean Winchester asks for a
favor, he's not screwing around.
Benny,
sending you back there
is the last thing
I ever wanted to do.
I know. I know.
But my little brother
is stuck down there.
This would be the little brother
who wants to kill me, right?
You got access
to the place.
By "access,"
you mean "getting beheaded"?
Yeah,
you're right -- it's too much.
It's not like I've exactly been
there for you lately.
What?
Oh, come on, Dean.
You know
I love a challenge.
You're serious?
Hey,
he's your brother.
I say let's do this.
I owe you.
Oh,
you don't owe me nothing.
Truth is, uh...
I could use a break
from all this.
It really been
that tough?
I'm not a good fit,
Dean.
Not with vampires and, for sure,
not with the humans.
I don't belong.
And after a while...
that starts to wear on you.
Right?
Cry me a river.
Like you need to listen to this.
Well,
when you get back up here,
we're gonna fix all that,
okay?
When I get back?
Yeah,
you find the portal,
and your ride out of Purgatory
with Sam
just like you did with me,
okay?
As soon
as I send you back,
I'm gonna haul my ass
up to Maine,
and I'm gonna be waiting there
for you when you get topside.
Yeah. That sounds
like a plan, chief.
Let's get on with it.
You sure about this?
Not my first rodeo,
man.
Thank you.
Well, come on.
You a wimp?
Dean spent a year
in this place?
Running and fighting,
all day, every day.
Must have been hell on you
not being able to get him out
all that time.
You did try?
Look, Bobby, Dean and I
had an agreement, okay?
I know that agreement.
I taught you
that agreement.
That's a non-agreement.
I get the feeling a lot must
have happened while I was gone.
Sam!
Bobby, no, no, wait!
Wait! Wait!
Why are you here?
Dean sent me.
Dean? Not my Dean.
He's a buddy of Dean's,
Bobby.
A buddy?
A good buddy.
A frigging vampire?
Well, you two really
went off the rails
while I was gone,
didn't you?
Hey, Benny, listen -- I know
you saved my brother's ass
a few times down here,
and I respect that.
Yeah, and now
I'm trying to save yours.
You know, I'm a disgrace
to my own people.
Yeah,
this is the spot.
The seam that gets us
back up top?
Mm-hmm.
Is that it?
Yeah, that's it.
You boys remember
what I told you?
Yeah.
All right, Bobby,
here it goes.
When we get to earth
and I release you,
it's an express
straight to heaven.
No time for goodbyes.
Already said goodbye
to you once, Sam.
Didn't seem to take.
No reason to think
I won't see you again
somewhere down the road.
Yeah.
But if they give me
a rocking chair up there,
I'm raising hell.
Conjuncti sumus,
unum sumus.
All right. Come on, Benny.
It's your turn.
Hurry up.
Benny.
And still working
with the Winchesters.
Hurry.
Time for you to go,
Sam.
Benny?
Go on.
It's me they want. Go on.
You just make sure you tell Dean
I said goodbye.
I was never any good
up there anyway.
Benny, wait!
Benny?
Purgatory, right?
A real garden spot,
ain't it?
Yeah.
Did you get him out?
Only Bobby.
What?
I mean,
that's fantastic about Bobby.
Dean, look --
Benny, uh...
He got us out.
A bunch of vamps showed,
and he used himself as bait.
I get the feeling
that even if that didn't happen,
he didn't want to come back,
you know?
I'm sorry.
You're probably right.
So, uh...Bobby -- how --
how'd he hold up down there?
He's good,
all things considered.
Ornery as hell,
of course.
As he should be.
Let's put that old man
where he belongs.
Yeah.
Solvo haec phantasmata
in terram,
et inde ad olympum.
What the hell?
Hello, boys.
Bobby Singer --
I'd know you anywhere.
Let him go, Crowley.
He doesn't belong
in Hell.
He does
if I say he does.
He's inflicted untold damage
on my kind.
From where I sit, actually,
Hell's too good for him.
Really?
What?
Oh, come on!
Let me see if I've interpreted
the situation correctly.
The Winchesters have freed
an innocent from Hell,
to which you are
wrongfully trying to return it.
Siding with them, Naomi?
You don't know those two.
Before they're done,
we'll both be locked away.
I'm just hoping
they lock you away, dear.
The rest I'll figure out.
Bureaucrat.
You're fighting
outside your weight class.
Don't call me
a bureaucrat.
I told you
you could trust me.
What the hell
was that about?
I'll tell you later.
Let's get this trial done.
Kah-nuh-ahm-dahr.
Sam?
What? What?!
Talk to me! What?!
It's okay! It's okay!
It's okay. I'm fine.
It's done.
Or a slow player?
So tired of this,
aren't you, Kevin?
Fear, the hiding.
I know I am.
Just a dream.
It's just a dream.
Kevin Tran.
It's been a while.
Thought you could
elude me forever?
There's always a way.
If you can't find one Tran,
find another.
Your mom,
she didn't want to give you up.
Quite a pain threshold,
that one.
But even she
could only take so much.
She never would have
told you.
Moms are like that,
aren't they?
So we killed her and got
your address off her smartphone.
No!!
What you people
never seem to understand
is that you are nothing!
Fleeting blips
of light.
I am forever.
You okay?
I buried Benny...
...but I didn't burn
his bones.
After he said he'd try
to get you out of there,
it just didn't seem right.
I know you got
no use for him, but --
No, no, no.
You know what?
I get it.
I do. He's a...
He's a little different
from what I thought.
So, go ahead and leave the door
open if you want.
All right, well, let's go
check in with Prophet boy
and see where he stashed
that tablet.
Kevin? It's us.
Kevin!
Kevin?
He's gone.
He took all our stuff,
his notes...
I saw this coming.
Finally freaked.
Little geek
made a run for it.
Yeah, but where?
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org