Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
You're from Baker?
Tell Baker that I told him
all that I know already.
Tell him I want to live in peace,
understand?
There is no use to go on tormenting me!
I know nothing at all
about that case of coins.
Now that gold has disappeared,
but if he'd listened...
we could have avoided this altogether.
I went to the army court.
There were no witnesses.
They couldn't uncover any more.
I can't tell Baker
what happened to the money.
Go back and tell him that.
Word's around you had a visitor...
and Baker knows it.
Name of Jackson.
Well...
Jackson was here...
or Baker's got it all wrong.
He's not wrong.
Maybe Baker would like to know
just what you and Jackson had to say...
about the cash box.
That's not what I'm being paid for.
I'm only interested in what name
Jackson's hiding under now.
Why do you think Jackson may be
assuming another name?
I would have found him already.
When I start off to find somebody,
I find him.
That's why they pay me.
What is Baker paying you?
That your family?
Yes.
Nice family.
What does he pay you for murdering me?
Five hundred dollars...
to get the name.
The name.
Carson. Bill Carson.
That's what he calls himself now.
That's a lot of money... 1,000.
A thousand dollars?
And some in gold. That's a tidy sum.
But when I'm paid,
I always see the job through.
It's you.
Any information?
Too much.
He said quite a bit
that should interest you...
and one or two things that interested me.
Such as?
The name Jackson's hiding under
is Bill Carson.
That's your bit.
Keep talking.
He also mentioned something
about a certain cash box...
which just happened to disappear.
- That's my bit.
- Anything else?
Not enough for you, eh?
Well, you don't have to worry.
He won't say anything to anybody again.
Oh, yeah, yeah. Perfect.
Here you are.
Here. This is for you.
You did a good job for me.
Worth $500.
Yeah. I almost forgot.
He gave me a thousand.
I think his idea was that I kill you.
But you know the pity is, when I'm paid,
I always follow my job through.
- You know that.
- No! Angel Eyes...
No. No pistol, amigo.
It won't do you any good.
There are three of us.
You know you've got a face
beautiful enough to be worth $2,000?
Yeah.
But you don't look
like the one who'll collect it.
A couple steps back.
Thank you.
How much are you worth now?
How much?
Two thousand dollars.
- That's right... $2,000.
- Yeah.
You'll pay for this!
I hope you end up in a graveyard...
with the cholera
and the rabies and the plague!
Cut me loose!
Cut me loose, you filthy bastard!
Put me down!
I hope your mother ends up in
a two-dollar whorehouse! Cut me loose!
You can still save yourself.
Let me go, and I'll pardon you.
Let me go!
I think I feel sick.
The blood is bursting through my...
I'm dry, Blondie.
Water.
You swine! You son of a bitch!
Let me go!
You're brave with a man
who's tied up! Come back!
Come back and fight! You bastard.
Who the hell is that?
One bastard goes in, another comes out.
Cut it out! Cut it out!
I'm an honest farmer!
I'm innocent of any...
So, you're an honest farmer.
You recognize this man?
- Me?
- Yeah, it's you.
Me? Who says so? You can't even read.
Yeah, roll it up. Roll it up.
I'll give you a good idea
where you can put it.
To hell with all you sheriffs and
deputies and all who gave birth to you.
Hey, everybody, look!
He's giving him the filthy money!
Judas! You sold my hide!
But you won't enjoy
any of that money... not a penny.
If there's justice in the world,
every penny will go to the undertakers.
You know who you are?
You want to know whose son you are?
You don't, I do. Everybody does.
You're the son of a thousand fathers,
all bastards like you.
And your mother... Your mother!
She's... You bastard!
Your mother...
it's better not to talk of her!
I never hurt anybody!
"Wanted in 14 counties of this state...
"the condemned is found guilty
of the crimes of murder...
"armed robbery of citizens,
state banks and post offices...
"the theft of sacred objects,
arson in a state prison...
"perjury, bigamy,
deserting his wife and children...
"inciting prostitution,
kidnapping, extortion...
"receiving stolen goods,
selling stolen goods...
"passing counterfeit money and,
contrary to the laws of this state...
"the condemned is guilty...
"of using marked cards and loaded dice."
Therefore, according to the powers
vested in us...
we sentence the accused here before us...
Tuco Benedicto Pacifico
Juan Maria Ramirez...
- Known as "The Rat."
- and any other aliases he might have...
to hang by the neck until dead.
May God have mercy on his soul.
Proceed.
Five for you. One, two...
three, four, five for me.
Five for you...
and five for me.
Know how much you're worth now?
- No. How much?
- $3,000.
There are two kinds of people
in the world, my friend...
those with a rope around their neck, and
the people who have the job of cutting.
Listen, the neck
at the end of the rope is mine.
I run the risks...
so the next time, I want more than half.
You may run the risks, my friend,
but I do the cutting.
If we cut down my percentage...
Cigar?
It's liable to interfere with my aim.
But if you miss,
you had better miss very well.
Whoever double-crosses me
and leaves me alive...
he understands nothing about Tuco.
Nothing.
"Wanted in 15 counties of this state.
"The condemned standing before us..."
sitting before us...
"Tuco Benedicto Pacifico
Juan Maria Ramirez...
"has been found guilty by the Third
District Circuit Court of the following:
"murder, assaulting
a justice of the peace...
"raping a virgin of the white race...
"statutory rape of a minor
of the black race...
"derailing a train
in order to rob the passengers...
"bank robbery, highway robbery...
"robbing an unknown number
of post offices, breaking out..."
- What'd you find out, Shorty?
- If you ask me, it seems like a book...
an armed unit escorting a cash box
of gold coins meets a Yankee ambush...
and only three of them are saved:
Stevens, Baker and Jackson.
The thing that wasn't saved, though,
was the coins.
But then the army decides, of course...
it ought to hold a hearing,
and Jackson's acquitted.
- He disappears and becomes Bill Carson.
- I know his name.
But you don't know
just who you're looking for, and I do.
And when he's found,
I'd be scared to be put in his shoes.
Where is Carson?
All I know is Carson reenlisted.
The poor guy's minus an eye.
He lives with a girl called Maria
who'll tell you.
She's a fresh young whore in the territory.
- Where's she?
- Now, what's the name of that town?
Someplace fairly near.
Santa Ana.
Adios, half-soldier.
Hey, Luke, hand me down a whiskey!
"...and the sheriff's office in Sonora.
"The condemned hired himself out
as a guide to a wagon train.
"After receiving his payment in advance,
he deserted the wagon train...
"on the hunting grounds
of the Sioux Indians."
Glad they got him...
a man guilty of all those crimes.
People with ropes around their necks
don't always hang.
What do you mean?
"The condemned is also guilty..."
Even a filthy beggar like that
has got a protecting angel.
- "...as a Mexican general."
- A golden-haired angel watches over him.
"For all these crimes
the accused has made...
"a full, spontaneous confession.
"Therefore, we condemn him
to be hung by the neck until dead."
May the Lord have mercy
on his soul. Proceed.
Let's get the hell out of here!
What are you trying to say...
anybody can miss a shot?
Nobody misses
when I'm at the end of the rope.
You've never had a rope around
your neck. I'll tell you something.
When that rope starts to pull tight,
you can feel the devil bite your ass.
Yeah, you're right. It's getting tougher.
The way I figure, there's not too much
future with a sawed-off runt like you.
What do you mean?
'Cause I don't think
you'll ever be worth more than $3,000.
What do you mean?
I mean, our partnership is untied.
Oh, no. Not you. You remain tied.
I'll keep the money,
and you can have the rope.
You filthy, double-crossing bastard!
- Of all the stinking, dirty tricks...
- The way back to town is only 70 miles.
You know, if you save your breath,
I feel a man like you could manage it.
You filthy bastard! Come here!
Come here! Cut this rope off!
Get off that horse, you filthy coward!
If I ever catch you, Blondie,
I'll rip your heart out and eat it!
I'll scalp you! I'll skin you alive!
I'll hang you up by your thumbs!
You pig! You vulture!
I'll kill you! I'll kill you!
Such ingratitude, after all the times
I've saved your life.
Where are you going? Wait a minute.
This is only a trick.
You wouldn't leave me here.
Come back! Wait! Blondie!
Listen, Blondie...
I believe madam is home.
Sweet dreams, and many thanks
from the Seventh Cavalry!
You filthy rats!
Maria.
Honey? Is that you, Bill?
Who are you? What do you want with me?
Go on talking about Bill Carson.
I don't know him.
You were calling to him in the dark.
Where is he?
What are you going to do to him?
I'll ask the questions.
Where is he?
Where is he? Where?
That's enough!
I don't know where he is.
He packed his things ten days ago...
and went away with his unit...
they all left.
Which company? Where'd they go?
Third Cavalry, General Sibley.
They left for Santa Fe.
That's all I know, I swear!
But, but...
I'm very sorry, but the store's closing.
- Revolvers.
- Yeah, revolvers.
Revolvers.
Well, here's where I keep the best ones.
Here. Remington, Colt...
a Roat, Smith-Wesson...
Colt... Navy...
Joslyn...
another Remington.
- And this one is...
- That's enough.
Cartridges.
You want to try the pistol?
Just step out back.
Let's go.
Move. Move.
Cartridge.
- How much?
- Twenty dollars.
No.
Fifty dollars.
How much?
A hundred dollars.
Two hundred dollars.
It's all I've got.
Here.
Come here.
This morning I heard the whole thing.
They say that Colonel Canby's
closing in with his Northerners...
and no later than tomorrow
that they'll be in the city.
That's why these Southerners
are getting out.
You see, as soon as these cowards hear
a Blue Shirt's around, they run.
- These Rebels have no will to fight.
- Poor things.
They'll soon be finished.
We get rid of these bastards, then we
begin making money on those Yankees.
They carry gold, not paper dollars,
and they're going to beat the South.
Look. See that one with the white beard
sitting in the wagon?
General Sibley. He looks dead.
He's finally getting out of our hair.
Hurray for Dixie!
Where's the owner of that horse?
- Please, sir, a bad heart condition...
- Where?
The war has frightened me already.
I'm looking for the owner of that horse.
He's tall, blond, he smokes a cigar,
and he's a pig. Where is he now?
You leave him be.
He doesn't know who rides every horse.
You stay quiet, old hen.
Upstairs. Upstairs in room four, señor.
Hear that?
You rotten criminals. How dare you?
Your spurs.
There are two kinds of spurs, my friend...
those that come in by the door...
and those that come in by the window.
Take off that pistol belt.
It's empty.
Mine isn't.
Even when Judas hanged himself,
there was a storm too.
That could be cannon fire.
Cannon fire or storm,
it's all the same to you.
You ever see this before, my friend?
Throw it over the roof beam.
That's it.
Now get on that.
That's right.
Now make sure the rope is tight.
It's got to hold the weight of a pig.
Now put the rope around your neck.
That's very good.
It's too big for your neck, huh?
We fix that right away.
I have another system...
a little different than yours.
I don't shoot the rope.
I shoot the legs off the stool.
Welcome, my friend.
If you're looking for a summer
vacation spot, you've found it.
Our hotel is luxurious
and filled with conveniences.
And the attractions don't stop there.
International cuisine,
healthful and nutritious food.
Corn cobs, Dixie-style.
Our government has spared no expense.
As you can see, we are treated very well.
Have you ever heard of anyone
by the name of Bill Carson?
And you? Have you ever heard
of someone named Canby? No?
Well, you see, he's a Yankee colonel
who decided to tear us to pieces.
The only thing we care about
is saving our own hides.
And you ask me if I know someone.
I just don't know what you drifters
could be thinking.
Carson has a patch over one eye.
He's with the Third.
If he's with the Third,
they've already left.
For Glorieta.
Canby's front line is right on their heels.
Those poor young devils.
And the desert lies ahead of them. I really
doubt that any of them are still alive.
And what if they were still alive?
Worse.
Well, then, you must not have
heard anything about Batterville.
It's one of those Yankee prison camps
you'd better hope you never end up in.
Keep it. It's yours.
"We have found the accused,
Thomas Larson, alias Shorty Larson...
"guilty of the following crimes:
"horse theft, theft of supplies
belonging to the Union Army...
"theft of supplies belonging
to the Confederate Army...
"wounding two vigilantes...
"assault and battery on
one named Barry O'Keefe...
"perjury, blackmail, robbery...
"escaping from a state prison,
disturbing the peace...
- "pandering, highway robbery..."
- And Shorty?
"forgery and murder.
"Therefore, with the powers vested in us
by the laws of this state..."
- No.
- No?
"...we have condemned
the aforementioned Thomas Larson...
"alias Shorty Larson...
"to hang by the neck until dead."
May God have mercy on his soul. Proceed.
Sorry, Shorty.
Move. Come on, let's go.
I don't know. As soon as I hit
the desert, I'm thirsty.
Burns, huh? They say people
with fair skin can't take too much.
Like that,
you won't have to carry so much.
Where we going?
Where? Where I'm going, amigo.
Over that way.
Another hundred miles
of beautiful, sunbaked sand.
Even the armies are afraid
to march through there.
Sibley's men are retreating up there.
Canby's men are coming here.
But no one will set foot in this hell...
except you and me.
One hundred miles... that's a nice walk.
What was it you told me the last time?
"If you save your breath,
I feel a man like you could manage it."
And if you won't manage it,
you'll die, only slowly...
very slowly, old friend.
After you, please. Start walking.
Taking a rest?
Come on, Blondie.
We don't have very far to go.
Only 70 miles.
Only eight and a half hours more
before sunset.
That's not too bad.
Come on.
Okay, let's eat.
That is, I'll eat.
Meanwhile, you can enjoy a sunbath.
You want some water?
Drink. Drink.
Come on. Come on.
Well, Blondie. So long.
And so, Blondie...
it's good-bye.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Whoa, boy.
Easy, easy.
Easy, easy. Attaboy. That's nice.
Water. Water.
200,000 in gold.
It's yours. Just get me water.
What's that you say?
Who the hell are you?
Carson.
My name is Bill Carson now. It's Carson.
Surprise attack.
All dead. My name is Jackson, not Carson.
Carson, yeah, yeah.
Glad to meet you, Carson.
I'm Lincoln's grandfather.
What did you say about the dollars?
200,000... all mine.
Was the Third Cavalry's.
Baker has nothing.
The gold... I hid the gold.
The gold is safe.
Where? Where, here?
Here? Talk!
- Huh?
- In the cemetery.
- Which cemetery?
- The one...
on Sad Hill.
There's a grave by...
Which grave?
Have a name? Have a number?
Come on, you dummy, talk.
There's no number. There's a name.
- Huh?
- It's written...
Yes?
Water!
You talk first, huh?
I'll give you water later.
Sad Hill Cemetery. Okay.
In the grave. Okay.
But it must have a name
or a number on it, huh?
There must be a thousand, five thousand!
Don't die, huh?
Don't die. I'll get you water.
Stay there. Don't move. I'll get you water.
Don't die until later, you son of a...
Get away from there!
- He's dead.
- Yeah.
I'll kill you.
If you do that, you'll always be poor...
just like the greasy rat that you are.
If I were you, I'd keep me alive.
What did he tell you, huh?
- A name.
- Huh?
- A name on a grave.
- What name?
Blondie, don't die.
Blondie, don't die. I'm your friend.
Please don't die. Please!
I'm your friend. Come on.
I'll help you. I'll help you.
Don't move. I'll be right back.
Here's the water. Don't die like that pig.
Hey, Blondie, here's water. Water, Blondie.
Don't drink, don't drink.
Is no good for you.
Feel better?
Blondie, what's the matter?
Please, don't die.
Hey, open up! Open up! Hurry!
Settle down. Settle down. Who's there?
What do you mean, "Who's there?"
You think I'm the enemy?
If I were a Yankee,
you wouldn't have time to ask me that.
Come on.
Sergeant, listen to
this corporal for a moment.
Yes, sir.
Sergeant, I have a gravely wounded man
here, if he's not dead already.
- He's still alive?
- Well, he seems to be.
- What happened?
- It was a trap.
- Only the two of us got away.
- Name and traveling papers.
Here. Corporal Bill Carson.
Third Regiment, 2nd Cavalry Squadron,
arriving from San Rafael. Is that enough?
Are you reading when this man is dying?
Why, Corporal, we're trying to withdraw
and you're looking for an infirmary?
If you want one, you'll have
to make yourself a Yankee prisoner.
- So where are we?
- Near Apache Canyon.
- Apache Canyon?
- Apache Canyon.
Is a Mission San Antonio around here?
Sure, 18 miles south. Take him there.
The brothers take care of any wounded,
no matter what the color of his uniform.
And keep your eyes open,
the area is full of Yankees.
Thank you. Goodbye, Sergeant.
Take care.
- I've got a very sick man here.
- But we have no more beds here.
Let him have yours.
- Where's Pablo Ramirez?
- Father Ramirez.
He's away at the moment.
He should be back any day now.
Well, it doesn't matter. For the moment,
we take very good care of my friend.
And may God be praised.
In case you didn't know it,
God is on our side too...
because He hates the Yanks, huh, Blondie?
Blondie? Father, is he still breathing?
- Yes, of course.
- You're heavy.
There.
All right, put a fresh bandage on him.
Put him in my cell.
Easy.
- Out, soldier. Out you go. Come on.
- Look out for him, please.
He's like a brother to me.
Hey, Father, I...
Father, did he speak? Did he say anything?
Father, did he ask for me?
Did he speak about anything, Father?
Oh, no, he hasn't spoken as yet.
But you mustn't worry.
He's both young and strong.
That's what's kept him going until now.
He should regain his strength
in a very short time.
Thank you, Father. You don't know
how much this boy's life means to me.
Thanks be to Jesus. Thanks to all of you.
Hey, Blondie.
The old father tells me you'll be
up and around in a few days.
You're very lucky
to have me so close when it happened.
Think if you'd been on your own.
Look, I mean, when...
when one is ill...
it's good to have somebody close by...
friends or relations.
Do you have parents, Blondie? A mother?
Not even a mother.
No one?
You're all alone, huh? Like me, Blondie.
We're all alone in the world.
I have you, you have me.
Only for a little while, I mean.
It had to happen now.
What a dirty, rotten trick of fate.
We could have all that money
in our hands.
I must tell you the truth.
In my place, you would do the same thing.
It's all over for you now.
There's nothing anyone can do anymore.
God help me. It's my fault.
Mine, mine, mine.
I'll tell you one thing, Blondie.
If I knew that my last hour had come,
I swear...
in my place... in your place,
I would do the same thing.
I would tell about the gold. Yes, I would.
I'd tell the name on the grave.
After all, what good is
the money to you if you're dead?
I know the name of the cemetery,
but you know how many graves are there?
Please, Blondie.
Please, have a little, huh? Here. Coffee.
Please, tell me the name...
on the grave.
If I get my hands on the $200,000...
I'll always honor your memory.
I swear, I'll always honor your memory.
Come closer.
Tell me.
Why, you dirty...
I'll sleep better...
knowing my good friend is by my side...
to protect me.
"Tuco, water." Here's water.
But if I get that name from you,
I'll give you water.
All right, you dirty skunk,
get your ass off the bed.
Come on, the party's over.
The wagon is all ready to go.
From the way the wounded are pouring
into this place, we better leave...
before we get caught up in the war.
- Tuco, Father Ramirez is back.
- Yeah.
This is something I have to look into.
It'll only take a minute. Get moving.
- Where, this way?
- Yes.
Don't you recognize me?
It's me, Tuco. Let me embrace you.
I don't know the right thing.
I was just passing by here,
I said to myself...
"I wonder if my brother
remembers his brother."
Did I do wrong?
It doesn't matter. I'm very happy.
You have seen me, Tuco.
Yeah, well, I'm very glad I came.
Oh, my uniform!
It's a long story.
But let's talk about you.
It's more important. You look very well.
A bit thin, perhaps, but...
you were always thin, eh, Pablito?
What about our parents?
Only now do you think of them.
To begin after nine years.
Nine years?
So it's nine years. Nine years!
Our mother has been dead
a long time now.
Our father died only a few days ago.
That's why I was away.
He asked for you to be there,
but there was only me.
And you?
Outside of evil,
what else have you managed to do?
It seems to me
you once had a wife someplace.
Not one. Lots of them.
One here, one there,
wherever I found them.
Go on, preach me a sermon, Pablo.
What good would that be?
Just keep on the way you're going.
Go away.
- And the Lord have mercy on your soul.
- Sure, I'll go, I'll go.
While I'm waiting for the Lord
to remember me...
I, Tuco Ramirez,
brother of Brother Ramirez...
will tell you something.
You think you're better than I am.
Where we came from,
if one didn't want to die of poverty...
one became a priest or a bandit.
You chose your way, I chose mine.
Mine was harder!
You talk about Mother and Father.
You remember, when you left
to become a priest, I stayed behind.
I must have been ten, twelve.
I don't remember which, but I stayed.
I tried, but it was no good.
Now I will tell you something.
You became a priest because you were
too much of a coward to do what I do.
Tuco.
Please forgive me, brother.
Ah, my belly's full.
Nice guy, my brother.
I didn't tell you
my brother was in charge here?
Everything. Like the pope almost.
He's in charge in Rome.
Yeah, yeah, my brother, he say to me...
"Stay, brother. Don't go home.
We never see each other.
"Here there's plenty to eat and drink.
Bring your friend too."
Whenever we see each other, he never
lets me go. It's always the same story.
My brother... he is crazy about me.
That's so. Even a tramp like me,
no matter what happens...
I know there's a brother somewhere
who will never refuse me a bowl of soup.
Sure.
Well, after a meal,
there's nothing like a good cigar.
Here's the Sierra Magdalena.
Going this way, we cross the Rio Grande.
That sure is a long way.
Here to the northwest,
through all of Texas...
- After that...
- Then what?
When we get there, I'll tell you.
You're not worried, are you?
Those men aren't worried
about anything anymore, are they?
But since I'm alive and I've noticed
we'll be crossing Yankee and
Confederate lines a few times.
I thought you might tell me
where we're going.
Towards $200,000.
Is that good enough for you?
Whoa.
Hey, wake up, you.
- The troops are coming. Come on.
- Blue or gray?
They're gray like us. Let's say
"hello" to them and then get going.
Hoorah! Hoorah for the Confederacy!
Hoorah! Down with General Grant!
- Hoorah for General... what's his name?
- Lee.
Lee!
God is with us
because He hates the Yanks too!
God's not on our side
'cause He hates idiots also.
Hut, two, three, four.
Prisoners of war, forward!
March!
Halt!
Left face!
Form a single file. Move!
- Jonathan Frost!
- Present!
- Richard McGilley!
- Nathaniel Sullivan!
- Present.
- Robert Clark!
- Sam Richmond!
- Present.
Bill Carson.
I said Bill Carson!
Hey, Blondie, isn't that Angel Eyes?
All right, what's he doing, sleeping?
Yeah, and you better be Bill Carson.
Bill Carson!
Yeah, that's me.
Please, Carson...
answer "present."
What are you, deaf?
Now suppose you say "present," Carson.
I like big fat men like you.
When they fall, they make more noise...
and sometimes they never get up.
Wallace...
that's enough.
Sergeant!
The captain wants to see you right away.
Be sure these two get good treatment.
Hey, Blondie, did you hear that?
Good treatment.
Yeah.
For the last time, Sergeant...
I'm telling you, I want the prisoners
treated as prisoners.
No more brutality.
There's hundreds of prisoners out there
and only a few men to guard them.
Now what am I supposed to do?
I have to have respect.
I think that you'll manage to gain
their respect by treating them better.
Are our men treated that well
in Andersonville camp?
I don't give a goddamn
what they do in Andersonville.
While I'm in charge here,
the prisoners are not to be tortured...
or cheated or murdered.
That an accusation?
Sergeant, gangrene is eating
my leg away, not my eyes.
I know the prisoners here
are being robbed systematically.
I know there's scum around
who are bivouacked near the camp...
waiting for someone to deliver this loot.
But as long as I'm commandant, I won't
permit any such trickery. Am I clear?
Yes, sir...
just as long as you're the commandant.
Yes, Sergeant.
I know this leg means
I won't last very long...
but I pray I can manage to have
enough time to amass evidence...
and bring to a court-martial...
all those who discredit and dishonor...
the uniform of the Union.
I wish you luck.
You and the others better lay low
for a few days.
No, I'll keep this. You go.
Wallace will let you know.
- Bring me Carson.
- Right.
Listen, Angel Eyes said
for us to lay low for a few days...
but we'll keep close enough
to keep an eye on things.
Come on, saddle your horses.
Get in.
Come on in, Tuco. Don't be bashful.
There's no formalities here.
It's been a long time.
You're hungry. Sit down, eat.
I knew it, I knew it.
The minute I saw you, I said to myself...
"Look at that pig, Angel Eyes.
"I'll bet he got himself an easy job...
"and he never forgets a friend."
I never forget old friends, Tuco.
- Right.
- It's good to see old friends again.
Good.
Especially when they've come
from so far away...
and have so much to talk about.
And you do have a lot
to talk about, haven't you?
You were captured near Fort Craig.
Well, if you were with Sibley,
that means then that you...
were coming from Santa Fe.
- Was it hard crossing the desert?
- Very hard.
Especially if you don't have
anything to drink.
Why are you going under the name
of Bill Carson now?
One name is as good as another.
Not wise to use your own name.
Like you. I'll bet
they don't call you Angel Eyes.
Sergeant Angel Eyes.
Like a little music with your meal, Tuco?
Music? Yes, it's very good...
very good for the digestion.
So...
Bill Carson's a fake name, huh?
That fake too?
Bill Carson's name's written in it.
Have some. It's Bill Carson's tobacco.
More feeling.
Was Carson dead or alive
when you found him?
What'd he tell you about the money?
I don't...
I don't know what you're talking about.
How's your digestion now?
You'd better talk.
I have nothing to tell you.
Play that fiddle, you!
You can sure consider yourself
much luckier than your pal.
Wallace will punch your friend
as long as the song goes.
So many of us have had a session in there.
Enough. Enough. I talk. I talk.
What did he say about the money?
It's buried in a grave.
- Where?
- Sad Hill...
Sad Hill Cemetery.
Which grave?
I don't know. I don't know, I tell you.
Ask Blondie.
He knows the name on the grave.
Put those clothes on.
- Why?
- We're going for a ride.
- Where?
- To find $200,000.
I know the name of the cemetery now...
and you know the name of the grave.
You're not gonna give me
the same treatment?
Would you talk?
No, probably not.
That's what I thought.
Not that you're any tougher than Tuco...
but you're smart enough to know
that talking won't save you.
And Tuco... is he...
Not yet.
But he's in very good hands.
You've changed partners,
but you still got the same deal.
I'm not greedy. I'm only taking half.
There's two of us. it should
make it easier than just one.
Yeah.
Hold it. That's it, don't move.
Now don't breathe. Still. That's it.
Got it. Thank you.
Hey, Corporal, afraid he'll get lost?
Where's the rebel going?
To hell, with a rope around his neck
and a price on his head.
$3,000, friend.
That's a lot of money for a head.
I'll bet they didn't even pay you
a penny for your arm.
I told you once, friend,
if I ever get you down...
you're gonna need a lot of help
to get up again.
You're a lot luckier than that one.
Grub, a rope, and you're all finished.
And there isn't any partner this time to
shoot you down.
If your friends stay out in the damp,
they're liable to catch a cold,
aren't they?
Or a bullet.
Hear that, boys? Come on out here.
Since we're all going in the same
direction, might as well go together.
One, two, three, four,
five, six.
Six... Perfect number.
Isn't three the perfect number?
Yeah. But I got six more bullets in my gun.
Sure would like to put
your paw on it, huh?
I would like to piss. It's rough.
I've been shaken up on this train
nearly ten hours now.
You smell like a pig already...
but let's not try to make things any worse.
Get going.
I can't while you're watching me.
You made a lot of noise, my friend, huh?
You don't want to break our friendship,
huh? Well, I'll break it.
Halt.
Take your places.
Ready!
Aim! Fire!
Slim, take care of the horses.
I've been looking for you for eight months.
Whenever I should've had a gun
in my right hand, I thought of you.
Now I find you in exactly
the position that suits me.
I had lots of time to learn
how to shoot with my left.
When you have to shoot, shoot. Don't talk.
Every gun makes its own tune.
It's perfect timing, Large One.
Clem, follow him.
Just a minute. I'll be right there.
Just give me a little time
to get dressed, and I'll open up.
Put your drawers on and take your gun off.
How the hell did you get out
of that pigsty?
My own way. I'm here
with your old friend, Angel Eyes.
You talked, you traitor. You talked.
No, I didn't talk.
If I did, I probably wouldn't be here now.
You, me...
So only you know your half of the secret?
I'm very happy you're working with me...
and we're together again.
I get dressed,
I kill him and be right back.
Oh, listen...
I forgot to mention...
He's not alone. There's five of them.
- Five?
- Yeah, five of them.
So that's why you came to Tuco?
It doesn't matter. I'll kill them all.
They shot him at close range.
Well, look who's here.
The other one will be along.
They'll come looking for us.
Watch out.
There's two of them.
I want that blond alive.
You, back there. Come on, let's go.
Were you gonna die alone?
Halt!
- Angel Eyes is mine, huh?
- All right.
"See you soon..."
"Idiots."
It's for you.
How peaceful and quiet, amigo.
Like a cemetery, for instance?
There should be a bridge across that river.
- We'd better wait for nightfall.
- Trust in me, Blondie.
I got a good sense of where I'm going.
Tuco has taken you this far.
I will take you all the way...
Gentlemen.
- Tell the captain.
- Yes, sir.
Come along now. Follow me.
We found them near the perimeter, sir.
- Where do you hail from?
- Illinois.
- And you?
- I'm with him.
Any reason for being around here?
We want to enlist, General.
You better learn to distinguish rank.
I'm a captain.
Get the hell out.
It sure as hell might be you today,
so go write your will.
Yes, sir.
So you want to enlist?
You gotta take a test to prove it.
Well, show me.
You've got a career. At the least,
I'd say you'll make colonel.
- Really?
- Sure.
Like it says in the manual...
"You've got every qualification...
"to become an expert
in the use of weapons."
For this, sir,
is the most potent weapon in war.
The fighting spirit's in this bottle.
Volunteers.
You want to enlist, hmm?
Let's go.
Come on, gentlemen. Come on.
The shooting hasn't begun yet.
You're still in time.
Whoever has the most liquor
to get the soldiers drunk
and send them to be slaughtered...
is the winner.
We and the ones over on the other side of
the river only have one thing in common.
All of us reek of alcohol.
What did you say your name was?
And you?
No.
Names don't matter.
Yes, because soon you can join
the gallant heroes of Branson Bridge.
- We have two attacks a day.
- Two attacks a day?
Sure, the Rebs have decided
that damn bridge...
is the key to this whole area.
Stupid, useless bridge.
Flyspeck on headquarters' maps.
And headquarters has declared
we must take that ridiculous flyspeck...
even if all of us are killed.
Otherwise, the key will get rusty...
and just be a spot on the wall.
And that's not all.
Both sides want the bridge intact.
Intact is how the South wants it...
and we want it intact too.
You'll all turn to dust...
but one thing is sure, boys:
Branson Bridge will stand unbroken.
Is it bad to speak the way I do
to volunteers?
I've done a lot worse.
I've done it. I've blown it up. Boom!
In here, I've destroyed it all.
It's a court-martial offense to imagine...
to dream of blowing it up...
a serious crime.
Even to think of destroying
that bridge is just...
Why not really blow it up, Captain?
Yeah, Captain, it's nothing.
Let's scare the hell out of them.
I've been dreaming about it.
I've even worked out a plan.
I sure have.
The best time is after the attack...
when there's a truce to get the wounded.
If I could do it...
I could save many thousands of men.
But what I lack is the guts.
They're beginning their daily slaughter
right on time.
Captain, all companies
are awaiting your orders.
Be right there.
Let's go.
All right, friends...
come along and enjoy the spectacle.
Companies, report!
Company B ready!
Company E ready!
Company D ready!
Companies, forward!
It looks like the captain is
really asking for a bullet in his guts.
Yeah.
I've never seen so many men
wasted so badly.
I have a feeling it's really
gonna be a good long battle.
- Blondie?
- Huh?
The money's on the other side of the river.
Where?
Amigo, I said the other side,
and that's enough.
But while the Confederates are there,
we can't get across.
What would happen if somebody were
to blow up that bridge?
Yeah.
Then these idiots would go
somewhere else to fight.
Maybe.
Doctor, quick, the captain's wounded.
Hurry, a stretcher.
Easy. Easy now.
Get things ready.
A little of this will help.
Take a slug of this, Captain.
Keep your ears open.
What are you doing? No, leave me alone.
You realize we might be risking our lives.
Yeah, and if I get killed...
you'll never get your hands
on all that beautiful money.
Yeah, Tuco...
it sure would be a pity.
Doc.
Doctor...
could you help me live a little more?
I expect good news.
Why don't we tell each other
our half of the secret?
- Why don't we?
- Huh? You go first.
No, I think it's better that...
you start.
All right.
The name of the cemetery is...
Sad Hill. Now it's your turn.
The name on the grave is...
Arch Stanton.
Arch Stanton? Are you sure?
Yeah, sure, I'm sure.
It'll be a lot easier with that.
Two can dig a lot quicker than one.
Dig.
You're not digging.
If you shoot me,
you won't see a cent of that money.
Why?
I'll tell you why.
'Cause there's nothing in there.
Why, you son of a...
You thought I'd trust you?
$200,000 is a lot of money.
We're gonna have to earn it.
How?
I'll write the name
on the bottom of this stone.
The gun.
You pig. You want to get me killed?
When'd you unload it?
Last night.
You see, in this world, there's
two kinds of people, my friend...
those with loaded guns...
and those who dig.
- You dig.
- Where?
Here.
There's no name on it!
There's no name here either.
You see, that's what Bill Carson told me.
It was the grave marked "Unknown"...
right beside Arch Stanton.
Go ahead.
Blondie! It's all ours, Blondie!
You're joking, Blondie. You wouldn't
play a joke on me like that.
It's no joke. It's a rope, Tuco.
Now I want you to stand up there
and put your head in that noose.
Well, now, seems just like old times.
Four for you...
and four...
four for me.
Blondie!
Hey, Blondie!
You know what you are?
Just a dirty son of a bitch!
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org