Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Over here! Help!
Quick, hurry!
Hurry up! This way!
Hurry!
- Ma'am. Ma'am?
- What's wrong with her?
We don't know yet, son.
Pinpoint pupils.
Do you know what kind of drugs
she was taking?
- Resp in the toilet. You wanna intubate?
- No, let's bag her first.
Go ahead. Give it to her.
Is she dead?
Hey, Eddie, you got any Oxy?
No Oxy. Got some H, though.
- I don't want that shit.
- Well, suit yourself.
Wait.
Fly safe.
Eddie, what's up?
- Hey, man.
- Wanna hit it?
Nah, I'm good, man.
- How much?
- Half-load.
- Ooh! Business been good.
- Fuck, yeah.
- What you do with your profits?
- Shit, I don't know, man.
- Spending it.
- You smart, you get in the market.
I got a broker. I can hook you up.
- No, I think I'm good, man.
- You sure?
- Yeah, dude. I gotta run. Marco.
- Hey.
- Fuck, yeah.
- What?
My broker told me
to short Weight Watchers,
and it just went down 12%.
You got a broker?
You gotta clean your money somehow, man.
- Hey, look, I'll send you his email.
- Okay.
Yeah, baby!
- It's party time!
- Hit it!
Morning, ladies.
- We ready?
- Mm-hmm.
Looking good.
Call the Mexicans.
Enlighten my eyes...
or I shall sleep the sleep of death.
Hey, Zeke.
Want some eggs?
Hey.
Marty.
No, thank you.
Some coffee would be great,
though, please.
How long is he staying with us?
Just until they can find
a suitable home for him.
So, people just give us
babies indefinitely?
- What, like we're such the model family?
- Okay.
Easy on the sarcasm. We told you.
Mason asked us to help him out.
Where you goin'?
Wyatt's.
I thought Ruth told you
to stay away from him.
I don't care.
In case you've forgotten, it was Wyatt
that got expelled for protecting Jonah.
- That's not our fault.
- Bullshit.
- Hey.
- Jonah didn't get expelled.
They threw out Wyatt
because he's a Langmore.
I suppose you think that that's fair.
Well, none of it's fair.
Jonah, would you take the baby
in the other room?
I wanna talk to your father.
Come on, buddy.
Did you get any sleep?
She's right about Wyatt, you know?
Well, we have other problems.
Beecher's report to the commission.
It's as bad as we expected.
Marty, we've gotta get ahead of this,
or else the casino's
gonna go down in flames.
What do you wanna do?
Wilkes isn't returning my calls.
You know, I used to think
that we were, uh, different than them.
You know, these people that we work for.
And, um...
Hey.
We are different from them.
You saved my life.
Mason would've killed me otherwise.
And you are the one who has always said,
"People make choices."
Mason's wife didn't have a choice.
Our kids, they didn't have a choice.
Okay, well, we have to concentrate
on the casino.
So, I am going to go see Wilkes.
- Hello.
- Can you look after the baby
while I'm gone?
Jesus, is she dead?
I'll be right there.
What?
Rachel OD'd.
I gotta go.
I just wanted to thank you
for what you did.
I know you didn't sign up for this.
It's all been a nightmare.
Pretty weird kidnapping
when the victim gets to keep the ransom.
He gave it to us.
He was going on the run, and he knew
he couldn't take care of the baby.
I have no idea whether
to believe you or not.
- I'm sorry you feel that way.
- Yeah.
Have you heard about the Beecher letter?
Oh, yeah, I heard about it.
The casino's doomed.
The commission will never approve it.
- Unless you interceded.
- Yeah.
Nope, can't do it.
- Can't or won't?
- It's too late.
What about your offer?
Is it still on the table?
- Come on, Wendy.
- No, I'm serious.
You would leave Marty?
If it kept him safe. Him and the kids.
You said you'd do anything
to get that final vote on the casino.
I always wondered if you were lying.
Try me.
It's gone too far.
Are you wearing a wire?
Fuck you.
The EMTs took it off me.
Okay.
I didn't know you were using.
Yeah, well, it's not your problem.
I'm not a fucking junkie,
so don't worry about it.
Nix said that he thought
that the dope was spiked.
So?
So, it's not your fault, okay?
None of it is.
I'm really sorry
that I got you involved in all of this.
Yeah, well, no offense, Marty,
but that don't really mean shit.
You're right.
You know, when I first came-to,
I was relieved.
I was like...
"Well, that's good. I didn't die."
Then I was like...
"What the fuck now?"
Hey.
What if I can get you out?
The cartel doesn't know about you.
I don't know. I'm just really tired.
I know. I know.
Then let me help.
I can't fuck it up any worse.
That's the hearse Wendy was driving in.
They could've moved that dough anywhere.
You think you can handle
that Keebler Elf-looking motherfucker?
Only one way to find out.
- Hi, Harry.
- Ruth, hi.
You here for the invoices?
No, I actually need to talk to you
about something.
Come on in.
Um, it's kind of weird.
Weird?
Well, confidential-like.
Oh. Do tell.
Do you like what you do, Harry?
I never wanted to be anything else. Why?
Well...
you know, I work in the strip club, and...
I've just been thinking
about job security.
I mean, that's not something
I really wanna do for the rest of my life.
Not like what you do.
Well, that's the thing about our business.
You never run out of customers.
To tell the truth,
not everyone has the stomach for it.
I got a pretty strong fucking stomach.
Pardon my French.
Why don't you come back with me?
I'll show you what we do. Come on.
What's the line?
Eagles and three?
No, fuck the spread.
I told you before,
I'll tell you again, man.
They just a fluke.
Yeah, let me get three large
on the Browns.
FBI! Everybody down!
Don't move!
Don't move! Don't move!
- Hands! Freeze! Drop it!
- Put your hands up.
The latest update is 22 fatalities,
seven more in critical condition.
Fentanyl mixed with heroin.
Upstairs is getting their asses kicked.
No one cared as long as the minority
communities were the ones dying,
but once it hit Northwestern...
Do we have a source yet?
We're rolling up as many
mid-level and street dealers as we can.
The ODs seem to be limited
to the Navarro Cartel's territory.
With all due respect,
it doesn't sound like Navarro.
For all you who haven't had the pleasure,
this is Agent Petty.
He's been undercover down in Lake Ozark
for the past few months,
that is, until one of his informants
blew his cover.
Our theory is they're amping the dope
with fentanyl.
Maybe they overdid it.
Got a better idea?
Look at it epidemiologically.
If the tainted drugs were
from the Navarro Cartel,
we'd see a spike in ODs in Chicago,
Milwaukee, Detroit,
Cleveland and Indianapolis,
because Chicago's the hub.
But right now, we have a spike in ODs
in only two places:
Chicago and the Ozarks,
which indicates two things.
The contaminated drugs are a small batch,
and the drugs came
from the Ozarks to Chicago.
Okay.
Find the connection.
You can tell a lot
about a guest...
I call them guests.
When you're working on them.
Did they drink? Were they fit?
I can even tell you their station in life.
Like this guy.
Had his teeth straightened.
Family probably had money.
Oh, my God.
The smell of formaldehyde.
The funny thing is people are scared
of the dead, and they shouldn't be.
It's the living who can hurt you.
- We don't do that.
- Sorry.
Is there a bathroom I can use?
Stomach not as strong as
you thought?
Come on. I'll show you.
What's in here?
That's a storage room.
Just some surplus caskets.
Bathroom's just down the hall.
I appreciate you bailing me out,
Ms. Pierce.
I'll pay you back every penny
just as soon as
we get back up and rolling.
I know you will, Amos.
I don't know what happened, man.
It seemed like the feds was everywhere.
Come on. We'll give you a ride home.
I really appreciate it,
but, uh, I can just catch me an Uber.
It's no problem. It's on our way.
You can't save the world, Marty.
I'm not trying to.
I told Rachel that I'm gonna help her
get out from under Petty.
Jesus.
- How are you gonna do that?
- I don't know yet.
You're a good man, Marty. You are.
But right now,
we need to get the casino over the hump,
and then we can make things right.
She almost died because of what we did.
Rachel almost died
because she's a drug addict.
She stole from us. She informed on us.
She wore a wire.
At what point is any of that our fault?
Is there something I need to know
about you and Rachel?
Mom, Dad.
Sheriff Nix, this is a surprise.
Mrs. Byrde. Marty.
I'm sorry to stop by so late,
but I needed to ask you some questions
about Mason Young.
Thank you, Charlotte.
Can I get you some coffee?
Or maybe some tea, or...
No, I won't be long.
Social services is looking for Mason.
It seems like he's disappeared.
- Oh, dear.
- Disappeared, huh?
He hasn't answered his phone,
and no one's seen him.
So, I thought I would check with you,
see if you knew anything.
Well, we were contacted
by social services about the baby,
but we actually hadn't spoken
to Mason in months.
See, it just seems a hair strange
that you end up with his child,
and then he goes missing.
Yeah, well, uh...
Actually, I think
it was probably the reverse.
He must've gone missing
after social services took the baby
into custody.
So, you think he might've
done himself some harm?
We know how much he loved that baby.
- Yeah.
- Which is why we wanted to get the boy
out of the system as quickly as possible.
We've been waiting to hear from Mason.
You didn't try to reach him?
We went up to Jeff City looking for him,
but he wasn't on his regular corner.
Mm-hmm.
Why not just call him?
We didn't have his new number.
Hmm.
You know...
you might wanna talk to the Snells.
You know they have a relationship.
Yeah, I may have to do that.
You know, the Snells and I,
we go back a long way.
But everything has its limit.
Thank you for your time.
You'll let me know if you hear from Mason?
- Of course.
- All right. Good night now.
Why are you asking me this?
I don't know, Amos.
Maybe because most of the ODs were
on your turf.
I don't know nothing about it. Any of it.
You cut our heroin with fentanyl.
You tampered with our product,
and now people are dying.
I didn't. I wouldn't!
We don't wanna do this.
But we are going to find out,
one way or another.
Make it easy on yourself.
- What did you do to the drugs?
- Nothing.
There's still some hidden
in the body shop.
It's wrapped in that plastic.
That's the way it came.
Okay.
I lost money on the market,
so I hit the dope.
But only with inert stuff.
Fentanyl?
No fucking way, I swear to God.
I only used B12,
and who's that gonna hurt, huh?
I appreciate your honesty, Amos.
And don't worry. It's all over now.
I saw Susan Blake today.
Her husband kept a file on Wilkes.
He's over-leveraged.
He's using his charity
as his own personal account.
Now, I have a plan, but I need your help.
Did you hear me?
I wanted to tell Nix the truth
about Mason,
just to get it over with.
That would have been a very bad idea.
Well, I didn't say I was going to.
I just wanted to.
So, why are we here, Marty?
EMTs found a wire on Rachel.
I know she was working with you.
And?
She's worthless to you now.
It's kind of touching,
the way you care about her.
I mean, she was trying to put you away.
She almost died last night.
I'm asking you as a human being
to let her go.
You work for one of the most
vicious cartels in the world,
and you're talking to me
about being human?
Rachel isn't a criminal.
Does your wife know
about your feelings for Rachel?
Do your superiors know
that you were supplying drugs to Rachel?
Just so we're clear, the drugs she OD'd on
came from your business partners.
But I might be willing
to let her off the hook, if...
If?
I want the Snells' operation.
The Snells are our partners in the casino.
I'm not aware of an operation.
We think the Snells poisoned
the cartel's dope.
Maybe this marriage of convenience
became inconvenient.
But once the cartel figures it out,
it doesn't bode well
for their partnership.
So... if you really care about Rachel,
you're gonna have to choose sides, Marty.
What are you doing down here?
I like it here.
- Is the baby asleep?
- Finally.
Is that homework?
- Do you know what gamer currency is?
- Mnh-mnh.
Cyber criminals use it to launder money.
I could do this.
We're not looking to get into more crime,
sweetheart. We're trying to get out of it.
But let me ask you a question.
The account you were using,
Mike Fleming's...
How did you open that
without an adult's permission?
Well, I looked into some local banks,
and there was one small one
that failed the stress test a few times.
Not enough capital,
so I figured they wouldn't look
too closely into a kid's account.
So, hypothetically speaking, um...
I mean, would it be possible to open
an offshore account with that?
- You wanna launder money through it?
- No. No, no, no. No, of course not.
I'm just wondering if it's possible.
I've already done it, Mom.
So, if I wanted to disguise the source
of some funds...
I can do it.
Just this once.
You going somewhere?
Yeah, I'm going home.
I'll give you a ride.
I'll take a cab.
You outed yourself to Marty, didn't you?
You really think he's gonna rescue you?
Maybe he will.
You're not going home.
You're being detained until I can
extradite you back to Louisiana, so...
You still belong to me.
Hi. I didn't know you had a key.
We don't.
You should've called.
I would've met you here.
No need.
I just wanted to talk about the accounts.
I send you statements.
Hmm. We're kinda like the US government.
Trust, but verify.
Like this $1.8 million withdrawal
from the construction account made today
caught my attention.
Um...
Right. Yeah, $1.8.
That seems a little odd.
We haven't started building yet.
We have infrastructure costs.
Gas and water and power.
We gotta get it all up there.
And, uh, we, uh... We took out a loan
to get things rolling.
Today was the due date.
Okay.
I just don't want you
to confuse our money with yours.
So from now on, all expenditures
over $50,000 get run by me.
Okay.
Uh... understood.
Anything else?
- The Snells.
- What about them?
They spiked our dope with fentanyl.
The feds are up our asses.
My client is furious with them.
And?
The cartel's gonna do
what the cartel does.
The casino is on their land.
The casino is gonna get built,
with or without them.
- Helen, that's gonna be a huge problem.
- Your problem, Marty.
I'm an accountant. I move numbers around.
I'm a lawyer. I move words around.
There are no victims here.
Just volunteers, right?
Following a teacher walkout
that began ten days ago,
state lawmakers finally passed
a new education budget bill
providing, on average,
a $3,000 raise for teachers statewide.
The strike ends amid a wave
of teacher protests throughout the state,
as reduced education...
I tried reaching you. I made dinner.
Helen Pierce, um, was curious today
as to why $1.8 million was missing
from the construction account.
I was gonna tell you when you got home.
Okay, I'm home.
I had to put something in motion
on Wilkes. I had to move fast.
Did it not occur to you
to ask me first, Wendy?
I did.
I asked for your help.
You were more interested in Rachel.
Okay, that ground
feels a little shaky to me.
Look, we're gonna get most
of the money back,
if that's what you're worried about.
Do you not know
what happens to people who skim?
This is not skimming.
This is me trying to make sure
that we build a fucking casino
for the fucking cartel,
so that we all don't get killed.
Now, you wanna second-guess me,
go right ahead.
What I want is to not be blindsided...
...by having $1.8 million
just mysteriously disappear.
You know what?
Since Mason, your priorities have been
completely upside down.
Well, you seem completely unaffected
by what happened. How about that?
I'm the one he kidnapped!
I'm the one who he threatened to kill,
so don't you fucking tell me what I feel.
Do you know what? Just...
You take care of the baby.
I'm gonna go get some sleep.
Is something bothering you?
As a matter of fact, there is.
Should I make you some cocoa?
It was you, wasn't it?
You spiked the product.
What if I did?
You know how many people you've hurt?
Ugh!
Some junkies who were killing themselves
with dope succeeded.
So what? This is about respect.
The cartel thought
they could roll right over us.
Well, they don't anymore.
I think you misconstrue the situation.
I told you not to get involved with them.
I don't answer to you, Darlene.
I think you misconstrue the situation.
They'll come after us.
There'll be a war.
We've had to fight before.
I am not afraid. Are you?
Yes, I am. I am afraid.
Of you...
and your implacable rage.
Your rashness.
You killed Ash...
for no reason.
For money, for a casino.
I killed him to save you.
I guess we just see things differently.
Hey.
You okay?
Morning.
Hello, Ruth.
What the fuck is it now?
You already kicked out Wyatt.
- Please sit down.
- You kicking out Three, too?
- What, you get a family rate?
- I guess they didn't tell you.
This school has had it in
for the Langmores
- since my daddy's been here.
- This has nothing to do with Three.
Wyatt is a good kid.
Did you even read his application essay
for Mizzou?
He's smart.
He ain't like the rest of us.
I mean, he can go somewhere.
We're letting him back in, Ruth.
What?
Assuming there are no further incidents,
we're rescinding the expulsion.
A benefactor made a very eloquent case
on his behalf.
- Who?
- Well, I can't tell you.
He prefers it that way.
Make sure Wyatt's back on Monday.
Okay.
Hey, boss.
What's up?
Well, some interesting news.
Looks like the right-to-work initiative's
gonna make it on the ballot.
Mmm! About time.
And a lot of pushback from the unions,
big surprise.
And a $1.8 million donation was made
to the foundation.
- That's generous.
- Yeah, with some strings.
Half goes to the Wilkes Foundation,
a third passes through
to the Blake Foundation,
and the rest goes
to some hurricane victims charity.
600K to Blake?
- That's close to the amount we owe them.
- I know.
- It smells a little.
- Who's the donor?
- It's an anonymous gift.
- That's even worse.
Before you accept it,
you better find out
who the hell anonymous is.
Yeah.
Whoa!
They've got a ton of first editions.
Look Homeward, Angel.
That's, like, probably
my favorite American novel ever.
Excuse me.
Could you unlock that case for me? Thanks.
Just be careful. These are worth a lot.
- Thanks.
- Thank you.
You're welcome.
Wow!
Thomas Wolfe, huge guy. Like, 6'6".
But he liked to write standing up.
So, he would stand at his refrigerator
and use it as a desk.
Crazy.
Ruth, what's up?
Yeah.
Okay, what's that mean?
Okay.
Did she tell you who?
All right. Love you. Bye.
I got back into school.
- What?
- Yeah.
Well, that's cool.
What happened?
I don't know.
Ruth just said she talked to Abbott.
She said someone came in
and made my case for me,
and I go back on Monday.
Hey, do you think it was Marty?
I don't know.
You think he felt guilty about my dad?
About what happened?
I'm not sure I know
who my parents are anymore.
Bet you were a teacher's pet.
Straight-A student. Sat in the front row.
Hair combed. Hand up first.
Yeah, you'd lose that bet.
I, um... I spent fifth grade in the hall.
I kept correcting the teacher's spelling.
She never appreciated it.
You always thought you were
the smartest one in the room, huh?
Some rooms are smarter than others.
You got Wyatt back into school,
didn't you?
It didn't seem fair.
Like being tossed out of the classroom
for knowing more than the teacher?
Listen, um...
I... I should've protected you
from the cartel.
I know it doesn't mean much,
but I blame myself.
You should.
I want my office back.
Anything else?
It's a start.
Turn off the lights when you leave.
You bought that?
Not exactly.
What did you do?
What does it matter? It's yours.
I don't want it.
Why? What's wrong?
You just don't get it.
It's like what happened at school.
If you get caught,
you get a slap on the wrist.
Marty pays for the book.
I get caught, I go to fucking jail.
You liked it so much,
and I wanted to get it for you, so...
I just got back into school,
for Christ's sake.
- I thought you hated school.
- I...
That's not what I said, Charlotte.
- I'm sorry, okay? It was stupid.
- No...
You just don't understand
who my family is, okay?
The shit that they've done,
it's like I can't escape it.
Oh, Jesus, you think you're the only one?
I saw a guy get killed in my house.
I loaded money into a wall.
The fucking FBI raided us.
My parents are paranoid
about anyone I hang out with.
And now we have a baby,
and I know they're lying
about how they got it.
A fucking baby!
It's all just so fucked up.
Why would you do that?
Do you have any idea
how much that's worth?
Charlotte, will you let your brother know
that dinner's ready, please?
Jonah!
That's great. I could have done that.
Take a seat, sweetheart.
Sorry, I was just finishing up.
What were you finishing up?
Jonah is...
um, creating an online profile...
for Mike Fleming.
What does that mean?
We're using his account,
only temporarily.
The Blake Foundation
is having a benefit tomorrow night,
and we'll see if Wilkes bites.
You didn't need to ask Jonah.
It was an emergency, and you were busy.
What'd you do today, Charlotte?
I stole a book.
- You what?
- You stole a book?
A first edition of Look Homeward, Angel,
from an antiquarian bookstore.
Why would you do that?
I don't know.
Because I'm a Byrde and that's what we do.
Then you return it.
- It's too late. I gave it to someone.
- Then you need to pay them for it.
You don't steal things from a store.
You know that.
This is insane. You see that, right?
Charlotte. Charlotte!
Hi, Helen.
I got the link you sent
and did some digging.
Check your inbox. I think you'll be happy.
- Yeah?
- It's me. I wake you?
- What do you think?
- Yeah, say hello to Sherry.
- She finish your taxes yet?
- Fuck off.
What do you want?
Well, I paid off a teller at the bank
that made the wire transfer.
The name of the anonymous benefactor
is Michael Fleming.
Michael... Never heard of him.
That's because he's a 14-year-old boy.
What?
Evidently, his father died
and left him a foundation.
They need to make some bequests
for tax reasons.
Hello.
I'm here.
What do you want me to do?
- If I had more time...
- It's fine.
The world needs a little bit more trust.
Just accept it. Accept the money.
There's not much to like
about the Ozarks, but, man...
This French toast is...
I think it's the fresh buttermilk.
You gonna give me the details
of the Snell operation,
or are you on your way out?
You're a fucking angel.
I needed a fix, and there you were.
How did you know who I was?
I'm a friend of your son's.
You want me to tie you off?
- Oh, yeah. Yeah.
- Yeah.
You're a fucking angel.
Angel.
I will fucking kill you.
No, you won't.
Not if you care about your mother.
You're gonna let Rachel go,
and you're gonna drop all pending charges.
If she gets so much as a parking ticket...
You proud of yourself?
Threatening a sick woman?
No.
Not for a second.
Hello, Charlie.
I didn't know you had an eye for art.
I don't. It's a commodity,
like everything else. Should I buy it?
It's better than hog futures,
and it's for a good cause.
Mind if I borrow your date?
As long as you return him
in the same condition.
What are you doing here?
I heard you finally made good
on your donation.
- Yeah? Where'd you hear that?
- Susan Blake.
Oh, you're friends now?
- We have mutual interests.
- Like what?
Like making sure promises are lived up to.
Are you trying to tell me something?
Marty and I facilitated the donation
from Mike Fleming to you.
My position has not changed on the casino.
I am still out.
I assumed.
Unfortunately, you just accepted
Mexican drug cartel money
and helped launder it
through a Guyanese charity.
That is just not a good look
for a moralist like you.
We had no idea where that money came from.
I'm not so sure
the FBI will see it that way.
And once they start looking into
how you use your own charity
as your own personal piggy bank,
well, I guess you're looking at
tax evasion,
wire fraud, money laundering...
- You fucking set me up?
- Hey.
Take a drink, Charlie.
Smile. People are watching.
You try and take me down,
believe me,
I take you and Marty down with me.
I don't doubt that for a second,
but there's a less painful way out
of this,
one where you get to keep the donation,
recoupable against your piece
of the profits,
and we get the casino.
Just help us get through the commission.
You are one cold-hearted bitch.
Let's go.
Camera to the left.
Oh, shit.
Fuck.
God damn it. Fuck.
Fuck!
Where is it?
Maybe I just got it wrong.
You're always wrong
when it comes to Marty fucking Byrde.
You are like a fucking dog,
going to whoever feeds you.
I saw the hearse. It has to be here.
Yeah? And when was that?
- How long you been holding out?
- I'm not holding out.
You been leading me on this
fucking goose chase for months now.
- Where the fuck's the money?
- I don't know!
You know what? You're worthless to me.
You're like a piece of shit
on the bottom of my shoe. Yeah.
Don't say that, Daddy.
You made me do it.
When are you gonna learn?
What, are you gonna cut me now?
You ungrateful fucking cunt.
What were you running from, Buddy?
Ghosts?
Were they in your dreams?
Did they forgive you?
Bye, Buddy.
I'll be seeing you.
Hey.
- Hi.
- Can I come in?
How do you feel?
Um, okay.
Good.
Petty is not going to be
bothering you anymore.
How'd you get me out?
He had a change of heart.
What's this?
That's a plane ticket.
To Miami?
There's a clinic there
where you can clean up.
I said I wanted to help,
and this is what it looks like.
Well, I can't even afford that, so...
It's paid for. It's done.
And this is an advance on the Blue Cat.
You send me your account information,
and I'll deposit the rest.
I guess I should say thank you.
No.
I fucked your life up pretty good.
Hey, Marty.
I, uh...
Thank you.
- Y'all take care.
- Appreciate it.
Wonderful sermon, Reverend.
The nature of salvation.
Gave me a lot to think about.
Thank you.
And that fried chicken.
It must be genetic.
Women around these parts
all just seem to know how to cook.
- Isn't that right, Darlene?
- Mmm.
Oh, it was good to see you, Darlene.
Well...
- good night now.
- Good night.
Jesus, it's just fucking fried chicken.
A cat could make it.
Thank you.
Y'all got a problem?
Where have you been?
It's late. We've been worried.
I have something
I wanna talk to you about.
What is it?
I wanna get emancipated.
- What are you talking about?
- What?
Do you remember Jordan Parks
from back home?
He did it. He had his own apartment
when he was a senior.
That kid's parents are drug addicts.
- There's a difference there.
- This is silly.
You'd have to pay for rent, food, clothes.
I'll get a job.
Where? McDonald's?
You think minimum wage
would pay for all that?
Charlotte, I know things have been crazy,
- but we gotta stay together.
- Why?
We're a family.
What does that even mean?
I don't wanna hurt you.
I love you,
but I can't be a part of this anymore.
Everyone lies about everything.
It's gone too far.
You can fight me on this,
or you can help me.
I've made up my mind.
I want out.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org