Ah, you know what?
Just remind me.
I got to write a thank-you note
to the guy who invented waffles.
The recipe first appeared
in Le Ménagier de Paris, a book
a husband wrote for his wife
in the 14th century.
Since he's dead,
a note would be pointless.
I pity the men who aren't
married to you, Bones.
Booth, did you see
what Christine brought home
from preschool?
Hey, look at
that, huh?
15th place winner
in an egg race. Huh.
Our little girl's
a champion.
Booth, there are only
15 children in the class.
What do you want me to do?
Get her a trainer
so we could work her harder?
If she's 15th,
that means that she lost.
Children need to understand
what losing means.
It's an egg race.
When I was a child,
I played blackjack with Max,
and he never let me win.
I lost my allowance,
but I got a realistic view
of the world.
Your dad took your allowance?
Won it. Actually,
he won the marker he gave me
that said he owed me the allowance.
I don't think
we should use your father as
an example here. It's not...
Oh. Brennan.
Okay, I'm on my way.
Wait. Wait. Wait a second.
What about the waffle I just made you?
Sorry.
A body's on its way to the lab.
More for you.
I'll call if it concerns you.
I got waffles flying
all over the place here.
That's hot. That's hot.
The remains are
in the pig troughs?
Yes. I am setting up
a filtration system
that will allow us to separate
liquid in the pig slop
from any human remains,
such as tissue,
bones, organs...
But you're not waiting.
I was told
the body was dumped
on a pig farm in Virginia.
Yeah.
So the noise of the pigs feeding
woke up the farmer,
so he was able to stop them
before they finished eating
all the human remains.
I need an intern.
Where's Oliver Wells?
Out of town on family business.
Dr. Brennan, Dr. Hodgins,
you remember Dr. Filmore?
It's our favorite Canadian
forensic podiatrist.
Hello, Dr. Hodgins.
Dr. Brennan, it's a pleasure
to be working with you again.
I'm afraid there will be
no pleasure, Dr. Filmore.
His field is forensic podiatry.
Dr. Filmore is writing a report
at the request
of the FBI
and the Royal Canadian
Mounted Police
on cooperation between
the United States and Canada
in the field of
forensic sciences.
It's the first trans-border
study in forensic cooperation
between our two
great nations.
No. I can't allow that.
We're in the middle
of an investigation.
Hmm.
What are you doing?
Notes for my report.
"Check American definition
of 'cooperation.'"
Dr. Filmore
will be your intern so he can
observe firsthand that
our definition
of cooperation is the same
as our neighbors to the north.
By his own admission,
he's familiar with only 25%
of the bones in the human body.
Actually, I just completed
my PhD in forensic anthropology,
so I am now fully qualified
to work with you...
as a peer.
Then that settles it.
Now, if you'll
excuse me.
Put on some gloves.
We're looking for human remains
in these troughs.
We might not be able to recover
a complete
skeleton because...
Because pigs eat human bones.
I grew up
on a farm in Manitoba.
Angela...
Oh, hey. I can't do anything
until I have a skull,
so I thought I'd just
create something alive.
Not why I'm here.
It's, uh...
Science Monthly
just contacted me
about their Outstanding Women
of Science issue.
Oh. Brennan again?
No. Me.
They want me this year.
Oh, my God!
Cam, that's fantastic!
Congratulations!
I should be happy,
but I just feel uncomfortable.
Brennan?
Yeah. She can sometimes feel...
I don't know how to say it.
That all awards
should go to her?
And I don't really care.
I could just
tell the magazine no.
Oh, no. Don't be ridiculous.
This is...
this is a huge honor,
and we're all going
to celebrate this,
including Brennan.
You have to
enjoy this.
Smile. You deserve it.
Aah. This will be easier.
So, the pump
creates suction
and delivers the contents
of the troughs into this
sluice box,
which will separate liquid
from particulates greater than
.03 millimeters.
Quite the impressive
contrivance, Dr. Hodgins.
Right? All right.
Here we go.
- Yeah!
- Oh!
It appears to working.
You know, this death
might just be an accident.
We had a farmhand
who fell into the trough after
drinking to excess.
The pigs must have
thought he was delicious,
because there was nothing left.
Well, considering
this person was
dismembered, I would
rule out an accident.
Yes.
Oh. Ah.
Dark brown hair.
Definitely human.
Well, the greater
sciatic notch indicates a male.
The auricular surface indicates
an age range
between 29 and 35.
Huh. A central incisor.
Not in any way connected
with the foot, of course.
This spatula shape indicates
the victim was Caucasian.
Told you it would work, huh?
Well,
it's not the filter.
Can you hold that?
Yes.
It's got to be
the hose.
Hey. Good news.
Cam got a call from
Science Monthly.
They announced this year's
Outstanding Women
of Science award.
Why did they call Cam?
Why didn't they just
call me directly?
Because Cam is getting
the award, sweetie.
Wow!
That's great.
Yes, I'm very happy for her.
And you're happy
for her, too, Brennan.
Very happy.
Because she's your friend.
Yes.
Just the-the descriptor
is "outstanding."
All right, we're all good to go.
You know, Science Monthly is
an exceptional mag...
Oh! My.
Don't move,
Dr. Filmore.
You're covered in evidence.
It's no problem.
Just like being
back on the farm.
Oh, here's a piece...
Thank you.
...that's important.
♪ Bones 9x14 ♪
The Master in the Slop
Original Air Date on January 24, 2014
♪ Main Title Theme ♪ The Crystal Method
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
♪
A foot!
A foot is not necessarily
the solution
to this forensic puzzle.
I see you haven't
lost your conviction
that you have
all the answers.
Well, I am outstanding
and without peer in my field.
I assume that is why
your government wanted
you to observe me.
What are you
writing now?
Oh, just an observation
that Americans are hubristic,
and Canadians must deal
with this challenge
in future cooperative ventures.
Facts are not
hubris, Dr. Filmore.
The left side of the frontal
bone, including the supraorbital
foramen, as well as the maxilla,
and the right zygomatic
are all missing.
Facial reconstruction would
prove difficult for Angela.
It appears there's a fracture
on the occipital,
and avulsion fractures
on the left mastoid process.
Confirming that
a hit and tear
from the occipital
to the mastoid
as a possible
cause of death.
Hey. So, the hair sample
carried traces
of beeswax and hempseed oil.
Think our victim had dreadlocks.
Victim had blonde hair.
That dark brown hair
could belong to the killer.
All right, well,
Cam's running a DNA
on both samples,
but I also found traces
of chestnuts
imbedded on
the victim's clothing.
You know,
at our farm,
when the pigs wouldn't eat,
my father used to sweeten
the slop with chestnuts.
So it's possible the killer
knew how to get the pigs
to devour the victim.
Yes.
Hey, Sweets,
got the DNA results
from the hair the squints found
in the pig slop.
Jarrick Henry.
Who?
Oh, right.
He's the guy who fed
his victim to pigs,
right? Nice fella.
Yeah, and with no body,
the lawyer got an acquittal.
Didn't think
he'd pull that M.O. twice.
You mean feed another
victim to pigs?
He's a high-risk
repeat offender.
He got away with it once.
Probably figured he could
get away with it again.
You felt the honor
from Science Monthly
should go to you, eh?
It's called "Outstanding
Women of Science."
I have the utmost
respect for Dr. Saroyan.
I can only surmise the editorial
staff consists of laymen.
You know, in Canada,
we have a saying.
"Wait your turn.
"If you are truly deserving,
an honor will eventually
come to you."
That's why I don't
live in Canada.
There are striations
that indicate
a reciprocating saw was used
to sever the head of the femur.
And here,
the same striations.
There are false-start
kerf marks on this radius.
The blade broke.
And here,
the striations
from the new blade.
So the killer used
a reciprocating saw
to cut up the body.
You know, that moment there
where we were working together
seamlessly
in true harmony
and cooperation--
it was... almost Canadian.
You should write that
in your little book.
We found the saw
in your garage-- the one
you used to cut up the victim.
Ballistic fingerprinting for
a saw blade? I don't think so.
You also broke the blade
when you were cutting him up,
smart guy.
See, that does
leave a fingerprint on the bone.
Look, okay, I'm being set up,
all right?
Somebody tossed a dead guy
over the wall into my backyard.
I didn't even know him.
I'm confused.
Why didn't you call the cops
when this dead body
showed up?
Come on, man.
If I reported him to the cops,
I'd be their number one suspect.
No, no, no, no, no.
Now you're
the number one suspect.
We have your DNA
on the victim.
We also got you
for illegal disposal
of human remains...
I didn't kill him.
It's the dreads, baby.
You're shedding
like a husky in the summer.
You got away
with it last time.
You're not getting away
with it this time.
Wait, wait, wait.
You never mentioned
the name of the dead guy.
And I'm thinking
that's 'cause you don't know.
Yeah.
I got that right.
Listen, all right,
I didn't kill him.
All I did was feed
his body to the pigs.
But I saw his face
before those pigs ate it.
I can get you
a description.
So...
you ready to deal, G-Man?
So, labs came back negative--
there was no blood found
in Jarrick's trunk.
Well, he was meticulous.
He was careful not to
bleach the saw blades,
so he probably used
plastic sheets, right?
No. Guy-- he's got no motive.
Forget him, okay?
But Angela got an I.D.
based on Jarrick Henry's
description.
Oh, my God.
You know him?
That's Albert Magnuson.
The chess guy?
Anyone who knows chess
knows Albert Magnuson.
I used to be a serious
chess player, till college.
Then I became a little obsessed,
had to give it up.
But Albert's a genius,
brilliant.
Turns out, Magnuson was
bringing in some serious cash.
Angela found out
this information.
Check out
the Web site here, huh?
Your chess champion--
he was bringing in
some serious merchandise.
And there's some big
companies thought they could
cash in if chess
made it into the Olympics.
They were buying the master.
Yeah.
But all the names
and likeness of Albert Magnuson,
all the merchandizing
and the sponsorship--
that just goes
to Levitt Holdings.
All right, so?
There's only one chief officer
of Levitt Holdings--
Suzanne Levitt.
Oh, and with Magnuson gone, she
gets to keep all of his money.
Right. I'm bringing her in.
I can't believe this.
Who would
murder Albert?
Well, that's what
we're trying to find out.
When was the last time
you saw him?
Two days ago.
We had lunch,
then he went to the chess club,
and I-I didn't
see him after that.
Your relationship with Albert
wasn't just business
though, was it?
He lived with me
and my son Tim.
We were going to be married.
In going over his life, we've
red-flagged a couple of issues
regarding his finances;
you controlled
all of the finances, right?
All of it.
Well, all Albert wanted to do
was play chess.
You're saying it was
out of concern for Albert
that you controlled
all of his money?
I didn't kill Albert.
I loved him.
And you made him
all of his money.
Right. Magnuson
chess boards,
TV appearances,
chess retreats...
I had a background
in marketing;
why shouldn't Albert
capitalize on his talent?
And where were you
two nights ago?
Home. Alone.
And unless my cat can talk,
I have no alibi.
But you should really be talking
to Albert's ex-wife.
She hated him.
She burned down his apartment.
So, Magnuson's ex-wife Ingrid
is a member
of the Dutch Reformed Church.
He wasn't; that caused
the couple to drift apart.
Well, it's a very
strict religious sect.
Right. Well, you know, she was
here on a visitor's visa.
It expired and...
it was never surrendered.
She's living under the radar;
she'll be hard to find.
We'll find her.
We will find her.
Booth, do you think
I'm being small-minded
about Cam getting
the award and not me?
Yes.
What?
You might want another answer,
but I can't give that to you.
But I'm clearly
the best scientist.
And are you a worse scientist
because Cam's getting the award?
Of course not.
See?
Yeah. So you're just being petty
because you want to win.
I thought you would
take my side.
I am on your side, okay?
I'm on your better side.
Huh?
Much better side.
Oh, hey.
Hey, guys.
Yeah.
So, I called
the Mayfair Chess Club
where Magnuson was last seen.
I know some people there
from my chess days.
Apparently, Magnuson had a lot
of enemies in the chess club.
You think that the killer
could be a chess player?
Yeah, I think
it's very possible.
The killer did use Jarrick
to dispose of the body,
basically sacrificing him
like a chess piece, right?
There's a strong connection
between chess and the logic
and forethought needed
to plan and execute a murder.
Look, I'll tell you what,
why don't you go
to the chess club
and see what you can dig up.
So you're saying that
I'm the lead on the case?
No. You're the...
chess nerd on the case.
Lead chess nerd--
good enough for me.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Hey.
Guess I shouldn't
be surprised to see you here.
Dr. Sweets,
this is my son Tim.
Y-You're investigating
Albert's murder, aren't you?
Do me a favor,
keep it on the down low.
- Sure.
- I have to go, Tim.
Call me when you're done?
Yeah.
You don't drive?
Uh, Mom's been trying
to spend more time with me.
Especially since... you know.
Mm-hmm.
Were you and Albert close?
My mom met Albert through me.
He was kind of my mentor here.
Like-like a second father to me.
Right.
Sweets!
Hey, Romanov,
good to see you.
You have been
conspicuously absent
for the past decade.
Whoa, Sweets! Hi, Lance!
Hey, guys.
These-these guys know you?
Ten years ago, Sweets was one
of the youngest chess masters
in the federation.
Brilliant.
Yeah, I'm probably
very rusty at this point.
Ah, I think not.
Remember the old Russian saying:
"You cannot drink
your glass away."
I look forward
to sitting
opposite you again, Sweets.
You want to
show me around?
Sure.
Um...
You are good.
Yeah, good and rusty.
I'd like to be
as rusty as you are.
Sorry about Magnuson, son.
I hope he didn't misinterpret me
the last time we spoke.
No, sir, it was very clear
how you felt.
Seems like a lot
of people here
had an issue with Mr. Magnuson.
Sweets, right?
Dimitri told me about you.
Magnuson was
a good player.
Great, even.
But?
But nothing.
Mr. Wakefield
used to be my teacher.
And then you started
studying with Albert.
Before you jump
to ugly conclusions,
I never liked Albert, true,
but I was with Tim
when it happened.
At the deli.
I wasn't accusing you
of anything.
I'm sorry for your loss, Tim.
If you need
my help again,
just let me know.
Magnuson was last
seen headed here.
His parking's spot
somewhere over there.
Where, in the dark?
Lights are broken.
Any suspects
at the chess club?
Well,
you know, like a lot
of brilliant people,
Magnuson had a huge ego,
left little room for others.
Ah. So no one was, uh,
mourning his loss.
Oh... look at that.
Broken glass.
Ah.
Light's broken.
Hold up.
Broken lights
all over the place.
A good place
for an ambush.
Lot of water on the ground here;
must be a busted pipe.
Yep, there it is.
Security camera--
hopefully it's infrared.
Could be our lucky day.
Get some
footage off it.
Found his parking spot.
Look at that.
Blood.
This is where Magnuson
was killed.
I've got more blood
over here.
Impact hit?
Probably.
Spatter pattern looks
like someone may have
smashed the victim's head
against the wall.
This may match
the skull fractures
we found on the occipital.
Looks like
water evaporated,
- leaving rock salt.
- Excuse me, sir.
Yeah?
I'm wondering how long
you're gonna be tying up
our parking garage?
As long as it takes, I'm afraid.
Some of our members had
to park in the street,
and my car is
blocked in over there.
Yeah, murder's such
an inconvenience, right?
The hard drive
from the surveillance camera
is totally fried.
Our killer was pretty thorough.
I did manage to get the time
that it was fried though.
2:30 a.m. on the night
that Magnuson was murdered.
That syncs up
with Jarrick Henry's story.
He said the body was dumped
at his place at 3:30 a.m.
I'll tell Booth.
I... called...
Science Monthly.
Oh. You didn't
turn them down, did you?
Not exactly.
But I did tell them
that if they didn't honor
you and Dr. Brennan as well,
that I couldn't
accept the award.
You... you told
them to honor me?
Oh, my gosh,
you're so sweet.
Hey, we're nothing
without each other, Angela--
that's a fact.
You're amazing.
Wait till
I tell Brennan.
I'd like to tell her myself--
if this all works out.
Mate.
Bravo.
You have not lost
your edge, Mr. Sweets.
Thank you, Dimitri.
It's my pleasure.
Bishop's pair checkmate--
that is so cool.
Yeah, I saw
Kasparov do that.
Study the greats--
that's what Magnuson taught me.
Well played.
He's a master.
Uh, this is An Ni.
It's nice to
meet you, Annie.
Not Annie. An Ni.
An, first name; Ni, last.
You guys'll
have to excuse me.
I have a game starting.
Is that you up
there, Annie--
uh, An... An...
Ni.
Yes.
I had a good year.
They let me hold the plaque.
When was the
picture taken?
A month or so ago,
I think-- I'm not very good with time.
Oh.
What happened
to Magnuson's hand there?
Olin.
Tiffin Olin.
He broke it with a clock timer.
Is Olin in the photo?
No. He got kicked out
of the club for that.
Mm.
That's him.
When did you last see Olin?
You ask so many questions,
curious guy.
Weeks ago.
Olin plays in the park now.
Tiffin Olin.
FBI. Special Agent
Seeley Booth.
Need to ask you
a few questions
about Albert Magnuson.
I'm playing.
When I finish these games.
Take a break.
Albert Magnuson was murdered.
We know you broke
his hand in the past.
Why'd you break his hand?
Oh, God.
Oh, no.
Whoa, easy, easy!
Hold it right there.
Nice and slow.
Don't do
anything stupid.
On the table.
Easy.
What is that?
A sandwich?
When I get stressed, I eat.
You're accusing me
of killing Albert,
so I'm stressed, I want to eat.
Okay, listen, you can
eat after we talk.
Magnuson was crazy.
He told everybody that my
cell phone gave off vibrations
in Morse code a-and
that's how I was winning.
Well, was it?
Are you crazy?
He just wanted me
out of the tournament
because I was his only
serious competition.
Where were you three nights ago?
It's embarrassing.
More embarrassing than
sitting in an FBI holding cell?
I'm lonely.
Okay.
I got arrested
for propositioning
a prostitute
who turned out to be a cop.
I spent the night in jail.
I-I'm sure you can
verify that.
Booth.
I found Magnuson's
ex-wife Ingrid
through her church.
She's in McLean, Virginia,
working as a nanny
for a church family
under her maiden name...
Ingrid Vanderlube.
C-Can I have my sandwich now?
Yeah, you can have
your sandwich.
Okay, I'll go bring her in.
I thought my life
with Albert was good.
But getting those
pictures in the mail...
was a real wekroep.
I'm sor... A real what?
Wake-up call.
It's Dutch.
Right.
Wow... whoa.
What was going on in those
photos was unnatural.
Evil.
And this is Albert and...
The hellhag.
Suzanne Levitt.
She sent them.
The hellhag.
Right, you saw
these photos, and, uh,
you got upset and you...
burned down his place.
Albert betrayed me.
He became an unholy apostate.
A phallacist.
Right, that sounds dirty.
His apartment needed
to be cleansed by fire.
Right.
So you got off the grid.
Yes.
Earthly laws shouldn't apply
in that situation.
All right, well,
you live on Earth, Ingrid,
and those laws
do apply to you, so...
Where were you
three nights ago?
At the house where I work.
The family was out,
but I was there.
Okay.
Please, d-don't tell
them about this.
I need that job.
Well, I wouldn't
get your hopes up.
I mean, um, your visa's expired
and you burn down apartments.
DNA confirmed
that the burned flesh
found in the pig slop
was from the victim.
And take a look at this.
There are microblisters in the
stratified squamous epithelium
and the external
horny layer.
And enlarged vacuoles
within the epidermal cells.
The cells are flattened.
What part of the body
was this tissue taken from?
The feet.
Ah. Now, see,
these phalanges may show signs
of avulsion fractures
due to subluxation.
You're right, but
it's not subluxation.
There's a complete
separation there.
I think I know what happened!
This is wonderful to see.
Note the capsular ligaments
and coracoacromial ligaments
show signs of stretching
and abnormal position.
If you add these findings
to the stress fractures
and numerous avulsion fractures...
We will find that
the answer to how our victim
was killed came from the feet.
The feet.
My, my, my.
I'm surprised to see such
a patriotic Canadian gloating,
Dr. Filmore.
You're absolutely right.
I'm sorry.
A negative note about a
Canadian, Dr. Filmore?
Oh, yes.
A report without negative
comments about a Canadian
would be unacceptable in Canada.
Excuse me.
What's going
on in here?
Well, let's see
if you're as good
as you want us all to think
you are, Sweets.
There were actually
people who...
I have seniority.
You take white.
I won't need the advantage.
All right.
♪ I heard that girls like you
were hard to find ♪
♪ I'm sure it's something that
just takes some time from... ♪
Mate.
Wow.
♪ Your motivation's
not that hard to see... ♪
What's his problem?
How's it going?
♪ Real interesting
♪ From tearing out your heart
♪ That's beating like a drum
♪ From dancing to the tune of
♪ I don't even know
who you are... ♪
Mate.
♪ And you know you will get
what you want by now ♪
♪ And you want it now...
Mate.
♪ And you know you will get
♪ What you want somehow
♪ And you will somehow,
you will somehow... ♪
Big mistake.
Check.
Mate, Annie.
An Ni.
Right.
I will study this game
and beat you next time.
Patterns. Patterns.
Do you know what I'm saying?
Patterns.
♪ That's beating like a drum
♪ From dancing
to the tune of... ♪
Guess it's my turn.
♪ And you know you will get
♪ What you want somehow
♪ And you will somehow,
you will somehow... ♪
Okay.
You know my game play.
I've been watching you.
And I looked up your old games
on the federation database,
just like Albert taught me.
Hey, Hodgins found
clamp marks
in the 480-volt main
in the parking garage
where the killer
tied into the panel
and created his own circuit.
Because of Dr. Filmore,
we know the killer planned
to electrocute Magnuson
as he got into his car.
No accolades, please;
they embarrass me.
That was merely
a statement of fact.
Hmm. So, uh, how did the killer
connect the circuit
to the victim?
According to Hodgins,
the killer
poured water and rock salt
onto the garage floor.
Creating an extremely conductive
electrical environment.
Uh, this should be
an accurate reconstruction
of the murder.
As Magnuson
returned to his car,
the killer placed
the live end
of the circuit into the water
and fried him.
And the shock was so traumatic,
it literally blew
the victim's toes off.
And created stress
and avulsion fractures
throughout the body.
And launched him into the wall
where we found
the bloodstains.
Breaking bones of his left hand
when it hit first.
The surge of power fried the
surveillance camera hard drive.
And blew out
the jelly jar lights.
The only problem is
that none of our suspects
could have been there
when this happened.
Except the woman
he was going to marry.
Well, you-you had me there.
Why didn't you
sacrifice your queen?
I didn't see it.
I don't believe that
for a second.
What's he doing?
Make your move.
You want to take a nap?
No, I'm fine.
You're playing
way above your rating.
Magnuson wasn't your mentor.
He thought he was.
All right.
Checkmate.
Wow, nice.
He did it.
Tim Levitt, you're under arrest
for the murder
of Albert Magnuson.
You arrested this kid
'cause he beat you at chess?
Listen, he could've won
much earlier in the game,
but he refused
to sacrifice his queen.
His queen? Okay, do you know
how crazy you sound right now?
It's symbolic of Tim not wanting
to sacrifice his mother.
The two of them are too close.
Plus, he didn't yawn when I did.
That's not gonna hold up
in court.
It's a test for sociopaths.
A normal person,
when they see someone yawn,
they yawn.
Sociopaths don't
'cause they don't have empathy.
The kid has an alibi. He was
at a deli, but his mother...
The mother was going
to marry Magnuson.
To Tim, he was being replaced.
He's guilty, Booth.
He's guilty; I know it.
Fine. Let me go
talk to him.
No, no, no, let me.
No.
We got him for six hours
before we have
to release him; let me at him.
No. You're a shrink;
I'm a trained interrogator.
But this isn't
a normal interrogation, is it?
To Tim, this is chess.
And every move he's made so far
has been a brilliant
and careful calculation.
Okay, one shot.
That's it.
If I see you going south
with this,
or you're screwing it up, I'm
gonna pull you from the room.
Great.
It's been two hours.
Why are you keeping me here?
I haven't done anything wrong.
Sit down, Tim.
Let me tell you
what we know so far.
Is that the killer?
He's so young.
Yeah, and very smart.
You dumped the body
at Jarrick's house
because you knew he'd
get rid of it for you.
You introduced me to An Ni
'cause you knew
she'd lead us to Tiffin Olin.
You've been playing us all
from the beginning,
like we're your chess pieces.
Dr. Sweets,
I didn't do anything like this.
- Let me tell you what I think.
- See, that's good.
He's staying in control,
not letting him say
that he's innocent.
Take his coat off;
it says that,
you know what, he
ain't going anywhere.
Dr. Sweets,
I loved Albert.
I would never do any...
You didn't love Albert.
Nobody did.
Even your mom said
that he was volatile
and had a temper.
People would say
that you did the world a
favor by taking him out.
What Sweets is saying is absurd.
It's called developing themes.
He's giving him
alternative versions
of the crime
so he might admit to it.
But it's not working.
Well, of course it's not.
I mean, if he was guilty,
he'd be leaning back.
Oh, right.
Because kinesiology suggests
that he'd maintain
as much distance
from his accuser as possible.
Fascinating.
So, I managed
to retrieve a
partial image
from the surveillance
camera hard drive.
Now, this is the moment
when Magnuson
was electrocuted.
Take a look at this.
On the left is Magnuson,
and on the right is the killer.
But look at the time stamp.
He was killed two hours
earlier than we thought.
Wait. But your analysis
of the hard drive showed
it was fried at 2:30 a.m.
Because there were
two power surges.
There was one at 12:30,
which killed Magnuson,
and another at 2:30 which fried
the surveillance hard drive.
How did he cause
the second power surge
when he was at the deli?
My guess:
he isolated the circuit
for the surveillance camera,
put it on a timer,
and came back later
and removed the evidence.
Tim has no alibi.
Unfortunately,
this is not enough evidence
for a conviction.
We need a confession.
I'd like some more water,
please.
You've had
enough water, Tim.
Setting that trap
to electrocute Albert--
now, that required
a lot of expertise.
You could have
killed yourself.
Lucky for you,
you took that electrical
engineering course in school.
Mr. Wakefield worked
as an electrician for years.
Maybe you should talk to him.
He's countering
every move Sweets makes.
This is like chess.
He's playing this perfectly.
Your mom had a couple of
boyfriends before Albert,
and those ended
badly, too, huh?
Too? My mom
and Albert were happy.
His temper, the fighting,
his wanting you to move out.
He didn't want that.
We were close, all of us.
That's not
what your mother said.
You're really reaching,
Dr. Sweets.
And you're leaning back, Tim.
If I could hit the
timer now, I would.
Boom. That was good.
You're the only one
that your mother
could count on, right?
You're the only one
that can make her happy.
Albert made her happy.
Albert made...? Okay.
Well, taking these photos
of Albert and your mom
and sending them to his ex-wife
Ingrid-- that sounds like
a happy family, right?
I didn't take any photos,
Dr. Sweets.
You would do anything
to protect your mom.
That's why you refused
to sacrifice your queen.
That's why you killed Albert,
isn't it?
Sweets' logic
is quite manipulative
and very impressive.
You're inventing a motive based
off of a chess game we played?
Really, Dr. Sweets?
I thought
you were smarter than that.
Game play mirrors
the personality of the player.
Didn't Albert teach you that?
All I can say is the same thing
I've been saying
for the last three hours.
I did not kill Albert Magnuson.
Well, I'd advise you to
call your lawyer, Tim.
Why? I haven't done
anything wrong.
I really would like
that water now,
please, if that's all right.
I just need one more shot
with him.
Trust me, Sweets,
this is gonna work, okay?
Booth is right. It's
like the queen sacrifice
Marshall used against
Levitsky in 1912.
What?
He wouldn't see that coming.
How'd you know about that?
I play, too.
Not like you, of course.
I've been trying
to teach Booth, but
he keeps referring
to the knights as "horsies."
That's great.
Can we just move this along?
Okay, chess is
a one-on-one game,
but in a real war,
you need a platoon,
and that's what
we are right now, okay?
So let's move out.
I'd like to apologize, Tim.
You're free to go.
We found the killer.
What?
I was mistaken,
and I'd like to offer my help,
because this could be
very difficult for you.
I don't understand.
Your mother had access to your
electrical engineering books.
That doesn't mean anything.
There's more, Tim.
We have a partial DNA match from
the trunk of the victim's car.
It's either yours or your mom's.
You have an alibi,
and she doesn't.
My mom wouldn't do that.
This is clearly painful for you.
I-I misunderstood
your relationship
with your mother.
She was the one who'd do
anything to protect you.
She felt that Albert
was taking you away from her.
No, you've got it all wrong.
No, Tim.
She confessed.
Confessed?
Tim! Timmy!
Mom.
Tim, call a lawyer.
Hold him
back, Sweets.
Timmy...
Hold him back! Hold him back!
Call me a lawyer!
You-you can't do this.
It wasn't her!
I did it!
I set a timer.
That's how I got my alibi.
It wasn't her!
I killed Albert!
You did what?
I did it!
That-that was my DNA!
I... I'll-I'll tell you
everything!
Just don't take my mom.
No.
I had to.
I had to protect you.
I couldn't let another guy
take you away!
Tim, what have you done?
What have you done?
You were right.
He couldn't sacrifice
his own queen.
Dr. Brennan,
I just thought
I'd drop by your office
before I leave.
You've finished cleaning
the bone room already?
Well, actually, I won't be
cleaning the bone room,
Dr. Brennan,
and I thank you for that.
That makes no sense.
I'm asserting myself--
something I learned from you,
which I intend to share
with all my Canadian colleagues.
I've decided, like you,
I'm too extraordinary to clean.
But...
You've been
an excellent example
to me, Dr. Brennan.
Be confident, be stubborn,
and shout down
the opposition, eh?
Well, I...
I must go now.
And you're welcome
for my outstanding expertise.
Oh, you're
also welcome.
What's this?
This is from Science Monthly.
Oh, Cam,
I'm actually very happy for you.
Apologies are difficult for me.
No. I appreciate that,
Dr. Brennan,
but they actually want
to honor all three of us.
Oh. Really?
Because Cam insisted.
We're nothing
without each other.
Well, agreed,
but I've never heard
of them honoring
three women before.
Well, uh, this year,
there are 12.
Twelve?
They, uh... they sent us these
for a photo shoot.
They're doing a calendar
this year.
12 Outstanding Women of Science
showing a lot of skin.
Magazine's having
budget problems,
and they thought
this would help.
I can tell them
to call three other scientists.
Who are the nine scientists
who agreed to this?
Um...
Oh. Dr. Katherine Kasarinsky...
Oh, she's a brilliant
quantum physicist.
Dr. Jennifer Austin.
She won the National
Medal of Science.
Yes.
Dr. Sun Yoon Chang...
She's a Delta Science Fellow.
So they actually are
outstanding women of science.
I would hate to think of
three less outstanding women
replacing us.
But we'll be hanging in labs
all across the country.
Exactly.
We have a duty to show
the scientific community
that the Jeffersonian
is an institution
where pulchritude
is as abundant
as brilliance.
I never thought
that I would be
honored in this way.
Okay.
Oh, my God.
Dr. McClintock looks
wonderful on your breasts.
Lookin' good.
Oh, my God.
I'm glad I got
Madame Curie.
I can't...
Ah!
No...
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
What?
You can't make that move.
Why?
Bishops can only move diagonally.
I thought that was the castle.
That's a rook. It's called a rook.
Chess is like school.
Why can't we just play checkers?
No, there's no sophisticated
strategy in checkers.
How about we have a game
of Ready, Set, Fun?
What? Christine's game?
Yeah.
No, it's for children.
What, you think I'm gonna kick
your ass in the Happy Hideaway?
No, we're playing
chess, Booth.
Right.
It's my move.
Here we go!
I'm not doing this, Booth.
Come on.
I'll be Tom Foolery...
...and you can be
Wendy Whoopee!
No, no, no.
I'm always
Hildy Highjinks.
Hildy Highjinks, right.
You're getting into it, right?
Okay, tell you what:
if you pick a card
that says Two Giggles,
you got to do a shot.
One game.
That's all it's gonna take.
Ready, set, pick.
Okay.
I think I should come
to the photo shoot with you.
Ooh...
I really do.
Not going to happen.
Right.
Dah! Two Giggles! Drink!
No, it's your card.
You drink.
Hey... we both drink.
Okay?
There it is.
Down the hatch.
Mmm. You know what?
I want to come
to the photo shoot with you.
You know, for science.
No.
Look who's going to
Happy Hideaway.
Who's giggling now?
Isn't this a lot better than chess?
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
What's that mean?
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org