Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
_
"There will be no mob justice today.
Trust in the law."
Mama!
It's time to go.
_
Run! Run!
Hurry!
Don't backtalk
me, boy! Get up there!
Come on! Come on!
Stay down!
Hey! Get back here!
Get back here!
Get 'em!
Over there!
Watch out!
All right. We're here.
I told you, ain't no room!
Just the boy then.
Hey! Hey! Goddammit, O. B.!
It's gonna be okay, baby. All right?
You're gonna go with Heck and Liddy,
and they're gonna get
you someplace safe.
Are you comin' too?
We're gonna be right
behind you, all right?
Get her!
We gotta go now!
Don't move.
Hey, get your thumb out your mouth, boy.
O.B., come on! We gotta go!
- Be strong.
- Okay.
Get down.
_
You're okay.
Aah, shit!
Shit, shit.
This interaction
is being recorded.
Do you consent?
Yes, sir. Sure.
It is... 9:35 p. M., September 8, 2019.
Initiated traffic stop.
How are you tonight, sir?
Good. Yeah, fine. Thanks.
- How are you?
- What you drinking there?
Oh, uh...
Coca-Cola, sir.
Mm.
What are you hauling?
Lettuce.
Lettuce?
- Yes, sir.
- Can I take a look?
Can I take a look at
your face?
What did you just say to me?
Hey, I'm-I'm sorry, officer.
- I was just kidding.
- License and registration.
They're in the glove.
I'm just gonna reach over
and open it on up, okay?
Go ahead.
Three-five, returned to vehicle.
I need Weapons Autho. Who's on the desk?
Panda. I'll patch you through.
Shit. No, wait. Is there anyone else...
This is Panda. What's up?
Hey, I just made a traffic stop.
Subject refused a search of his truck,
and I observed Kavalry
contraband in his glove.
Requesting firearm lock release.
What kind of contraband?
It was a Rorschach mask.
Are you sure?
I saw it. Panda, come on.
Release my weapon.
Probability of drugs and/or alcohol
- in the subject's vehicle?
- High.
Probability of firearms and/or explosives
- in the vehicle?
- High.
What's your overall perceived
threat level from the subject?
High. Just... buzz me, okay?
Stand by.
It's not working, I didn't get it.
Buzz me again, man.
Stand by.
We good?
Yeah, I got it. Thank you.
They bring my uniform up?
Next room over.
- Mind if I have a minute?
- Of course, sir.
You running background
checks on all the nurses
and orderlies that saw his face?
Yep.
We got roadblocks up
on all the egresses,
but he's probably gone to ground.
Sent a couple units out
to the address on his DL,
but the house was boarded up.
- Kavalry?
- More than likely.
You want me to call in Red and Night?
No.
Let 'em sleep.
She gonna be pissed.
Why in Christ's name would
they start this shit up again?
Maybe there was somethin' in the truck
they didn't want found.
Somethin' like what?
There was a head of
lettuce in Sutton's car.
Shooter must've tossed it in.
I believe it was romaine.
Were there any croutons?
Not that I could ascertain.
You don't start a war
over goddamn lettuce, Wade.
Come over here and pull your face down.
Mrs. Sutton?
Roberta.
Roberta, I'm Judd.
May I come in?
Yeah.
There was a shooting.
Charlie's in surgery now.
When he's out, we're gonna move him
to our secure medical
facility over at the precinct.
Ah. Okay.
Can I go see him?
Of course.
Did he tell anyone that he was police?
That's against the rules.
Yeah.
But people still talk.
He didn't.
Where did he tell folks that he
was going when he was on shift?
Night school, for engineering.
All right.
We'll say it was a carjacking.
He was leaving school and
that's when he got shot.
Why?
We have protocols.
We just want to keep everybody safe.
Safe.
- Yeah, I know what you're thinkin'.
- Mm-hmm.
Fuck me and the horse I rode in on.
He liked you.
No. He likes me.
Egg whites are made of protein.
When we whip 'em, we get bubbles,
and it's the proteins that form
the walls of those bubbles.
If we don't have walls, it
all comes tumblin' down.
Now, those walls are strong,
but they won't stay that way
if just even a little bit of yolk
gets mixed in with the whites.
So, that's why we gotta separate 'em.
- Ta-da!
- Wow!
Can we eat our cookies now, please?
Y'all go ahead.
Okay, Ms. Abar, while
they're stuffing their faces,
maybe you can explain to
them what they're eating.
Oh, um...
It's called a banh bia.
When I was a little girl in Vietnam,
we called them "mooncakes."
Oh, were you born there before
or after it became a state?
Um, a couple years before.
Um, I was born just outside of Saigon
and when I grew up, I
was a police officer there
until I moved here to Tulsa.
Did you stay a police officer?
For a while, then I retired.
Why?
Um...
I was one of the cops who got
attacked on the White Night.
And that was before police
officers were allowed to wear masks.
So, the bad guys, they knew who I was
and they knew where I lived,
and they came to my
house and they shot me.
Right here.
And the doctors, they had
to pull apart my insides
to find the bullet and get it out
- 'cause they didn't want it to...
- Ahem.
Oh, um, anyway.
I figured making cakes and cookies
was better than getting shot.
So, I quit the police force
and opened up a bakery.
Mm-hmm?
Did Redfordations pay for it?
Excuse me?
Your bakery... did you
pay for it with Redfordations?
Tommy!
Ooh! Topher!
Don't tilt your head
back, just pinch your nose.
Why'd you hit him?
'Cause you wanted to hit him.
He's ten years old.
You still wanted to.
He said... Redfordations.
I heard him.
- He's a racist.
- He's not racist.
But he's off to a good start.
Oh, goddammit.
Maybe it's a false...
It smells.
Well, at least your nose is working.
- Oh, get the truck.
- Get the truck!
Hey.
- We're cleaning up the squids.
- Thanks, baby!
Hey, you left your pager. It's
been going off all morning.
What's Little Big Horn?
I gotta go to the bakery.
You pick up Rosie from school?
Of course.
Sweetie, I need you to go with Dad
and pick up your sister
from school, okay?
Don't let him drive too fast.
- I love you, sweetie.
- Love you too, Mommy.
I also love you.
Don't drive fast.
No TV!
The clock is ticking.
The New York Times is calling it
the most important television
event of the new millennium.
Tomorrow night, the countdown ends.
American Hero Story: Minutemen.
- Do you own that place?
- Mm-hmm.
- When is gonna open?
- A couple months.
Mm-hmm.
I'll wait.
Hey.
You think I can lift 200 pounds?
Sure you could.
Whoa! Hey!
Cop carcass
on the highway last night.
Soon, the accumulated black
filth will be hosed away,
and the streets of Tulsa will
turn into extended gutters
overflowing with liberal tears.
Soon all the whores and race
traitors will shout "Save us!"
And we will whisper... No.
We are the Seventh Kavalry.
We are no one. We are
everyone. We are invisible.
And we will never compromise.
Do not stand between us and our mission,
or there will be more dead cops.
There are so many
deserving of retribution
and there is so little time.
And that time is near.
Ticktock. Ticktock. Ticktock. Ticktock.
Ticktock.
Ticktock. Ticktock. Ticktock.
Ticktock. Ticktock. Ticktock. Ticktock.
Ticktock! Ticktock! Ticktock!
Ticktock! Ticktock! Ticktock! Ticktock!
Kavalry's back.
Three years of peace,
and we convinced ourselves
that they were gone.
But they were just hibernating.
Good thing we know
where their caves are.
So roll into Nixonville
and round 'em up,
and drag their asses into
the pod for interrogation.
One of them's gonna give up the shooter.
Warrants-free, weapons hot?
We are Article Four.
Panda, buzz out the guns.
"An emergency 24-hour
release of deadly weapons
- can be authorized only...
- Shut the fuck up, Panda.
...if the majority of the police force
believe their lives are under
direct immediate threat."
LG...
do you believe your life is
under direct and immediate threat?
Yes, I do.
What about you, Red?
Absolutely.
Firearms release is authorized.
Chief, you're making a mistake.
Yeah, well...
it's my funeral.
Quis custodiet ipsos custodes?
Nos costodimus!
Why didn't you call me?
Wanna take your feet
off my desk, please?
Kavalry involved shooting last night,
and I don't get a Little
Big Horn until two hours ago?
We were still working
the scene. It was late.
Mm. I know why you didn't call me.
Why?
You were mad that my sitter bailed
and you had to suffer
through black Oklahoma
without having someone
to roll your eyes at.
- Sitter bailed?
- Yes.
Well, you and Cal missed out,
because black Oklahoma
was delightful.
You are not allowed to call it that.
You gonna give me the speech now?
What speech?
About how I'm overreacting
by calling Article Four,
and I should calm down and take a
breath before we're at war again.
There's a guy in my trunk.
I knew you were gonna tell
us to round up the likelies.
I just got a jump on things.
You knew?
Yes.
How do you know he's Seven K?
I got a nose for white supremacy,
and he smells like bleach.
So, put him in the pod?
Put him in the pod.
Howdy.
I'm just gonna ask you
a series of questions.
Answer them honestly
and you can go home.
Do you know why you're here?
Some bitch dressed like a nun
kicked in my door and put me
in the trunk of her fucking car.
That is correct.
I want my lawyer.
Yeah, we really don't
have to do that with terrorists.
I... I'm not a terrorist.
How long have you lived in Tulsa?
Uh, five years... six. Almost six.
What did you have for
breakfast this morning?
Cereal, I think.
If I defecated on the American flag,
how would that make you feel?
Defecated?
Shit. If I took a shit
on the American flag,
how would that make you feel?
Confused.
Are you a member of or
do you associate with
members of the white
supremacist organization
known as the Seventh Kavalry?
No.
Do you believe that
transdimensional attacks
are hoaxes staged by
the U.S. Government?
I dunno, maybe.
Are you a member of or
do you associate with
members of the white
supremacist organization
known as the Seventh Kavalry?
You already asked me that.
- Should all Americans pay taxes?
- Yes.
Are you a member of or
do you associate with
members of the white
supremacist organization
known as the Seventh Kavalry?
Are you a member of or
do you associate with
members of the white
supremacist organization
known as the Seventh Kavalry?
Are you a member of or
do you associate with
members of the white supremacist group
known as the Seventh Kavalry?
No... No.
Well?
He knows.
You sure?
He's not gonna talk sans motivation,
but he was off the charts
on the bias questions.
Eyes dilated on all the Rorschachs.
Yeah. I'm sure.
Like I said...
bleach.
Cop got shot, so we're
all a little wound up here.
But still that's no excuse
for how I treated you.
Sorry.
Yeah, okay.
Appreciate your understanding.
Fuck!
Fuck you!
Where... is... he?
Where is he?!
Where... is... he?!
Cattle ranch.
We're almost at the
house. Is there any movement inside?
Do you got a head count?
Looks like four.
Maybe five.
Cops! Pack it up! Let's go!
Let's head on out! Come on!
Aw, shit! They're moving!
Go. Go now!
Take that.
All right. Come
on, boys, let's go!
Come on! Come on!
Down! Down! Everybody down!
They've
got a fucking plane.
Come on, go!
Aah!
Fucker!
Spit it out! Spit it out, motherfucker!
Spit it out!
Fuck!
Pill?
Fucking coward!
Where are the others?
Shit!
Crawford! Crawford! Two of them got out.
They're taking off.
They're right under you.
All right. Bring her out.
Good.
Stay with 'em.
Higher.
- Higher, damn it!
- I'm trying!
Chief, fucking
quit! The ship can't take it!
Fuck!
Are you okay?
Oh, shit!
What the fuck?
- Welcome home, Master.
- Thank you, Alphonse.
Your thighs are quite raw, Master.
Yes, I rode quite a distance yesterday.
But don't worry, Ms. Crookshanks.
Have at it.
Sir.
Shall I dress you?
Looks a little formal, Mr. Philips.
- Is it a special occasion?
- Of course it is, Master.
It's your anniversary.
Ah. Hmm.
Well, it looks delicious.
We used the honeycomb
you gave us, Master.
Ah.
Would you like to cut it, sir?
That is a horseshoe, Mr. Philips.
I'm so sorry, sir.
- Would a knife be more appropriate?
- No, it's...
It's all right.
It's the bee's knees.
Mmm.
Happy anniversary, Master.
You had discarded
some drawings of it, sir.
The pieces were most intricate.
But I tried my very best
to get it to function.
I...
wanted to surprise you, sir.
It's exquisite, Mr. Philips.
Speaking of surprises, I
have a surprise for you.
I've started writing a play.
It's a tragedy in five acts.
When it's finished, I
want the two of you...
to play the leading roles.
And what do you call it, Master?
The Watchmaker's Son.
ROSIE, EMMA: Truman, President
Eisenhower, President...
Okay, we get it!
ROSIE, EMMA: ...Nixon, President
Ford, President Redford!
- All right, baby girl!
- I'm gonna get another bottle.
Rosie and
Emma, I am officially convinced
that one day another little
girl will be listing your names.
You hear that?
Maybe Aunt Jane will be
your campaign manager.
Alas, as wonderful a president
as you both would be,
I've quit politics.
My mommy quit her
job too. She was a policeman.
Um, I didn't quit,
sweetheart. I retired.
What's the difference?
Topher, don't be disrespectful.
Better not stand up for her or
she'll take away your TV too.
All right.
Cal, I'm taking away your TV.
Ha-ha! Mommy took your TV away!
Wait a minute.
What happened? What'd I miss?
ROSIE, EMMA: No TV for anybody!
Oh, no! That's horrible!
Cal, this
was a wonderful meal.
Totally worth getting
ditched for Oklahoma.
Ditched for what?
Oh.
Oh, well, you didn't even tell him?
- I spared him.
- What? What's happening?
You didn't know that your sitter bailed?
Babe, you hate musicals.
Nobody hates Oklahoma!
- You did.
- No. I thought it was great.
Then why'd you tell me at intermission
that their hearts weren't in it, hmm?
- Really? Okay.
- Yeah...
He's just jealous because he
played Curly in high school.
No way!
ROSIE, EMMA: Who's Curly?
Curly... Curly is the star of Oklahoma.
He gets the girl, he kills the bad guy,
- and he sings a lot.
- Sing, Uncle Judd!
- No, no, no.
- Yeah, Uncle Judd, sing!
No. No!
All: Sing! Sing! Sing!
Of course he sings.
Oh, my turn.
Watch batteries?
Mm-hmm. Pulled a duffle
out of that plane you blew up.
There was a couple
hundred of them in there.
Well, can't you just buy
those at any old store?
No. Not anymore, they're the old
kind. The synthetic lithium...
the ones that were making people sick.
Oh, I get it.
Kavalry's gonna make a cancer bomb.
I don't know.
But that fucker in the video
said that they had a mission,
and it was gonna happen soon.
Aren't you worried?
Oh, Angela.
I'm worried as fuck.
Hey. What are you two
talking about that's taking so long?
Oh, nothing. Just the end of the world.
Ticktock. Ticktock. Ticktock. Ticktock.
The clock is ticking.
We're running out of time.
Evil is rising.
Second by second we all cry out...
Yes, sir. You
bet. We got them all.
Well, shooter took some
sort of damn poison pill
before we could interrogate
him, but... you know.
Uh, well...
Yeah, there's always a
chance of reprisal, Governor,
but we just gave 'em a pretty good taste
of what happens when
you take one of ours.
Well, you're welcome, Governor.
Bye now.
- How'd I do?
- You sounded very confident.
That's because, my dear,
I am full of confidence.
Yeah, I noticed some of it
coming out of your nose at dinner.
It's been a tough week.
Yeah.
It's the hospital.
- Charlie Sutton just woke up.
- Oh.
I'm gonna
change into my uniform,
and I'm gonna go over there
and I'm gonna see him.
Baby, maybe you shouldn't drive.
I'll get one of the
boys out front to take me.
You don't have to wait up for me.
But it's a
helluva name, isn't it?
Senator Joe Keene was a real cowboy,
unlike our current Sundancer in Chief.
Thirty years of Redford and
what've we got to show for it?
More land we can't live on,
more animals we can't kill,
and a six-month wait to get
a gun for our own protection.
Hell, if Joe Junior wants to mount up
and gallop into the White
House, I say let him ride!
Shit.
Oh! Jeez...
We should... we should answer that.
No. I'm close, I'm close.
It's gonna wake up the kids.
Okay, okay, okay.
Goddammit.
Hello.
Is this Angela Abar?
Yes.
Is your father Marcus Abar?
Who is this?
Big oak tree out on Rowland Hill.
Something you need to see there.
I know who you are,
so don't wear no goddamned mask.
What?
Watch the street. If anybody
pulls up other than me,
fucking shoot 'em before
they get to the porch.
Okay.
Turn it off!
Or I'll shoot!
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
Who are you?
I'm the one who
strung your chief of police up.
You're 90 fucking years old,
how the fuck did you hang him?
I am 105, and you curse too much.
You didn't kill him.
This doesn't make any sense.
Just get those fuckers
who did this to him.
Okay.
Laurie Blake, FBI. I'm here to help.
Folks assume
the Seventh Kalvary did it.
But that's not what you assume?
There are people who
believe that this world...
is fair and good.
It's all lollipops and rainbows.
We don't do lollipops and rainbows.
'Cause we know those are pretty colors,
that just hide what
the world really is...
black and white.
The only
way to stave off mankind's extinction
is with a weapon more powerful
than any atomic device.
That weapon...
is fear.
There's a vast and
insidious conspiracy at play.
I have a secret plan to save humanity.
And it starts in Oklahoma.
She threatens to disrupt the peace.
Are we safe, Angela?
What did you do?
Mankind is ready for change.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org