Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
What's the matter, mister?
The water's come!
Here now.
Hold your left hand lower.
Try using your right hand...
...get less tired then.
Not enough sleep.
You can rest.
You're not used to it yet.
Were my veins filled with cement,
I bet I'd feel this way.
Get tired at first.
Will I ever get used to it?
You will.
I don't know.
Don't you feel
all this is meaningless?
Are you raking sand to live,
or living to rake sand...?
Of course, it's not so much fun
as Tokyo.
I'm not talking about Tokyo!
How can you stand being
trapped like this?
But it's my home.
Then demand your rights.
In my case, it's only till
I'm rescued.
Rescued?
Of course.
Away a week without leave.
Someone will call on me.
They'll see the book left open
in my room...
...the small change in my pocket.
They're bound to wonder.
But for you,
it's a lifelong problem.
My family's graves are here.
Yes, my husband and girl...
Then you...?
You'll leave if they're dug up?
You know how to make them
let down the ladder.
I've nothing to do outside.
You could walk around!
Walk around?
Yes!
It's great to walk around freely!
Wouldn't you get more tired
just walking around?
Don't joke!
Even dogs go crazy tied up
forever!
And we're men!
But if it weren't for the sand,
no one would bother about me.
Isn't it so? Even you...
Look, here's one.
Stop it!
This is what I came out here
looking for.
A kind of tiger-beetle.
Got any scissors?
Scissors?
I just want to clip my beard.
I think I have some...
They're not very sharp.
They're pretty rusty.
The sand does it.
They don't work.
No?
Not even close.
We'll ask for a razor
when they bring the ration.
See? The sand in my beard
makes it all scratchy.
Really! That sand just makes
a mess of everything.
Say, hurry up!
All right! Thanks!
Where's your "husband"?
Stomachache. Chilled, perhaps.
Love him too much?
A bath? Shall I help?
No, I'm tired today.
I'd like one.
No, you're sick.
My body feels sticky.
I must have sweated in bed.
I can boil it...
Let's. I'll help.
Never mind, I'll do it.
Thinking?
Not especially.
I'll take you. Stand there.
No, don't.
Come on.
Smile now.
Want to go home?
Why?
A radio would be good for you.
You'd hear about the world.
Silly!
You'd know all about Tokyo then.
That's what started me
collecting insects.
Having my name in an insect
book's better than nothing.
But a radio would take your
mind off things.
I see.
Finish off that sake?
You're still sick.
Helps you sleep.
I feel sleepy enough without it.
Be a sport.
I can't drink.
Never mind. I feel like it today.
Looks boiling.
Come on.
You amaze me.
Now, drink up.
My, that feels good.
You're cruel, when I'm so tired.
Help!
Someone help me!
Catch hold of it.
Please pull me out with this.
We can't pull you out
like a root.
We'll dig you out.
Grab on to the board.
Good thing we made it.
Quicksand around here.
Even the dogs won't come near.
How many people fell in before?
Hikers don't know about it.
If we dug, might find
something valuable.
Two or three cameras for sure.
Be quiet.
I'm sorry.
Shall I make some tea?
What's the time?
I don't know... about 8:30?
I failed.
Yes.
Complete and utter failure.
Do you have...
...a wife?
In Tokyo...
That's no concern of yours.
No.
But it's too bad.
If I'd succeeded, I was going to
buy a radio and send it to you.
A radio?
You wanted one...
That's all right.
You don't have to do that.
I can do piece-work
and buy one here.
I failed.
Shall I wipe you up?
I should have known the geography.
They'll always come after me.
Behind me will be friends,
a cooperative...
...the Board of Education
and the PTA...
They won't leave me to my fate.
Come on. I'll wash you.
What is it?
My hope.
A crow trap.
I leave a bait here.
When a crow gets it,
the sand will swallow it.
But crows are very clever.
Hunger makes them stupid.
But why is this your hope?
It is.
I'll tie a letter to its leg
asking for help.
They don't come.
It's almost three months.
Who?
Your rescuers.
They may think you ran away...
Tired of your work.
Hardly.
I left my bankbook.
I left my book open on my desk.
Anyone would know.
The room's screaming for help.
What's there?
What?
In Tokyo...
So I said to go and see!
It's too much.
Your ration!
Say, wait! Wait!
Let me up awhile!
Thirty minutes, once a day,
to see the sea!
I promise not to escape!
Twenty minutes! Even ten!
I've been good for three months!
I'm going out of my mind!
We'll talk it over and let you know!
Please! You can watch me!
Working hard.
Twenty more and I'll earn 1,000 yen.
Stupid!
I won't die like a dog!
Radio, nothing.
You'll be beyond help soon.
How can they be your friends?
I know it.
Everyone for himself.
Wagging your tail like a good dog.
Soon, we'll only have ourselves.
That can't be! We have the sand!
Sand? What's good in it?
Just makes trouble.
It sells.
Where?
At the town works.
Are you joking?
Against the law... it's salty!
In secret... at half price.
A total loss if it eats away
dams and buildings.
That's other people's business.
Yes, it's other people's business.
But this phony business
makes others rich.
Why help them?
The union buys and sells it.
They treat me very well.
I'll sift it.
Like building a house on water.
A boat might be better.
Why insist on a house?
But you want to go home, too?
That's...
Even a lie will do.
Perhaps, tomorrow...
If there's hope that
something may happen...
I'm so frightened each morning
when I go to sleep.
Afraid I'll wake up all alone again.
I'm really so frightened...
Put them in there.
Working hard, mister?
Too early for the carrier.
You want to see the sea?
Yes. Please! Will you let me?
We might consider it.
Please. I learned my lesson.
All right for an hour?
Then show us that.
Out in front, both of you,
where everybody can see you.
That?
Yes, that.
You know, with your old lady.
You know!
I asked the others.
They said, "sure"!
What're you doing? Hurry up!
What'll we do?
It's ridiculous!
It's my chance.
Don't listen.
Look, we needn't take it so
seriously.
What? We're not perverts!
We're pigs, anyhow!
Come on! Just pretend!
Fool! Fool! Fool!
What's this?
Funny.
Not a drop of rain for three weeks.
Capillarity?
That's it!
It may mean
we'll have enough water.
Surface evaporation must be
acting as a suction pump.
The sand's a pump.
Like sitting on a pump.
Perhaps I can think of a more
effective system to store the water.
It's awful. Can't even breathe.
It'll be December soon.
Again.
Getting cold and food's scarce.
Easier to catch a crow.
Really, men are...
My turn to be the trapper.
If the radio came, we could
hear the weather report.
I'm afraid.
I'll bury it while the water boils.
Till tomorrow!
Help!
Someone, come here!
What is it?
Pains!
A baby.
A baby?
Since when?
October.
Hurt?
Nausea?
May be an abnormal pregnancy.
How do you know?
He used to shoe horses for
a veterinarian.
Anyway, call a doctor!
He'll be too late.
Doctors nowadays...
Get a small truck.
It's come.
I'm afraid.
Is the wind down?
Yes, it's quieter.
How?
Bedding and all.
Let's do it.
Put a board beneath.
Radio.
The radio.
Bad timing. Shall I open it?
Want to take it?
In the bedding.
Have you got another board?
Take one from the shelf
out back.
Below there. That one.
I don't want to go!
Listen, it's...
Something?
No, some other time.
I don't want to.
Pull her up!
No.
No...no...!
There's no need to rush away yet.
I am free to do as I like now.
What I want now is to tell someone
about the water tank.
It will be best to tell the villagers.
If not today, maybe tomorrow.
I'm sure I'll end up
telling somebody.
After that I can think of escaping.
REPORT OF MISSING PERSON
JUMPEI NIKI,
BORN MARCH 7, 1927
MISSING OVER 7 YEARS
LISTED AS DISAPPEARED
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org